<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Application Name="war_thunder">
  <SettingInfo Name="Advanced Shore">
    <Image>war_thunder_001.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="669" Top="618" />
    <TextRect Height="97" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Increases the visual quality of shores ******* adds more realistic water effects in their proximity.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">زيادة جودة الرؤية للدعامات وإضافة المزيد من انعكاسات الماء الواقعية في المقربة.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Zvyšuje vizuální kvalitu břehů a přidává realističtější efekty vody v jejich blízkosti.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Forøger den visuelle kvalitet på kysten og tilføjer mere realistiske v*******effekter i deres nærhed.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Steuert die visuelle Qualität von Küsten und fügt in deren Nähe realistischere Wassereffekte hinzu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Αυξάνει την οπτική ποιότητα των παραλιών και προσθέτει πιο ρεαλιστικά εφέ νερού στην εγγύτητά τους.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Increases the visual quality of shores ******* adds more realistic water effects in their proximity.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Aumenta la calidad visual de las orillas y añade efectos de agua más realistas en su proximidad.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Aumenta la calidad visual de las costas y agrega efectos de agua más realistas en las proximidades.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Parantaa rantojen visuaalista laatua ja tekee niiden lähellä olevista vesitehosteista entistä realistisempia.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Améliore la qualité des rivages et ajoute des effets d'eau plus réalistes à proximité.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">הגדרה זו מגדילה את האיכות החזותית של חופים ומוסיפה אפקטים ריאליסטיים יותר של המים הנמצאים בקרבתם.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Javítja a partok vizuális minőségét, és valószerűbb vízeffektusokat jelenít meg a partok közelében.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Aumenta la qualità visiva delle rive e aggiunge effetti dell'acqua più realistici in prossimità.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">海岸の映像クオリティを向上させ、よりリアルな水のエフェクトを付近に追加します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">해변의 시각적 품질을 높이고 해변 주변에 사실적인 물 효과를 더합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Verhoogt de visuele kwaliteit van kusten en voegt meer realistische watereffecten toe in hun omgeving.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Øker den visuelle kvaliteten på strender og legger til flere realistiske vanneffekter i nærheten.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Zwiększa jakość obrazu brzegu i dodaje bardziej realistyczne efekty wody w jego pobliżu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Aumenta a qualidade visual das margens e adiciona efeitos mais realistas nas suas proximidades.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Aumenta a qualidade visual das margens e adiciona efeitos de água mais realistas nas proximidades.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Повышает качество отображения береговых линий и добавляет реалистичные водные эффекты вдоль них.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Zvyšuje vizuálnu kvalitu pobrežia a pridáva realistickejšie efekty vody v blízkosti pobrežia.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Zveča vidno kakovost obal in doda bolj realistične vodne učinke v njihovi bližini.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Ökar den visuella kvaliteten på stränder och lägger till mer realistiska vatteneffekter i deras närhet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">เพิ่มคุณภาพของภาพชายหาด และเพิ่มเอฟเฟกต์น้ำที่เหมือนจริงยิ่งขึ้นในบริเวณใกล้เคียง</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Kıyıların görsel kalitesini artırır ve kıyıya yakın sulara daha gerçekçi su efektleri ekler.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">提高海岸的视觉质量，并在海岸附近添加逼真的水景效果。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">提高海岸的視覺品質並且在他們的附近增加更逼真的水效果。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Anisotropy">
    <Image>war_thunder_002.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="152" Top="550" />
    <TextRect Height="97" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Improves the sharpness of textures, especially those viewed at a distance or on an angle.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">تحسين حدة مواد الصور المعروضة وخاصة تلك الموجودة على مسافة أو على زاوية.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Zvyšuje ostrost textur, zejména těch zobrazených na dálku nebo z úhlu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Forbedrer skarpheden på teksturer, især dem som ses på afst******* eller ved en vinkel.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Verbessert die Schärfe von Texturen, vor allem von solchen, die aus der Ferne oder in einem Winkel betrachtet werden.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Βελτιώνει την ευκρίνεια των υφών, ιδιαίτερα αυτών που προβάλλονται σε απόσταση ή υπό γωνία.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Improves the sharpness of textures, especially those viewed at a distance or on an angle.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Mejora la nitidez de las texturas, especialmente las que se ven a una distancia o en un ángulo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Mejora la nitidez de las texturas, especialmente las que se pueden ver a una cierta distancia o desde un ángulo determinado.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Parantaa pintakuvioiden terävyyttä, erityisesti kun niitä katsotaan kaukaa tai tietystä kulmasta.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Améliore la netteté des textures, en particulier celles vues à une certaine distance ou selon un certain angle.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">משפרת את החדות של מרקמים, במיוחד אלה שנצפים מרחוק או בזווית.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Javítja a textúrák élességét, különösen azokét, amelyek távolról vagy kis szögben láthatók.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Migliora la definizione delle texture, in particolare di quelle visualizzate a una certa distanza o angolazione.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">特に遠距離または角度から見たテクスチャの鮮鋭度を高めます。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">특히 원거리 또는 사선 방향에서 볼 수 있는 텍스처의 선명도를 높입니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Verbetert de scherpte van patronen, met name wanneer deze op afst******* of in een hoek worden bekeken.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Forbedrer skarpheten i teksturer, særlig dem som vises på avst******* eller på skrå.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Zwiększa ostrość tekstur, w szczególności tych widzianych z odległości lub pod kątem.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Melhora a nitidez das texturas, em particular qu*******o vistas à distância ou em ângulo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Melhora a nitidez das texturas, principalmente as que são vistas à distância ou de certo ângulo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Повышает четкость текстур, особенно при просмотре издалека или под углом.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Zvyšuje ostrosť textúr, predovšetkým tých, ktoré sú zobrazované v diaľke alebo z určitého uhla.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Izboljša ostrino tekstur, posebno tistih, ki se jih vidi od daleč ali pod kotom.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Förbättrar skärpan för texturer, speciellt sådana som visas på avstånd eller i vinkel.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับปรุงความคมชัดของพื้นผิวให้ดีขึ้น โดยเฉพาะเมื่อดูจากระยะห่างหรือจากมุมหนึ่งๆ</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Dokuların, özellikle de uzaktan veya açılı olarak bakılan dokuların keskinliğini artırır.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">增加在特定距离或角度看到的纹理的锐度。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">提高特別是從遠處或一個角度觀看時的紋理鮮明度。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Anti-aliasing">
    <Image>war_thunder_003.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1066" Top="396" />
    <TextRect Height="225" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Enables post-process anti-aliasing. FXAA is a low-cost anti-aliasing, which removes jagged edges from game elements. TAA, Temporal Anti-Aliasing, reduces the visibility of shimmering edges when the player's camera is in motion, ******* further improves the quality of edge ******* transparency anti-aliasing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">تمكين منع ترادف العملية اللاحقة. FXAA عبارة عن منع ترادف منخفض التكلفة، والتي تزيل الحواف المسننة من عناصر اللعبة. TAA، منع الترادف المؤقت، الذي يعمل على تقليل رؤية الحواف المضيئة عندما تكون كاميرا اللاعب في وضع الحركة، مع تحسين جودة الحواف بشكل إضافي ومنع ترادف الشفافية.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Aktivuje post-processing vyhlazování hran. FXAA je low-cost vyhlazování hran, jež odstraňuje zubaté okraje z herních prvků. TAA, dočasné vyhlazování hran, snižuje viditelnost třpytících se hran, když je kamera z pohledu hráče v pohybu, což dále zvyšuje kvalitu vyhlazování hran a průhlednosti.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Aktiverer udjævning under efterbeh*******ling. FXAA er en billig udjævningsteknik, som fjerner takkede kanter fra elementer i spillet. TAA (Temporal Anti-Aliasing) reducerer synligheden af flimrende kanter, når spillerens kamera er i bevægelse, og forbedrer yderligere kvaliteten på udjævning af kanter og transparens.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Aktiviert Antialiasing-Nachbearbeitung. FXAA ist eine leistungsschonende Antialiasing-Technik zum Glätten der Kanten von Spielelementen. TAA, temporales Antialiasing, verringert die Sichtbarkeit flimmernder Ränder, wenn die Kamera des Spielers in Bewegung ist, und steigert zusätzlich die Qualität von Kanten- und Transparenz-Antialiasing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Ενεργοποιεί τη μετεπεξεργαστική εξομάλυνση ορίων. Το FXAA είναι μια εξομάλυνση ορίων χαμηλού κόστους, η οποία αφαιρεί τα ανώμαλα άκρα από τα στοιχεία παιχνιδιού. Το ΤAA είναι μια χρονική εξομάλυνση ορίων, η οποία μειώνει την ορατότητα των άκρων που λαμπυρίζουν όταν η κάμερα του παίκτη βρίσκεται σε κίνηση και βελτιώνει περαιτέρω την ποιότητα των άκρων και την εξομάλυνση ορίων διαφάνειας.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Enables post-process anti-aliasing. FXAA is a low-cost anti-aliasing, which removes jagged edges from game elements. TAA, Temporal Anti-Aliasing, reduces the visibility of shimmering edges when the player's camera is in motion, ******* further improves the quality of edge ******* transparency anti-aliasing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Activa el antialiasing de postprocesamiento. FXAA es un antialiasing de bajo consumo de recursos que elimina los bordes rugosos de los elementos del juego. TAA, el antialiasing temporal, reduce la visibilidad del reflejo de los bordes cu*******o la cámara del jugador está en movimiento, y mejora aún más la calidad del antialiasing de la transparencia y de los bordes.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Activa el suavizado de líneas durante el posprocesamiento. FXAA es un suavizado de líneas de bajo costo, que elimina los bordes distorsionados de los elementos del juego. El suavizado de líneas temporal, TAA, reduce la visibilidad de reflejos en los bordes cu*******o la cámara del jugador está en movimiento y mejora aún más la calidad del suavizado en los bordes y las transparencias.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ottaa käyttöön jälkikäsittelyreunanpehmennyksen. FXAA on keveä reunanpehmennys, joka poistaa rosoiset reunat pelin elementeistä. TAA, ajallinen reunanpehmennys, vähentää reunojen hohtoa, kun pelaajan kamera liikkuu, ja parantaa entisestään reunojen laatua ja läpinäkyvyyden reunanpehmennystä.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Active l'anti-crénelage post-traitement. Le FXAA est un anti-crénelage peu gourm******* en ressources qui adoucit les contours des éléments du jeu. L'anti-crénelage temporel (TAA) réduit la visibilité des contours scintillants lorsque la caméra du joueur se déplace. Améliore également la qualité de l'anti-crénelage des contours et de transparence.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מאפשרת החלקת שינון בעיבוד נוסף. FXAA היא החלקת שינון בעלות נמוכה, שמסירה קצוות משוננים מרכיבי משחק. TAA, החלקת שינון בממד הזמן, מפחיתה את הנראות של קצוות מרצדים כאשר המצלמה של השחקן נמצאת בתנועה, ומשפרת אף יותר את איכות החלקת השינון של קצוות ושקיפות.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Bekapcsolja az utófeldolgozó élsimítást. Az FXAA egy kis teljesítményigényű élsimítás, amely eltávolítja a játék elemeiről a recés éleket. A TAA (időbeli élsimítás) csökkenti a vibráló élek láthatóságát, amikor a játékos kamerája mozgásban van, valamint tovább javítja az elsimítás és az áttetszőségi élsimítás minőségét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Attiva l’antialias post-elaborazione. FXAA è una tecnica di antialias poco esigente in termini di risorse che rimuove i bordi dentellati dagli elementi di gioco. TAA, l'antialias temporale, riduce la visibilità del tremolio dei bordi qu*******o la telecamera del giocatore è in movimento, miglior*******o ulteriormente la qualità dell'antialias per bordi e trasparenze.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">ポストプロセスアンチエイリアシングを有効化します。FXAA はローコストのアンチエイリアシングで、ゲーム要素からエッジのギザギザをなくします。TAA は時間的アンチエイリアシングで、プレーヤーのカメラが作動中に揺れつきのあるエッジの可視性を低減し、エッジおよびトランスぺアレンシーアンチエイリアシングのクオリティをさらに向上させます。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">후처리 앤티엘리어싱을 활성화합니다. FXAA는 게임 요소에서 거친 가장자리를 제거하는 저비용 후처리 앤티엘리어싱입니다. TAA는 플레이어의 카메라가 이동할 때 시머링 가장자리의 가시성을 줄여주는 임시 앤티엘리어싱을 활성화하여 가장자리 및 투명도 앤티엘리어싱의 품질을 향상합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Schakelt anti-aliasing tijdens nabewerking in. FXAA is een voordelige anti-aliasing, waarmee gerafelde r*******en uit game-elementen worden verwijderd. TAA is tijdelijke anti-aliasing, waarmee de zichtbaarheid van glinsterende r*******en wordt verminderd als de camera van de speler in beweging is, waardoor de kwaliteit van anti-aliasing voor r*******en en transparantie wordt verhoogd.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Aktiverer etterbeh*******lingskantutjevning. Skyggebasert kantutjevning er en etterbeh*******ling av kantutjevning, som fjerner ujevne kanter fra spillelementer. TAA, midlertidig kantutjevning, reduserer synligheten av flimrende kanter når spillerkameraet er i bevegelse, og som forbedrer kvaliteten på kant- og transparensutjevning ytterligere.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Włącza wygładzanie krawędzi w przetwarzaniu końcowym FXAA to niewymagające wygładzanie krawędzi, które usuwa poszarpane krawędzie elementów w grze. TAA to czasowe wygładzanie krawędzi, które zmniejsza widoczność migoczących krawędzi, gdy kamera gracza jest w ruchu i jeszcze bardziej zwiększa jakość wygładzania krawędzi i przezroczystości.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Activa o antialiasing de pós-processamento. FXAA é um antialiasing com pouco impacto no desempenho, que remove as extremidades irregulares dos elementos do jogo. TAAA, antialiasing temporal, reduz a visibilidade da cintilação das extremidades qu*******o a câmara do jogador está em movimento e aumenta a qualidade do antialiasing de extremidades e transparência.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ativa o antisserrilhamento de pós-processamento. O FXAA é um antisserrilhamento de baixo custo que remove bordas irregulares de elementos do jogo. O TAA, antisserrilhamento temporal, reduz a visibilidade da cintilação de bordas qu*******o a câmera do jogador está em movimento e melhora mais a qualidade do antisserrilhamento de transparências e bordas.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Включает постсглаживание. FXAA — это нетребовательное к ресурсам сглаживание, которое устраняет "ступенчатость" краев игровых объектов. Временное сглаживание (TAA) делает мерцание краев при передвижении камеры игрока менее заметным, что еще больше повышает качество сглаживания краев и прозрачности.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Zapína dodatočné vyhladzovanie. Vyhladzovanie FXAA je nenáročné vyhladzovanie, ktoré odstraňuje z prvkov hry kostrbaté okraje. TAA, dočasné vyhladzovanie, znižuje viditeľnosť trblietajúcich sa hrán pri pohybe kamery hráča, čím ešte viac zvyšuje kvalitu vyhladzovania hrán a priehľadnosti.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Omogoči naknadno glajenje robov. FXAA, naknadno glajenje robov, je poceni glajenje robov, ki odstrani nazobčane robove z elementov v igri. TAA, začasno glajenje robov, zmanjša vidljivost migljanja robov, kadar se igralčeva kamera premika, in nadalje izboljša kakovost robu in prosojnost glajenja robov.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Aktiverar kantutjämning i efterbeh*******ling. FXAA är en billig kantutjämning som tar bort ojämna kanter från spelelement. TAA, tidsbestämd kantutjämning, minskar skimr*******e kanters synlighet när spelarens kamera är i rörelse, och förbättrar ytterligare kvaliteten i kantutjämning för kanter och transparens.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">เปิดใช้งานการลดรอยหยักหลังการประมวลผล FXAA เป็นการลดรอยหยักที่ใช้ประสิทธิภาพต่ำ ซึ่งจะลบขอบที่มีรอยหยักออกจากองค์ประกอบของเกม TAA เป็นการลดรอยหยักชั่วคราว ซึ่งจะลดการมองเห็นของขอบแบบระยิบระยับเมื่อกล้องของผู้เล่นกำลังเคลื่อนไหว และปรับปรุงคุณภาพของขอบและการลบรอยหยักแบบโปร่งแสงได้ดึขึ้น</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Son işlem kenar yumuşatmayı etkinleştirir. FXAA, oyun öğelerindeki tırtıklı kenarları gideren, düşük maliyetli bir kenar yumuşatmadır. TAA, oyuncunun kamerası hareket halindeyken titreyen kenar hatlarının görünürlüğünü azaltarak kenar ve saydamlık kenar yumuşatmasının kalitesini daha da artıran Zamansal Kenar Yumuşatma'dır.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">启用后处理反失真。快速近似平滑处理是低成本反失真，可消除游戏元素的锯齿状边缘。TAA，即临时反失真，能降低玩家照相机移动时的闪动边缘的可见度，进一步改善边缘和透明平滑处理的质量。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">啟用後續處理消除鋸齒。FXAA 是一種低成本消除鋸齒功能，可以消除遊戲要素參差不齊的鋸齒狀邊緣。「時間消除鋸齒」(TAA) 可以降低玩家的攝影機移動時閃光邊緣的可見性，並且進一步改善邊緣和透明度消除鋸齒的品質。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Cloud Quality (In Flight)">
    <Image>war_thunder_005.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1030" Top="451" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Control cloud quality during flights.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">التحكم في جودة السحابة أثناء الرحلات الجوية.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Nastavuje kvalitu mraků v průběhu létání.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Styrer kvaliteten på skyer under flyvning.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt die Wolkenqualität bei Flügen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Ελέγχει την ποιότητα σύννεφου κατά τη διάρκεια των πτήσεων.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Controls cloud quality during flights.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Controla la calidad de las nubes durante los vuelos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Controla la calidad de las nubes durante los vuelos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ohjaa pilvien laatua lentojen aikana.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Contrôle la qualité des nuages en vol.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">שולטת באיכות העננים במהלך טיסות.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Szabályozza a felhőminőséget repülés közben.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola la qualità delle nuvole durante i voli.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">飛行中の雲のクオリティを制御します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">비행 시 구름 품질을 제어합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de kwaliteit van wolken tijdens vluchten.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Kontrollerer skykvalitet under flyvninger.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Kontroluje jakość chmur w czasie lotów.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Controla a qualidade da nuvem durante os voos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Controla a qualidade da nuvem durante voos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует качество облаков во время полета.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Ovláda kvalitu oblakov počas letov.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Nadzira kakovost oblakov med leti.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Kontrollerar molnkvalitet under flygningar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ควบคุมคุณภาพของเมฆระหว่างเหินฟ้า</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Uçuşlar sırasında bulut kalitesini ayarlar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">控制飞行时的云朵质量。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">控制飛行中的雲朵品質。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Cloud Quality (On Ground)">
    <Image>war_thunder_009.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="324" Top="768" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adjusts the quality of cloud reflections seen on water.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">ضبط جودة انعكاس السحابة التي تظهر على الماء.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Nastavuje kvalitu odrazů mraků ve vodě.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Justerer kvaliteten på skyreflektioner, der vises på v*******.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt die Qualität von Wolkenreflexionen auf Wasser.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσαρμόζει την ποιότητα των αντανακλάσεων σύννεφων που φαίνονται στο νερό.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adjusts the quality of cloud reflections seen on water.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Ajusta la calidad de los reflejos de las nubes sobre el agua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Ajusta la calidad de los reflejos de las nubes que se ven en el agua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Säätää vedessä näkyvien pilvien heijastumien laatua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Règle la qualité des réflexions des nuages sur l'eau.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מכווננת את האיכות של השתקפויות עננים שנראות במים.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Beállítja a felhők vízről való visszatükröződésének minőségét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola la qualità dei riflessi delle nuvole visualizzati sull'acqua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">水面に映る雲の反射のクオリティを調整します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">물에 비치는 구름 반사의 품질을 조절합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de kwaliteit van de reflectie van wolken in het water.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Juster kvaliteten på skyrefleksjoner i vann.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dostosowuje jakość odbić chmur widzianych w wodzie.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Ajusta a qualidade dos reflexos das nuvens na água.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ajusta a qualidade dos reflexos de nuvem vistos na água.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует качество отражений облаков в воде.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Upravuje kvalitu odrazov oblakov viditeľných vo vode.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Prilagodi kakovost odsevov oblakov, ki so vidni na vodi.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Styr kvaliteten på molnspeglingar i vatten.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับคุณภาพของภาพสะท้อนของเมฆที่ปรากฏบนผิวน้ำ</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Suyun yüzeyinde görülen bulut yansımalarının kalitesini ayarlar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">调整水面反射的云朵的质量。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">調整水面上所見的雲朵倒影品質。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Detailed Foliage">
    <Image>war_thunder_007.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1493" Top="254" />
    <TextRect Height="113" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Enables high-cost, high-quality Multisample Alpha-To-Coverage Anti-Aliasing that dramatically improves the visual fidelity of foliage.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">تمكين التكاليف العالية والعينات المتعددة عالية الجودة بداية من ألفا وحتى تغطية مكافحة الخطوط القطرية التي تحسن من الدقة البصرية لأوراق الأشجار والنباتات بشكل كبير.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Umožňuje vysoce kvalitní, na výkon náročné vyhlazování hran Multisample Alpha-To-Coverage, které výrazně zlepšuje vizuální věrnost zeleně.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Aktiverer en dyr Alpha-To-Coverage anti-aliasing i høj kvalitet under multiprøvetagning, der dramatisk forbedrer den visuelle nøjagtighed på løvet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Aktiviert leistungsintensives, qualitativ hochwertiges Multisample-Alpha-To-Coverage-Antialiasing, das die visuelle Detailgenauigkeit von Blätterwerk drastisch steigert.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Ενεργοποιεί υψηλού κόστους, υψηλής ποιότητας, άλφα για κάλυψη εξομάλυνση ορίων πολλαπλών δειγμάτων που βελτιώνει δραματικά την οπτική πιστότητα των φυλλωμάτων.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Enables high-cost, high-quality Multisample Alpha-To-Coverage Anti-Aliasing that dramatically improves the visual fidelity of foliage.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Activa el antialiasing de alto coste y calidad alfa a cobertura, que mejora dramáticamente la fidelidad visual del follaje.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Activa suavizado de líneas multimuestreo, alfa a cobertura, de alto costo y alta calidad, que mejora notablemente la fidelidad visual del follaje.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ottaa käyttöön paljon tehoa vaativan, korkealaatuisen moninäyte-, alfa-peitto-reunanpehmennyksen, joka parantaa huomattavasti lehtien visuaalista todenmukaisuutta.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Active l'anticrénelage par multi-échantillonnage et à couverture par pondération alpha, qui améliore sensiblement la fidélité de la végétation.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מאפשרת החלקת שינון מסוג 'אלפא לכיסוי' באמצעות מולטיסמפלינג, הצורכת משאבי עיבוד רבים, אשר משפרת באופן משמעותי את המהימנות החזותית של עלווה.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Bekapcsolja a nagy teljesítményigényű, jó minőségű, többmintás alfa-fedés átalakítás élsimítást, amely drámai módon javítja a növényzet vizuális minőségét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Abilita l'antialias Alfa a copertura multi-campione ad alta qualità e molto esigente in termini di risorse che migliora sensibilmente la fedeltà visiva del fogliame.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">高コスト、ハイクオリティなマルチサンプル アルファ トゥ カバレッジ アンチエイリアシングを有効化し、群葉の視覚的な忠実度を劇的に向上させます。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">포울리지의 시각적 신뢰성을 극적으로 개선하는 고비용, 고품질 멀티샘플 알파투커버리지(Multisample Alpha-To-Coverage) 앤티엘리어싱을 활성화합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Schakelt kostbare Multisample Alpha-To-Coverage Anti-Aliasing van hoge kwaliteit in die de visuele precisie van gebladerte dramatisch verbetert.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Aktiverer dyr kantutjevning i høy kvalitet med flersampling og alpha-to-coverage som forbedrer den visuelle kvaliteten til bladverket betraktelig.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Wymagające wygładzanie krawędzi wysokiej jakości z wielokrotnym próbkowaniem wewnątrz półprzezroczystych tekstur, które znacznie zwiększa wizualną wierność roślinności.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Activa o antialiasing "Alpha-To-Coverage" de superamostragem de elevada qualidade e que requer mais recursos, que melhora drasticamente a fidelidade visual da folhagem.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Habilita o antisserrilhamento de multiamostragem, Alpha-To-Coverage, de alta qualidade e alto custo que melhora de maneira considerável a fidelidade visual da folhagem.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Включает ресурсоемкое и высококачественное сглаживание со множественной выборкой Alpha-To-Coverage, значительно повышающее визуальную достоверность растительности.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Aktivuje zložité, vysokokvalitné dereferencované vyhladzovanie Alpha-To-Coverage, ktoré výrazne zvyšuje vizuálnu vernosť vegetácie.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Omogoči drago, visokokakovostno večvzorčno glajenje robov od alfa do področja, kar občutno izboljša vizualno zvestobo zelenja. </TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Aktiverar resurskräv*******e, flersampl*******e Alfa till täckning-kantutjämning som drastiskt förbättrar den visuella återgivningen av lövverk.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">เปิดการทำงานการลดรอยหยักแบบ Alpha-To-Coverage แบบหลายตัวอย่างคุณภาพสูงที่มีต้นทุนสูง เพื่อปรับปรุงความสมจริงของใบไม้</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Bitki örtüsünün görsel gerçekçiliğini büyük ölçüde artıran yüksek maliyetli, yüksek kalitede Birden Çok Örneklemeli Kapsanacak Alfa kenar yumuşatmasını etkinleştirir.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">启用能够显著提升树叶的视觉逼真度的高成本、高质量、多重采样透明至覆盖反失真。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">啟用可以顯著地提高植被的視覺逼真度的高成本、高品質多重取樣 Alpha 覆蓋消除鋸齒。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Far Terrain Details">
    <Image>war_thunder_001.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="961" Top="362" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Increases the fidelity of distant terrain details.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">يزيد من دقة تفاصيل التضاريس البعيدة.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Zvyšuje věrnost detailů vzdáleného terénu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Forøger nøjagtigheden på terrændetaljer langt væk.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Erhöht die Detailgenauigkeit ferner Geländeeinzelheiten.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Αυξάνει την πιστότητα των λεπτομερειών απομακρυσμένου εδάφους.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Increases the fidelity of distant terrain details.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Aumenta la fidelidad de los detalles del terreno distante.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Aumenta la fidelidad de los detalles de terrenos distantes.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Lisää kaukaisten maaston yksityiskohtien todenmukaisuutta.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Augmente la fidélité des détails de terrains éloignés.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מגבירה את המהימנות של פרטי פני קרקע מרוחקים.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Növeli a távoli tereprészletek élethűségét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Aumenta la fedeltà dei dettagli del terreno in lontananza.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">遠方の地形のディテールの密度を高めます。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">멀리 있는 지형 디테일의 정확도를 높입니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Verhoogt de precisie van afgelegen terreindetails.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Øker kvaliteten på fjerne detaljer i terrenget.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Zwiększa wierność odwzorowania szczegółów terenu w oddali.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Aumenta a fidelidade dos detalhes distantes no terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Aumenta a fidelidade de detalhes distantes do terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Увеличивает четкость отдаленных элементов рельефа.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Zvyšuje vernosť vzdialených detailov terénu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Poveča verodostojnost podrobnosti oddaljenega terena.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Ökar återgivningen för avlägsna terrängobjekt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">เพิ่มความสมจริงของรายละเอียดภูมิประเทศระยะไกล</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Uzaktaki arazi ayrıntılarının görsel gerçekçiliğini artırır.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">提升远处地形细节的逼真度。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">增加遠處地形細節的逼真度。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Global Illumination Quality">
    <Image>war_thunder_016.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="956" Top="551" />
    <TextRect Height="97" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Improves lighting by simulating the bouncing of light from surface to surface, as in the real world.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">تحسين الإضاءة عن طريق محاكاة قفز الضوء من سطح إلى سطح، كما في العالم الواقعي.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Zlepšuje osvětlení tím, že simuluje odrážení světla z povrchu na povrch, jako je tomu v reálném světě.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Forbedrer belysning ved at simulere lys, der hopper fra overflade til overflade, som i den virkelige verden.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Verbessert die Beleuchtungsqualität, indem simuliert wird, dass Licht von Fläche zu Fläche abgestrahlt wird wie im realen Leben.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Βελτιώνει το φωτισμό προσομοιώνοντας την αναπήδηση του φωτός από τη μία επιφάνεια στην άλλη, όπως στον πραγματικό κόσμο.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Improves lighting by simulating the bouncing of light from surface to surface, as in the real world.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Mejora la iluminación simul*******o la reflexión de la luz de una superficie a otra, como en el mundo real.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Mejora la iluminación mediante la simulación de rebote de la luz de superficie a superficie, como en el mundo real.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Parantaa valaistusta simuloimalla valon heijastumista pinnasta toiseen, kuten todellisuudessa.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Améliore l’éclairage en simulant l’effet de rebond de la lumière d’une surface à une autre, comme dans le monde réel.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">משפרת את התאורה באמצעות הדמיה של החזרת אור בין משטחים, כמו במציאות.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Szimulálja, ahogy a fénysugarak a valódi világhoz hasonlóan felületről felületre verődnek, így javítja a megvilágítást.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Migliora l'illuminazione simul*******o la luce che rimbalza da una superficie all'altra, come nel mondo reale.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">現実の世界にいるかのように、表面から表面への光の跳ね返りを再現することにより、ライティングを向上させます。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">실세계처럼 표면에서 표면으로의 조명 반사를 시뮬레이션하여 조명을 향상합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Verbetert de belichting door te simuleren hoe licht in de echte wereld op oppervlakken schijnt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Forbedrer belysning ved å simulere lys som reflekteres mellom overflater, slik som i virkeligheten.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Poprawia oświetlenie, symulując odbijanie światła od powierzchni do powierzchni, tak jak w rzeczywistym świecie.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Melhora a iluminação simul*******o os ressaltos da luz entre superfícies como no mundo real.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Melhora a iluminação ao simular o rebatimento da luz de superfície para superfície, como no mundo real.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Повышает качество освещения благодаря симуляции реалистичной игры отраженного света.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Zlepšuje osvetlenie simuláciou odrážania svetla od jedného povrchu na druhý ako v reálnom svete.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Izboljša osvetlitev s simulacijo odbijanja svetlobe od površine do površine, kot v resničnem svetu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Förbättrar belysning genom att simulera hur ljus reflekteras från yta till yta, precis som i verkligheten.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับปรุงการจัดแสงโดยการจำลองการตกกระทบของแสงจากพื้นผิวสู่พื้นผิว เช่นเดียวกันกับในโลกความจริง</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Gerçek dünyada olduğu gibi ışığın yüzeyden yüzeye yansımasını taklit ederek aydınlatmanın kalitesini artırır.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">通过模拟光从一个表面跳跃到另外一个表面（和现实世界中一样），提高照明效果。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">透過模擬有如現實世界中光在表面之間的彈跳以改善光源。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Graphics Quality">
    <Image>war_thunder_001.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="419" Top="760" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adjusts all other aspects of the game's graphics through a number of presets.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">يضبط كل الجوانب الأخرى لرسومات اللعبة من خلال عدد من الإعدادات المسبقة.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Nastavuje všechny ostatní aspekty grafiky hry pomocí mnoha přednastavení.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Justerer alle *******re aspekter af spillets grafik gennem et antal forudindstillinger.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt alle *******eren Aspekte der Grafiken im Spiel durch mehrere verschiedene Voreinstellungen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσαρμόζει όλες τις άλλες όψεις των γραφικών παιχνιδιού μέσω ενός πλήθους προεπιλογών.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adjusts all other aspects of the game's graphics through a number of presets.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Ajusta el resto de aspectos gráficos del juego mediante varios ajustes predeterminados.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Ajusta todos los otros aspectos de los gráficos del juego a través de ciertos valores predeterminados.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Säätää pelin grafiikan kaikkia muita osa-alueita useita esiasetuksia käyttäen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Règle les autres aspects graphiques du jeu à l'aide de plusieurs paramètres prédéfinis.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מכווננת באמצעות מספר הגדרות קבועות מראש את כל יתר ההיבטים של הגרפיקה במשחק.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Néhány előbeállítás használatával beállítja a játék grafikájának minden egyéb jellemzőjét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola tutti gli altri aspetti della grafica del gioco tramite una serie di valori predefiniti.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">ゲームのグラフィックスのその他すべての側面を複数のプリセットを使用して調節します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">사전 설정을 충분히 사용해 게임 그래픽의 모든 기타 측면을 조정합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt alle overige aspecten van de graphics van de game door middel van een aantal voorinstellingen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Justerer alle de ytterlige aspektene til spillets grafikk ved hjelp av en rekke forhåndsinnstillinger.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dostosowuje wszystkie inne aspekty grafiki gry za pomocą szeregu ustawień wstępnych.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Ajusta todos os outros aspectos dos gráficos do jogo através de diversas pré-configurações.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ajusta todos os outros aspectos dos gráficos do jogo através de várias predefinições.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует все остальные аспекты графики игры с помощью ряда предустановок.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Upravuje všetky ostatné aspekty grafiky hry pomocou množstva predvolieb.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Prilagodi vse druge vidike grafik v igri z uporabo številnih prednastavitev.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Styr alla *******ra aspekter av spelets grafik med ett antal förvalsinställningar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับคุณภาพด้านอื่น ๆ ทั้งหมดของกราฟิกในเกมโดยใช้การกำหนดค่าล่วงหน้าที่มีให้เลือกเป็นจำนวนมาก</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Çok sayıda önayar yardımıyla oyundaki grafiklerin diğer tüm özelliklerini ayarlar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">通过大量预设来调整游戏画面的全部其他方面。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">利用一些預設來調整遊戲圖形的所有其他方面。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Grass Range">
    <Image>war_thunder_006.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="580" Top="850" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adjusts the distance at which grass is visible.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">يضبط المسافة التي يظل عندها العشب معروضاً.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Určuje vzdálenost, na kterou je tráva viditelná.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Justerer den afst*******, hvorved græs er synligt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt die Entfernung, in der Gras sichtbar ist.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσαρμόζει την απόσταση στην οποία το γρασίδι είναι ορατό.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adjusts the distance at which grass is visible.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Ajusta la distancia a la que la hierba es visible.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Ajusta la distancia a la que se puede ver la hierba.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Säätää etäisyyttä, jolla ruoho näkyy.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Règle la distance d'affichage de l'herbe.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מכוונן את המרחק שממנו נראה העשב.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Beállítja, hogy a fű milyen távolságból legyen látható.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola la distanza di visibilità dell'erba.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">草の表示距離を調整します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">잔디의 가시 거리를 조정합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de afst******* waarop gras zichtbaar is.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Justerer avst*******en hvor gress er synlig.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dostosowuje odległość, z jakiej widoczna jest trawa.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Ajusta a distância à qual a vegetação é visível.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ajusta a distância na qual a grama é visível.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует дальность видимости травы.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Upravuje vzdialenosť, z ktorej je viditeľná tráva.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Prilagodi razdaljo, pri kateri je vidna trava.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Justerar på vilket avstånd gräs syns.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับเปลี่ยนระยะห่างที่ต้นหญ้าแสดงผล</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Otların hangi mesafede görünür olacağını belirler.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">调整草皮的可视距离。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">調整草的可見距離。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Object Shadows">
    <Image>war_thunder_002.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1347" Top="841" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Enables objects in the game world to cast shadows.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">تمكين الكائنات في عالم الألعاب للظلال التي بالجوار.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Umožňuje objektům ve hře vrhat stíny.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Gør det muligt for objekter at kaste skygger i spillets verden.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Ermöglicht es Objekten in der Spielwelt, Schatten zu werfen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Επιτρέπει στα αντικείμενα στον κόσμο του παιχνιδιού να ρίχνουν σκιές.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Enables objects in the game world to cast shadows.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Posibilita que los objetos del mundo del juego proyecten sombras.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Permite que los objetos del mundo del juego proyecten sombras.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ottaa käyttöön pelimaailman esineiden varjot.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Permet aux objets de projeter des ombres.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מאפשרת לעצמים בעולם המשחק להטיל צל.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Lehetővé teszi, hogy a játék világának objektumai árnyékokat vessenek.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Consente agli oggetti nell'ambiente del gioco di proiettare ombre.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">ゲームワールド内のオブジェクトによるシャドウの投影を有効にします。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">게임 세상의 개체에 그림자가 생기게 활성화합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Maakt het mogelijk dat objecten in de gamewereld schaduwen werpen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Muliggjør at objekter i spillet kan kaste skygger.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Włącza rzucanie cieni przez obiekty w świecie gry.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Permite que os objectos no mundo do jogo criem sombras.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Permite que os objetos no mundo do jogo criem sombras.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Позволяет объектам игрового мира отбрасывать тени.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Umožňuje objektom vo svete hry vrhať tiene.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Omogoči, da predmeti v svetu iger mečejo sence.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Gör att föremål i spelvärlden kan kasta skuggor.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ทำให้ออบเจ็กต์ในโลกของเกมทอดเงาได้</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Oyun dünyasındaki nesnelerin gölgelerinin düşmesine olanak verir.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">使游戏世界中的物体投射阴影。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">使遊戲世界中的物體投射陰影。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Particle Density">
    <Image>war_thunder_009.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="930" Top="390" />
    <TextRect Height="97" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adjusts the fidelity ******* density of particle effects, such as those used for explosions.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">يضبط دقة وكثافة آثار الجسيمات، مثل تلك المستخدم في الانفجارات.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Nastavuje věrnost a hustotu částicových efektů, jako jsou výbuchy.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Justerer nøjagtigheden og tætheden på partikeleffekter, såsom dem der bruges til eksplosioner.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt die Detailgenauigkeit und die Dichte von Partikeleffekten wie solchen, die für Explosionen verwendet werden.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσαρμόζει την πιστότητα και την πυκνότητα των εφέ σωματιδίων, όπως αυτών που χρησιμοποιούνται στις εκρήξεις.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adjusts the fidelity ******* density of particle effects, such as those used for explosions.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Ajusta la fidelidad y la densidad de los efectos de partículas, como los que se emplean en las explosiones.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Ajusta la fidelidad y la densidad de los efectos de partículas, como los que se utilizan en las explosiones.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Säätää esimerkiksi räjähdyksissä käytettyjen hiukkastehosteiden todenmukaisuutta ja tiheyttä.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Règle la densité et la fidélité des effets de particules tels que ceux utilisés pour les explosions.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מכווננת את האמינות והצפיפות של אפקטי חלקיקים כגון אלה המשמשים לפיצוצים.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Beállítja a részecskeeffektusok (például robbanások) élethűségét és sűrűségét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola la fedeltà e la densità degli effetti particellari, come quelli usati per le esplosioni.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">爆発などに使用されるパーティクル エフェクトの忠実性や密度を調整します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">폭발에 사용되는 것과 같은 입자 효과의 정확도 및 밀도를 조정합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de precisie en dichtheid van partikeleffecten, zoals die welke worden gebruikt bij explosies.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Justerer kvaliteten og tettheten på partikkeleffekter, som de som brukes ved eksplosjoner.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dostosowuje wierność i gęstość efektów cząsteczkowych, takich jak używane w wybuchach.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Ajusta a fidelidade e a densidade dos efeitos de partículas, como os utilizados em explosões.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ajusta a fidelidade e densidade de efeitos de partículas, como aqueles utilizados para explosões.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует качество и насыщенность эффектов, использующих частицы (например, эффекты взрывов).</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Upravuje vernosť a hustotu efektov častíc, napríklad tých, ktoré sa používajú pri výbuchoch.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Prilagodi zvestobo in gostoto učinkov delcev, kot so tisti, uporabljeni za eksplozije.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Justerar återgivning och densitet för partikeleffekter, t.ex. explosioner.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับความคมชัดและความเข้มของเอฟเฟกต์อนุภาค เช่น เอฟเฟกต์ที่ใช้สำหรับระเบิด</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Patlamalarda kullanılanlar gibi parçacık efektlerinin görsel gerçekçiliğini ve yoğunluğunu ayarlar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">调整颗粒物体（例如爆炸中的颗粒物体）的逼真度和密度。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">調整例如那些用於爆炸的顆粒效果的逼真度和密度。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Physics Animation for Suspension Model">
    <Image>war_thunder_002.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="896" Top="515" />
    <TextRect Height="97" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Realistically animates the suspension of tanks to improve immersion.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">تعزيز حيوية الدبابات المتوقفة بشكل واقعي لتحسين انتشارها.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Realisticky animuje odpružení tanků a navozuje tak pocit ponoření se do děje.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Giver en realistisk animation af affjedringen af tanks for at forbedre livagtigheden.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Sorgt für eine realistische Animation der Federung von Panzern, um das Eintauchen in das Spiel zu verbessern.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Κινεί ρεαλιστικά την αιώρηση των τανκς για να βελτιωθεί η εμβύθιση.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Realistically animates the suspension of tanks to improve immersion.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Anima de forma realista la suspensión de los tanques para mejorar la inmersión.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Anima de manera realista la suspensión de los tanques para mejorar la inmersión en el juego.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Luo realistisen animaation säiliöiden pysäytyksestä uppoutumisen parantamiseksi.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Anime de façon réaliste la suspension des chars pour améliorer l'immersion.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">הנפשה מציאותית של המתלים של טנקים, לשיפור הנאמנות למציאות.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Valószerűen animálja a tankok felfüggesztését, ami fokozza a játékélményt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Anima in modo realistico la sospensione dei carri armati per migliorare il livello di immersione nel gioco.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">実体感を向上させるために戦車の停止をリアルにアニメーション化します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">탱크의 서스펜션을 현실감 있게 애니메이션하여 몰입도를 높입니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Animeert op realistische wijze de ophanging van tanks om de beleving te verbeteren.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Animerer opphenget til tanker på en realistisk måte for å forbedre immersjonen i spillet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Powoduje realistyczną animację zawieszenia czołgów w celu zwiększenia wierności.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Anima realisticamente a suspensão dos tanques, de modo a melhorar a imersão.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Anima realisticamente a suspensão de tanques para melhorar a imersão.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Реалистичная анимация танковой подвески, повышающая достоверность.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Realisticky animuje pohyb tankov, čím zvyšuje zážitok.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Realistično animira vzmetenje tanka, da izboljša vživetje.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Animerar stridsvagnarnas fjädring realistiskt, vilket förbättrar upplevelsen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">สร้างภาพเคลื่อนที่สำหรับการหยุดของรถถังอย่างสมจริงเพื่อปรับปรุงภาพที่สามารถดึงอารมณ์ร่วม</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Gerçekçi bir şekilde tankların yaylanma animasyonunu yaparak in*******ırıcılığı artırır.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">真实地以动画绘制坦克暂停，从而提升沉浸感。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">現實懸掛坦克車的逼真動畫以提升沉浸感。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Physics Quality">
    <Image>war_thunder_013.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="684" Top="726" />
    <TextRect Height="209" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adjusts the visual quality of building, wall ******* object destruction powered by NVIDIA GameWorks' Destruction technology. At higher detail levels more debris is rendered, as are more dust ******* smoke particles, ******* the various components of the effect persist for longer on-screen before fading out.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">ضبط الجودة البصرية للبناء والجدران وتدمير المواد  التي تعمل بتقنية تدمير NVIDIA GameWorks. تقديم مستويات تفاصيل أعلى لمزيد من الحطام، وكذلك المزيد من جسيمات الغبار والدخان، ومختلف عناصر التأثير التي تستمر لفترة أطول على الشاشة قبل أن تتلاشى.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Nastavuje vizuální kvalitu budovy, stěny a destrukci objektu vytvořených pomocí technologie destrukce NVIDIA GameWorks. Při vyšších úrovních detailů je renderováno více nečistot, jako jsou částice prachu a kouře a jednotlivé složky efektu přetrvávající na obrazovce déle, předtím než vymizí.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Justerer den visuelle kvalitet på ødelæggelse af bygninger, mure og objekter drevet af NVIDIA GameWorks' destruktionsteknologi. Ved højere detaljeniveauer gengives der mere affald, såvel som flere støv- og røgpartikler, og de forskellige komponenter af effekten forbliver længere tid på skærmen, før de udtones.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt die visuelle Qualität der Zerstörung von Gebäuden, Mauern und Objekten mithilfe der Zerstörungstechnologie von NVIDIA GameWorks. Bei höheren Detailstufen werden mehr Geröll und mehr Staub- und Rauchpartikel dargestellt, und die verschiedenen Komponenten der Effekte bleiben länger auf dem Bildschirm erhalten, bevor sie verblassen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσαρμόζει την οπτική ποιότητα της καταστροφής κτιρίων, τοίχων και αντικειμένων που βασίζονται στην τεχνολογία καταστροφής του NVIDIA GameWorks. Σε υψηλότερα επίπεδα λεπτομέρειας, φωτοαποδίδονται περισσότερα σκουπίδια, όπως και περισσότερα σωματίδια σκόνης και καπνού, και τα διάφορα συστατικά του εφέ επιμένουν για περισσότερο στην οθόνη πριν σβηστούν βαθμιαία.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adjusts the visual quality of building, wall ******* object destruction powered by NVIDIA GameWorks' Destruction technology. At higher detail levels more debris is rendered, as are more dust ******* smoke particles, ******* the various components of the effect persist for longer on-screen before fading out.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Ajusta la calidad visual de la destrucción de edificios, paredes y objetos gracias a la tecnología de destrucción de NVIDIA GameWorks. Con niveles más altos de detalle se representan más escombros, polvo y partículas de humo. y los diversos componentes del efecto tardan más en desaparecer.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Ajusta la calidad visual de la destrucción de edificios, paredes y objetos, potenciado por la tecnología de destrucción GameWorks de NVIDIA. En niveles más altos de detalle, se generan más escombros, así como más partículas de polvo y humo; además, los diversos componentes del efecto permanecen por más tiempo en la pantalla antes de desvanecerse.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Säätää rakennusten, seinien ja esineiden tuhoamisen visuaalista laatua, joiden takana on NVIDIA GameWorksin tuhoamisteknologia. Yksityiskohtaisemmilla tasoilla piirretään enemmän jätettä ja pöly- ja savuhiukkasia, ja tehosteen eri komponentit pysyvät näkyvissä kauemmin ennen kuin ne häipyvät pois.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Règle la qualité visuelle de la destruction des bâtiments, des murs et des objets gérés par la technologie de destruction de NVIDIA GameWorks. Plus le niveau de détail est élevé, plus le nombre de débris affiché est gr*******, au même titre que les particules de poussière et de fumée. Les divers composants de l'effet persistent plus longtemps avant de disparaître progressivement.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מכווננת את האיכות החזותית של הריסת בניינים, קירות ואובייקטים באמצעות טכנולוגיית ההריסה של NVIDIA GameWorks. ברמות פירוט גבוהות יותר, מתבצעת הפקה של יותר הריסות וחלקיקי אבק ועשן, והרכיבים השונים של האפקט נשארים זמן רב יותר על המסך לפני שהם מתפוגגים.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Az NVIDIA GameWorks Rombolás technológiájával beállítja az épületek, falak és objektumok lerombolásának minőségét. Magasabb részletességek esetén több törmelék, füst és porrészecske látható, és az effektus különböző összetevői tovább láthatók a képernyőn, mielőtt elhalványulnának.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola la qualità visiva della distruzione di edifici, muri e oggetti, grazie alla tecnologia di distruzione NVIDIA GameWorks. Ai livelli di dettaglio superiori, vengono renderizzate più macerie e particelle di polvere e fumo, e i vari componenti dell'effetto rimangono visibili più a lungo sullo schermo prima di dissolversi.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">NVIDIA GameWorks の破壊テクノロジーを使用し破壊された建物、壁、オブジェクトのビジュアル クオリティを調整します。ディーテール レベルが高くなるにつれて、より多くの破片がレンダリングされ、より多くの埃や煙などのパーティクルもレンダリングされます。さらに様々なエフェクトのコンポーネントが消えるまでより長く画面上に残ります。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">NVIDIA GameWorks의 파괴 기술이 적용된 건물, 벽 및 개체 파괴의 시각 품질을 조정합니다. 디테일 수준이 높으면 더 많은 파편, 먼지 및 안개 입자가 렌더링되고 다양한 효과 구성요소가 사라지기 전에 화면에 더 오래 유지됩니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Past de visuele kwaliteit van de vernietiging van gebouwen, muren en objecten aan dankzij de vernietigingstechnologie van NVIDIA GameWorks. Bij hogere detailniveaus wordt meer puin gerenderd, evenals meer stof- en rookpartikels en de verschillende onderdelen van het effect blijven langer op het scherm zichtbaar voordat deze verdwijnen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Justerer den visuelle kvaliteten av bygning, vegg og objektødeleggelse drevet av NVIDIA GameWorks sin  ødeleggelsesteknologi. På høyere detaljnivåer blir mer rusk gjengitt, og også mer støv og røykpartikler, og de ulike effektkomponentene vedvarer lenger på skjermen før de tones ut.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dostosowuje jakość wyglądu budynków, ścian i niszczenia obiektów, stworzoną na bazie technologii destrukcji NVIDIA GameWorks. Na wyższych poziomach szczegółowości renderowana jest większa ilość gruzu, a także pyłu i cząsteczek dymu, a różne komponenty efektu utrzymują się dłużej na ekranie, zanim znikną.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Ajusta a qualidade visual da destruição de edifícios, paredes e objectos com recurso à tecnologia de destruição NVIDIA GameWorks. Em níveis de maior detalhe são apresentados mais detritos, bem como mais partículas de poeira e de fumo e os vários componentes do efeito permanecem mais tempo no ecrã antes de desvanecer.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ajusta a qualidade visual da destruição de edifícios, paredes e objetos acionada pela tecnologia de destruição do GameWorks da NVIDIA. Em níveis de detalhe mais altos, maior quantidade de detrito é renderizada, devido a que há mais partículas de poeira e fumaça, e os vários componentes do efeito persistem durante mais tempo na tela antes de ser atenuados.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует визуальное качество разрушения зданий стен и объектов на базе технологии NVIDIA GameWorks Destruction. Чем выше уровень детализации, тем больше отображается мелкого мусора, а также частиц пыли и дыма, а различные составляющие эффекта остаются на экране дольше.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Upravuje vizuálnu kvalitu ničenia budov, stien a objektov, používa technológiu ničenia NVIDIA GameWorks. Pri vyššej úrovni detailov sa vykresľuje viac trosiek, prachu a častíc dymu, pričom rôzne súčasti efektu zostávajú na obrazovke dlhšie, kým zmiznú.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Prilagodi vidno kakovost uničenja zgradb, sten in predmetov, ki jih poganja NVIDIA GameWorks tehnologija za uničenje. Pri višjih ravneh podrobnosti je prikazane več nesnage, kot tudi več prahu in delcev dima; in različne komponente tega učinka ostanejo na zaslonu dlje, preden pojenjajo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Justerar den visuella kvaliteten för förstörelse av byggnader, väggar och föremål som drivs av NVIDIA GameWorks förstörelseteknik. Vid högre inställningar renderas mer spillror, damm och rökpartiklar, och de olika effektkomponenterna varar längre på skärmen innan de bleknar bort.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับคุณภาพการมองเห็นของการทำลายอาคาร ผนัง และวัตถุที่สร้างสรรค์มาจากเทคโนโลยีการทำลายของ NVIDIA GameWorks หากแสดงภาพฝุ่นผงมากขึ้นในระดับรายละเอียดสูงขึ้น จะได้อนุภาคฝุ่นผงและควันมากขึ้น และองค์ประกอบหลากหลายของเอฟเฟกต์ที่ยังคงปรากฎอยู่เป็นเวลานานขึ้นบนหน้าจอก่อนที่ค่อยๆ จางลง</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">NVIDIA GameWorks Tahribat teknolojisine dayalı bina, duvar ve nesne tahribatlarındaki görsel kaliteyi ayarlar. Daha yüksek düzeylerde daha fazla atık, ayrıca daha fazla toz ve duman parçacığı görüntülenir ve efektin çeşitli bileşenleri yavaşça yok olmadan önce ekr*******a daha uzun süre kalır.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">调整 NVIDIA GameWorks 的破坏技术支持的建筑物、墙壁和物体破坏的视觉质量。细节级别越高，渲染的碎片以及灰尘和烟雾颗粒数量越多，而且效果的各个组件淡出前在屏幕上存在的时间也越长。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">調整由 NVIDIA GameWorks 的「破壞」技術所驅動的建築物、牆壁和物體破壞的視覺品質。精細度較高時，會呈現更多碎片，也會有更多的灰塵和煙霧顆粒，而且效果的各種元件會在淡出之前在螢幕上持續得更久。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Reflection Quality">
    <Image>war_thunder_011.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="935" Top="596" />
    <TextRect Height="129" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adjusts the quality of reflections seen on glass ******* other reflective surfaces, with the exception of water, which is adjusted by the "Water Reflections Quality" setting.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">ضبط جودة الانعكاسات التي تظهر على الزجاج والأسطح العاكسة الأخرى - باستثناء المياه التي يتم تعديلها من خلال إعداد "جودة تأملات المياه".</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Nastavuje kvalitu odrazů na skle a jiných reflektivních površích - kromě vody, jež jsou řízeny nastavením „kvality odrazů ve vodě“.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Justerer kvaliteten på refleksioner, som ses på glas og *******re reflekterende overflader – med undtagelsen af v*******, der justeres af indstillingen "V*******refleksioner".</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt die Qualität von Reflexionen auf Glas und *******eren reflektierenden Flächen – ausgenommen Wasser, das über die Einstellung „Qualität Wasserreflexionen” gesteuert wird.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσαρμόζει την ποιότητα των αντανακλάσεων που φαίνονται στο γυαλί και σε άλλες αντανακλαστικές επιφάνειες - με την εξαίρεση του νερού, το οποίο προσαρμόζεται από τη ρύθμιση «Ποιότητα αντανακλάσεων νερού».</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adjusts the quality of reflections seen on glass ******* other reflective surfaces, with the exception of water, which is adjusted by the "Water Reflections Quality" setting.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Ajusta la calidad de los reflejos en los cristales y otras superficies reflectantes, excepto el agua, controlada por el ajuste "Calidad de reflejos del agua".</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Ajusta la calidad de los reflejos que se ven en el vidrio y otras superficies reflectantes, con la excepción del agua, que se ajusta mediante la configuración "Calidad de reflejos del agua".</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Säätää lasin ja muiden heijastavien pintojen heijastumien laatua, lukuun ottamatta vettä, jota säädetään Veden heijastumien laatu -asetuksella.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Règle la qualité des reflets affichés sur le verre et les autres surfaces réfléchissantes, à l'exception de l'eau, qui dépend du paramètre « Qualité des réflexions de l’eau ».</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מכווננת את האיכות של השתקפויות המופיעות על זכוכית ומשטחים משקפים אחרים - מלבד מים, שאיכותם מכווננת באמצעות ההגדרה 'איכות השתקפויות במים'.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Beállítja az üvegen és más tükröző felületeken a tükröződések minőségét, kivéve a víz esetén, amely a „Víztükröződés minősége” beállítással szabályozható.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola la qualità dei riflessi visualizzati sul vetro e su altre superfici riflettenti, a eccezione dell'acqua, che viene regolata tramite l'impostazione "Qualità riflessi acqua".</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">窓やその他の反射するサーフェイスに映る反射のクオリティを調整します。ただし、水は「水面反射のクオリティ」設定で調整されるため除かれます。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">"물 반사 품질" 설정으로 조절되는 물을 제외하고 유리 및 기타 반사 표면에 보이는 반사 품질을 조절합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Past de kwaliteit van reflecties op glas en *******ere reflecterende oppervlakken aan, behalve water. Dit wordt aangepast met de instelling 'Kwaliteit waterreflecties'.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Justerer kvaliteten på refleksjonene som blir sett på glass og *******re reflekterende overflater - med unntak av vann, som justeres av "Kvalitet på gjenspeiling i vann"-innstillingen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dostosowuje jakość odbić widocznych na szkle i innych powierzchniach odbijających — wyjątkiem jest woda, której właściwości są regulowane ustawieniem „Jakość odbić w wodzie”.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Ajusta a qualidade dos reflexos em vidro e noutras superfícies reflectoras, excepto a água, uma vez que é ajustada pela definição "Qualidade dos reflexos da água".</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ajusta a qualidade de reflexos vistos no vidro e em outras superfícies refletivas, com a exceção da água, que é ajustada pela configuração "Qualidade dos reflexos da água".</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует качество отражений на стекле и других отражающих поверхностях, за исключением отражений на воде, которые регулируются параметром «Качество отражений на воде».</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Upravuje kvalitu odrazov zobrazovaných na skle a iných reflexných povrchoch s výnimkou vody, ktorá sa upravuje nastavením Kvalita odrazov vo vode.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Prilagodi kakovost odsevom, ki so vidni na steklu in drugih odsevnih površinah - z izjemo vode, ki se jo prilagodi z nastavitvijo "Kakovost vodnih odsevov".</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Justerar kvaliteten för speglingar i glas och *******ra spegl*******e ytor - med undantag för vatten, som styrs av inställningen "Vattenspeglingskvalitet".</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับคุณภาพการสะท้อนแสงที่มองเห็นบนต้นหญ้าและพื้นผิวสะท้อนแสงอื่นๆ โดยมีข้อยกเว้นของน้ำ ซึ่งถูกปรับโดยการตั้งค่า "คุณภาพการสะท้อนของน้ำ"</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">"Sudaki Yansımaların Kalitesi" ayarıyla ayarlanan su haricinde cam ve diğer bütün yansıtıcı yüzeylerdeki yansımaların kalitesini ayarlar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">调整玻璃和其他反射表面（可通过“水反射质量”设置调整的水除外）上可见的反射的质量。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">調整玻璃和其他反射性表面（除了以「水面倒影品質」設定進行調整的水之外）上所見的反射品質。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Reflex">
    <Image>war_thunder_007.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="994" Top="687" />
    <TextRect Height="97" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">NVIDIA Reflex is a software technology that reduces game latency in competitive games.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">NVIDIA Reflex هي تقنية برمجية تقلل من زمن انتقال الألعاب في الألعاب التنافسية.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">NVIDIA Reflex je softwarová technologie, která snižuje latenci systému v kompetitivních hrách.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">NVIDIA Reflex er en softwareteknologi, der reducerer spillelatenstid i konkurrencebetonede spil.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">NVIDIA Reflex ist eine Software, die Latenzzeiten bei anspruchsvollen Spielen verringert.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Το NVIDIA Reflex είναι μια τεχνολογία λογισμικού που μειώνει την καθυστέρηση παιχνιδιού σε ανταγωνιστικά παιχνίδια.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">NVIDIA Reflex is a software technology that reduces game latency in competitive games.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">NVIDIA Reflex es una tecnología de software que reduce la latencia del juego en juegos competitivos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">NVIDIA Reflex es una tecnología de software que reduce la latencia del juego en juegos competitivos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">NVIDIA Reflex on ohjelmistoteknologia, joka vähentää pelien viivettä kilpailupeleissä.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">NVIDIA Reflex est une technologie logicielle qui réduit la latence du jeu dans les jeux compétitifs.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">Reflex ‏NVIDIA היא טכנולוגיית תוכנה שמפחיתה זמן המתנה במשחקים תחרותיים.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Az NVIDIA Reflex egy olyan szoftvertechnológia, amely csökkenti a játék késleltetését a versenyjátékokban.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">NVIDIA Reflex è una tecnologia software che riduce la latenza di gioco nei giochi competitivi.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">NVIDIA Reflex は、競争の激しいゲームでゲーム遅延を軽減するソフトウェア テクノロジーです。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">NVIDIA Reflex는 경쟁 게임에서 게임 지연 시간을 줄여주는 소프트웨어 기술입니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">NVIDIA Reflex is een softwaretechnologie die de vertraging in competitieve games verlaagt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">NVIDIA Reflex er en programvareteknologi som reduserer spill-latens i konkurrerende spill.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">NVIDIA Reflex to technologia oprogramowania zmniejszająca opóźnienia w grach turniejowych.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">NVIDIA Reflex é uma tecnologia de software que reduz a latência do jogo em jogos competitivos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">NVIDIA Reflex é uma tecnologia de software que reduz a latência no jogo em jogos competitivos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">NVIDIA Reflex — это программная технология, которая снижает время задержки в соревновательных играх.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">NVIDIA Reflex je softvérová technológia, ktorá znižuje oneskorenie hry v súťažných hrách.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">NVIDIA Reflex je tehnologija programske opreme, ki zmanjša zakasnitev igre pri konkurenčnih igrah.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">NVIDIA Reflex är en programvaruteknik som minskar spellatens i tävlingsspel.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">NVIDIA Reflex เป็นเทคโนโลยีซอฟต์แวร์ที่ลดเวลาแฝงของเกมในเกมการแข่งขัน</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">NVIDIA Reflex, rekabetçi oyunlarda oyun gecikme oranını azaltan bir yazılım teknolojisidir.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">NVIDIA Reflex 是一种软件技术，可减少竞争游戏中的游戏延迟。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">NVIDIA Reflex 是一種軟體技術，可以減少競爭遊戲中的遊戲延遲。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Render Resolution">
    <Image>war_thunder_001.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1096" Top="647" />
    <TextRect Height="177" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Downscaling that reduces the internal rendering resolution to increase performance, significantly degrading image quality. Selecting "100%" disables downscaling ******* renders the game at the level determined by the in-game Resolution setting.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">تصغير يقلل من دقة العرض الداخلي لرفع مستوى الأداء، وتقليل جودة الصورة بشكل كبير. اختيار "100%" يعطل تقليص النطاقات ويجعل اللعبة على مستوى يحدده وضع الدقة في اللعبة.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Snížení rozlišení, které snižuje interní rozlišení vykreslení vede ke zvýšení výkonu a k výrazně snížené kvalitě obrazu. Volba „100%“ zakazuje snížení rozlišení a renderuje hru na úrovni stanovené v nastavení rozlišení samotné hry.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Nedskalering, som reducerer den interne gengivelsesopløsning for at forøge ydeevne, hvilket forringer billedkvaliteten betydeligt. Valg af "100%" deaktiverer nedskalering og gengiver spillet ved det niveau, som fastsættes af opløsningsindstillingen i spillet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Herunterskalieren, das die interne Darstellungsauflösung verringert, um die Leistung zu verbessern. Verschlechtert deutlich die Bildqualität. Die Auswahl von „100 %” deaktiviert das Herunterskalieren und stellt das Spiel entsprechend der spielinternen Auflösungseinstellung dar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Υποβάθμιση που μειώνει την εσωτερική ανάλυση φωτοαπόδοσης για να αυξηθεί η απόδοση, μειώνοντας σημαντικά την ποιότητα εικόνας. Αν επιλέξετε «100%» απενεργοποιείται η υποβάθμιση και φωτοαποδίδεται το παιχνίδι σε επίπεδο που καθορίζεται από τη ρύθμιση ανάλυσης εντός του παιχνιδιού.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Downscaling that reduces the internal rendering resolution to increase performance, significantly degrading image quality. Selecting "100%" disables downscaling ******* renders the game at the level determined by the in-game Resolution setting.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Reducción de escala que disminuye la resolución de renderizado interno para aumentar el rendimiento, degrad*******o significativamente la calidad de la imagen. Al seleccionar "100%" se desactiva la reducción de escala y se renderiza el juego al nivel determinado por el ajuste Resolución dentro del juego.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Reducción de escala que disminuye la resolución interna de renderizado para aumentar el rendimiento, lo que degrada significativamente la calidad de la imagen. Al seleccionar "100 %" se desactiva la reducción de escala y el juego se renderiza al nivel determinado por la configuración de resolución en juego.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Pienentäminen alentaa sisäistä piirtotarkkuutta suorituskyvyn lisäämiseksi kuvanlaadun kustannuksella. Kun valitset "100 %", pienentäminen poistetaan käytöstä ja peli piirretään pelin tarkkuusasetuksissa määritetyllä tasolla.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Une dégradation qui réduit la résolution de rendu interne pour améliorer les performances au prix de la qualité d'image. « 100 % » désactive la dégradation et affiche le jeu au niveau défini dans le paramètre de résolution en jeu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">הקטנה שלה מצמצמת את רזולוציית ההפקה הפנימית כדי להגביר את הביצועים, וגורמת לירידה משמעותית באיכות התמונה. בחירה ב'100%' משביתה את ההקטנה ומפיקה את המשחק ברמה שנקבעת על-ידי הגדרת הרזולוציה הפנימית של המשחק.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Leskálázás, amely a teljesítmény növelésének érdekében csökkenti a belső megjelenítési felbontást, jelentősen rontva a képminőséget. A „100%” beállítás letiltja a leskálázást, és a játék felbontási beállításának megfelelő felbontásban jeleníti meg a játékot.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Downscaling che riduce la risoluzione di rendering interna per aumentare le prestazioni, deterior*******o in modo significativo la qualità dell'immagine. Selezion*******o "100%" si disabilita il downscaling e si esegue il rendering del gioco al livello stabilito dall'impostazione di risoluzione del gioco.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">パフォーマンスを向上させるために内部レンダリング解像度を低くするダウンスケールを行い、画質を大幅に下げます。「100%」を選択することでダウンスケールを無効にし、ゲーム解像度設定によって決定されるレベルでゲームをレンダリングします。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">성능 향상을 위해 다운스케일하여 내부 렌더링 해상도를 줄이면 이미지 품질이 크게 저하됩니다. "100%"를 선택하면 다운스케일이 비활성화되고 게임 내의 해상도 설정에 따라 결정된 수준으로 게임이 렌더링됩니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Verlaging waarmee de interne renderingresolutie wordt beperkt voor betere prestaties, waardoor de beeldkwaliteit aanzienlijk afneemt. Wanneer "100%" wordt geselecteerd, wordt de verlaging uitgeschakeld en de game gerenderd op het door de Resolutie-instellingen in de game bepaalde niveau.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Nedskalering som reduserer den interne, gjengitte oppløsningen for å øke ytelsen, noe som betydelig reduserer bildekvaliteten. Ved å velge "100 %" deaktiveres nedskalering, og spillet gjengis på nivået som bestemmes av oppløsningen satt i spillet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Zmniejszenie rozdzielczości, które redukuje wewnętrzną rozdzielczość renderowania w celu zwiększenia wydajności. Znacznie obniża jakość obrazu. Wybranie opcji „100%” wyłącza zmniejszanie rozdzielczości i renderuje grę na poziomie określonym przez ustawienie rozdzielczości w grze.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Redução de tamanho que reduz a resolução de apresentação interna para aumentar o desempenho, degrad*******o significativamente a qualidade de imagem. A selecção de "100%" desactiva a redução de tamanho e apresenta o jogo no nível determinado pela definição Resolução.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Redução de escala que diminui a resolução de renderização interna para aumentar o desempenho, degrad*******o de forma significativa a qualidade da imagem. Selecionar a opção "100%" desativa a redução de escala e executa o jogo ao nível determinado pela configuração de Resolução durante o jogo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Уменьшение внутреннего разрешения для повышения производительности за счет значительного ухудшения качества картинки. Выберите значение «100%», чтобы отключить уменьшение разрешения и отображать игру в разрешении, определяемом игровой настройкой «Разрешение».</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Zníženie interného rozlíšenia vykresľovania s cieľom zvýšiť výkon. Výrazne znižuje kvalitu obrazu. Pri výbere hodnoty 100% sa zníženie interného rozlíšenia vykresľovania deaktivuje a hra sa bude vykresľovať na úrovni určenej nastavením rozlíšenia v hre.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Znižanje tega zmanjša interno ločljivost prikaza, da izboljša zmogljivost, pri čemer se kakovost slike občutno poslabša. Izbor "100 %" onemogoči znižanje in  prikaže igro na ravni, ki jo je določila nastavitev ločljivosti v igri.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Nedskalning som minskar upplösningen i den interna renderingen, vilket ökar prest*******a men med stor minskning av bildkvalitet. Valet "100 %" inaktiverar nedskalning och renderar spelet på den nivå som anges i inställningen Upplösning i spelet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">การลดขนาดที่ทำให้ความละเอียดภายในลดลงเพื่อเพิ่มสมรรถภาพ โดยการทำให้คุณภาพของภาพลดลงมาก การเลือก "100 %" จะปิดใช้งานการลดขนาดและสร้างภาพเกมในระดับที่กำหนดโดยการตั้งค่าความละเอียดในเกม</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Görüntü kalitesinden büyük ölçüde ödün vererek görüntü oluşturma iç çözünürlüğünü azaltan çözünürlük indirgeme. "%100" seçildiğinde çözünürlük indirgeme devre dışı kalır ve oyunun görüntüsü, oyun içindeki çözünürlük ayarıyla belirlenen düzeyde oluşturulur.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">降低内部渲染分辨率以提高性能，显著降低图像质量的缩小。选择“100%”可禁用缩小并从游戏内分辨率设置确定的级别渲染游戏。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">降低內部的呈現解析度以提高效能，顯著地降低影像品質的縮減比例。選取「100%」可以停用縮減比例，並以遊戲中解析度設定所決定的等級來呈現遊戲。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="RTX: DLSS">
    <Image>war_thunder_003.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1053" Top="643" />
    <TextRect Height="257" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">The GeForce RTX platform brings together real-time ray tracing, artificial intelligence, ******* programmable shading for a whole new way to experience games. NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) produces a much higher quality output than Temporal Anti-aliasing (TAA) from a given set of input samples, which significantly improves the overall performance.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">تجمع منصة GeForce RTX بين تعقب الأشعة في الوقت الفعلي والذكاء الاصطناعي والتظليل القابل للبرمجة لطريقة جديدة تمامًا لتجربة الألعاب. تنتج العينات الفائقة للتعلم العميق (DLSS) من NVIDIA مخرجات بجودة أعلى بكثير عن منع الترادف المؤقت (TAA) من مجموعة معينة من عينات المدخلات، مما يحسن الأداء العام بشكل كبير.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Platforma GeForce RTX spojuje sledování paprsku v reálném čase, umělou inteligenci a programovatelné stínování pro zcela nový zážitek z hraní her. NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) produkuje mnohem vyšší kvalitu výstupu než dočasné vyhlazování hran (TAA), a to díky dané sadě vstupních vzorků, která výrazně zlepšuje celkový výkon.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">GeForce RTX-platformen kombinerer ray tracing i realtid, kunstig intelligens og programmerbar skyggelægning, så du kan opleve spil på en helt ny måde. NVIDIA DLSS (Deep Learning Super-Sampling) producerer en meget højere kvalitet output end TAA (Temporal Anti-aliasing) fra et givent sæt input-prøver, hvilket forbedrer den generelle ydeevne betydeligt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Die GeForce RTX Plattform bündelt Raytracing in Echtzeit, künstliche Intelligenz und programmierbares Shading für ein völlig neues Spielerlebnis. NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) erzeugt aus einem bestimmten Satz von Eingangsmustern eine wesentlich höhere Ausgabequalität als Temporal Anti-Aliasing (TAA), was die Gesamtleistung beträchtlich steigert.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Η πλατφόρμα GeForce RTX συνδυάζει ιχνηλάτηση ακτίνων πραγματικού χρόνου, τεχνητή νοημοσύνη και προγραμματιζόμενη σκίαση για έναν ολοκαίνουριο τρόπο να βιώνετε τα παιχνίδια. Η υπερδειγματοληψία βαθιάς εκμάθησης NVIDIA (DLSS) παράγει έξοδο πολύ υψηλότερης ποιότητας από ό,τι η χρονική εξομάλυνση ορίων (TAA) από ένα δεδομένο σύνολο δειγμάτων εισόδου, γεγονός που βελτιώνει σημαντικά τη συνολική απόδοση.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">The GeForce RTX platform brings together real-time ray tracing, artificial intelligence, ******* programmable shading for a whole new way to experience games. NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) produces a much higher quality output than Temporal Anti-aliasing (TAA) from a given set of input samples, which significantly improves the overall performance.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">La plataforma GeForce RTX reúne el trazado de rayos en tiempo real, la inteligencia artificial y el sombreado programable para cambiar totalmente la forma de experimentar los juegos. El DLSS (Deep Learning Super-Sampling, supermuestreo de aprendizaje profundo) de NVIDIA produce una imagen de mucha mayor calidad que el TAA (Temporal Antialiasing, antialiasing temporal) a partir de un conjunto dado de muestras de entrada, lo que mejora significativamente el rendimiento general.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">La plataforma GeForce RTX junta el trazado de rayos en tiempo real, la inteligencia artificial y el sombreado programable para brindar una nueva manera de experimentar los juegos. El DLSS (supermuestreo de aprendizaje profundo) de NVIDIA produce una salida de una calidad mucho más elevada que el suavizado de líneas temporal (TAA) desde un conjunto determinado de muestras de salida, lo que mejora considerablemente el rendimiento general.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">GeForce RTX -alusta tuo yhteen reaaliaikaisen säteenseurannan, tekoälyn ja ohjelmoitavan varjostuksen, ja tuloksena on aivan uusi tapa kokea pelejä. NVIDIA Deep Learning Supersampling (DLSS) tuottaa annetuista syöttönäytteistä paljon laadukkaamman tuloksen kuin ajallinen reunanpehmennys (TAA), mikä parantaa yleistä suorituskykyä.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">La plate-forme GeForce RTX réunit le ray-tracing en temps réel, l'intelligence artificielle et l'ombrage programmable pour inaugurer une nouvelle ère du jeu vidéo. Le super-échantillonnage via deep learning (DLSS) NVIDIA produit une image de qualité beaucoup plus élevée que l'anticrénelage temporel (TAA) à partir d'un ensemble donné d'échantillons d'entrée, ce qui améliore significativement les performances globales.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">פלטפורמת GeForce RTX‏ משלבת מעקב אחר קרניים בזמן אמת, אינטליגנציה מלאכותית והצללה ניתנת לתכנות ובכך יוצרת דרך חדשה לגמרי לחוות משחקים. מערכת "למידה עמוקה באמצעות דגימת על" (DLSS) של NVIDIA מעניקה תוצאות איכותיות הרבה יותר מאשר החלקת שינון זמנית (TAA) על קבוצה נתונה של דגימות קלט דבר שמשפר את הביצועים באופן כללי.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">A GeForce RTX platform a valós idejű sugárkövetést, a mesterséges intelligenciát és a programozható árnyékolást ötvözve egy teljesen új játékélményt hoz létre. Az NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) egy adott bemeneti mintakészletből sokkal jobb minőségű kimenetet hoz létre, mint az időbeli élsimítás (TAA), jelentősen növelve az általános teljesítményt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">La piattaforma GeForce RTX mette insieme ray tracing in tempo reale, intelligenza artificiale e ombreggiatura programmabile per offrire un’esperienza di gioco completamente nuova. Il Deep Learning Super-Sampling di NVIDIA (DLSS) offre risultati di qualità molto più alta rispetto all’antialias temporale (TAA) a partire da un determinato numero di campioni, miglior*******o significativamente le prestazioni globali.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">GeForce RTX プラットフォームでは、リアルタイムのレイ トレーシング、人工知能、プログラム可能なシェーディングを組み合わせ、まったく新しいゲーム体験方法を提供します。NVIDIA ディープ ラーニング スーパーサンプリング (DLSS) は、与えられた入力サンプルから時間的アンチエリアシング (TAA) よりも高いクオリティの出力を生成し、全般的なパフォーマンスを大幅に向上させます。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">GeForce RTX 플랫폼은 실시간 레이 트레이싱, 인공 지능 및 프로그래밍 가능한 음영을 결합하여 새로운 방식의 게임을 경험할 수 있도록 합니다. NVIDIA 딥러닝 슈퍼 샘플링(DLSS)은 일련의 입력 샘플에서 일시적 앤티엘리어싱(TAA)보다 더 높은 품질의 출력을 생산하며, 이는 전반적인 성능을 현저히 향상합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Het GeForce RTX-platform biedt een combinatie van real-time raytracing, kunstmatige intelligentie en programmeerbare schaduwen voor een compleet nieuwe game-ervaring. NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) produceert een veel hoogwaardigere uitvoer dan Temporal Anti-aliasing (TAA) via een bepaalde set invoersamples, waarmee de algehele prestaties aanzienlijk worden verbeterd.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">GeForce RTX-plattformen samler strålesporing i sanntid, kunstig intelligens og programmerbar skyggelegging for en helt ny spillopplevelse. NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) produserer et resultat av mye høyere kvalitet enn midlertidig kantutjevning (TAA) fra et gitt sett med inndataprøver, noe som forbedrer den generelle ytelsen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Platforma GeForce RTX łączy w czasie rzeczywistym śledzenie promieni, sztuczną inteligencję i programowalne cieniowanie, zapewniając nową jakość grania. NVIDIA DLSS (Deep Learning Super-Sampling) oferuje znacznie wyższą jakość wyjściową niż TAA (Temporal Anti-aliasing) na podstawie danego zestawu próbek wejściowych, co znacząco zwiększa ogólną wydajność.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">A plataforma GeForce RTX junta a trajectografia em tempo real, a inteligência artificial e a iluminação programável para uma nova experiência de jogo. A Superamostragem de Aprendizagem Profunda da NVIDIA (DLSS) produz uma saída de qualidade muito superior do que a opção antialiasing temporal (TAA) de um conjunto de amostras de entrada, o que melhora significativamente o desempenho geral.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">A plataforma GeForce RTX oferece ray tracing em tempo real, inteligência artificial e sombreamento programável para uma maneira totalmente nova de experimentar os jogos. O NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) produz uma saída de qualidade muito maior do que a TAA a partir de um determinado conjunto de amostras de entrada, o que melhora significativamente o desempenho geral.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Платформа GeForce RTX, в состав которой входят трассировка лучей в реальном времени, искусственный интеллект и программируемое затенение, полностью изменит ваше представление об играх. Технология NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) обеспечивает гораздо более качественный результат на основе заданного набора входной выборки, чем временное сглаживание (TAA), что значительно повышает общую производительность.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Platforma GeForce RTX spája sledovanie lúčov v reálnom čase, umelú inteligenciu a programovateľné tieňovanie, vďaka čomu poskytuje úplne nový herný zážitok. NVIDIA DLSS (Deep Learning Super-Sampling) vytvára zo zadaného súboru vstupných vzoriek oveľa kvalitnejší výstup než dočasné vyhladzovanie (TAA), čo výrazne zlepšuje celkový výkon.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">GeForce RTX platforma združi sledenje žarkom v realnem času, umetno inteligenco in programirljivo senčenje za popolnoma novo izkušnjo pri igrah. Z NVIDIA DLSS (Deep Learning Super-Sampling, super vzorčenje globokega učenja) se iz kompleta vzorcev proizvede rezultat precej višje kakovosti kot TAA, kar močno izboljša splošno zmogljivost.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">På GeForce RTX-plattformen får man såväl spårning av strålar i realtid och artificiell intelligens som programmerbar skuggning för ett helt nytt sätt att uppleva spel. NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) producerar mycket bättre kvalitet än Temporal Anti-aliasing (TAA), kantutjämning, från en given uppsättning ingångssamplingar, vilket avsevärt förbättrar den allmänna prest*******an.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">แพลตฟอร์ม GeForce RTX จะรวมการติดตามแสงแบบเรียลไทม์ ปัญญาประดิษฐ์ (AI) และการให้แสงเงาแบบสั่งการได้เข้าด้วยกันเพื่อสัมผัสประสบการณ์ใหม่ในการเล่นเกม NVIDIA Deep Learning Super-Sampling (DLSS) สร้างผลลัพธ์ที่มีคุณภาพสูงขึ้นมากเทียบกับการลดรอยหยักแบบชั่วคราว (TAA) จากตัวอย่างอินพุตที่มี ซึ่งช่วยปรับปรุงประสิทธิภาพในภาพรวมอย่างมาก</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">GeForce RTX platformu, gerçek zamanlı ışın izleme, yapay zekâ ve programlanabilir gölgelendirme özelliklerini birleştirerek, oyunun oynama keyfine yepyeni bir boyut katar. NVIDIA Derinlemesine Öğrenen Süper Örnekleme (DLSS), belirli bir giriş örnekleri kümesinden yararlanarak Zamansal Kenar Yumuşatma'dan (TAA) çok daha yüksek kalitede çıkış üretip genel performansı önemli ölçüde artırır.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">GeForce RTX 平台将实时光线追踪、人工智能和可编程着色结合在一起，为用户提供了全新的游戏体验方式。NVIDIA DLSS 可从给定的一组输入样本中产生比 TAA 高得多的输出质量，从而极大地提高整体性能。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">GeForce RTX 平台匯集即時光線追蹤、人工智慧和可程式設計網底，以全新的方式體驗遊戲。NVIDIA 深度學習超級取樣 (DLSS) 從一組特定的輸入樣本中產生遠遠超過時間消除鋸齒 (TAA) 的輸出品質，因而顯著地改善整體效能。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Shadow Quality">
    <Image>war_thunder_010.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1186" Top="790" />
    <TextRect Height="97" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Controls the fidelity of the game's shadows, adding extra detail as the setting is raised.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">التحكم في دقة ظلال اللعبة، مع إضافة تفاصيل إضافية عند رفع قيمة الإعداد.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Určuje věrnost stínů ve hře. S rostoucí hodnotou nastavení přidává další detaily.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Styrer nøjagtigheden på spillets skygger, idet ekstra detaljer tilføjes, efterhånden som indstillingen hæves.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Steuert die Detailgenauigkeit der Schatten im Spiel. Bei höheren Einstellungen werden zusätzliche Details hinzugefügt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Ελέγχει την πιστότητα των σκιών του παιχνιδιού, προσθέτοντας επιπλέον λεπτομέρειες καθώς αυξάνεται η ρύθμιση.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Controls the fidelity of the game's shadows, adding extra detail as the setting is raised.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Controla la fidelidad de las sombras del juego, añadiendo detalles adicionales a medida que se eleva el parámetro.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Controla la fidelidad de las sombras del juego, lo que proporciona mayor nivel de detalle ya que se aumenta la configuración.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ohjaa pelin varjojen todenmukaisuutta lisäten yksityiskohtia, kun asetus on korkeampi.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Ajuste la fidélité des ombres en jeu et ajoute des détails supplémentaires si le paramètre est élevé.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">הגדרה זו מפקחת על מידת הנאמנות למציאות של הצללים במשחק ומוסיפה פירוט נוסף כאשר ערך ההגדרה גבוה יותר.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Az érték növelésének hatására további részletek hozzáadásával szabályozza a játék árnyékainak valósághűségét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Controlla la fedeltà delle ombre del gioco, aggiungendo ulteriori dettagli con l'aumento dell'impostazione.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">ゲーム内のシャドウの忠実性を調整し、設定を上げてディテールを追加します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">설정을 높이면 정밀도를 증가시켜 게임 그림자 정확성을 조절합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de precisie van de schaduwen van de game, waardoor extra detail wordt toegevoegd als de instelling wordt verhoogd.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Styrer kvaliteten på spillets skygger og legger til ekstra detaljer i takt med at innstillingen heves.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Kontroluje dokładność cieni w grze, zwiększając szczegóły w miarę podwyższania wartości ustawienia.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Controla a fidelidade das sombras do jogo, adicion*******o detalhes extra à medida que a definição aumenta.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Controla a fidelidade das sombras do jogo, adicion*******o detalhes adicionais conforme a configuração é aumentada.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует четкость теней в игре, добавляя больше деталей по мере повышения значения.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Ovláda vernosť tieňov v hre a pri vyššom nastavení pridáva ďalšie detaily.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Nadzoruje zvestobo senc v igri, kar doda dodatne podrobnosti, ko se nastavitev zvišuje.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Styr återgivningen av spelets skuggor, vilket ger fler detaljer när inställningen ökas.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ควบคุมความสมจริงของเงาในเกม ซึ่งช่วยเพิ่มรายละเอียดเพิ่มเติมเมื่อการตั้งค่าเพิ่มสูงขึ้น</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Ayar artırıldıkça daha fazla ayrıntı ekleyerek, oyundaki gölgelerin görsel gerçekçiliğini kontrol eder.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">控制游戏中阴影的逼真度，设定值越高细节就越多。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">控制遊戲中的陰影的逼真度，隨著設定提高而增加額外的細節。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Shadows">
    <Image>war_thunder_003.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1217" Top="1005" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Enables the display of shadows in the game.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">تمكين عرض الظلال في اللعبة.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Aktivuje zobrazení stínů ve hře.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Aktiverer visningen af skygger i spillet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Aktiviert die Anzeige von Schatten im Spiel.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Ενεργοποιεί την προβολή σκιών στο παιχνίδι.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Enables the display of shadows in the game.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Permite la visualización de las sombras en el juego.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Permite mostrar sombras en el juego.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ottaa käyttöön pelin varjojen esityksen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Active l'affichage des ombres.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">הגדרה זו מאפשרת הצגה של צללים במשחק.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Bekapcsolja az árnyékok megjelenítését a játékban.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Abilita la visualizzazione delle ombre nel gioco.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">ゲーム内のシャドウの表示を有効にします。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">게임에서 그림자의 디스플레이를 활성화합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Schakelt de weergave van schaduwen in de game in.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Aktiverer visning av skygger i spillet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Włącza wyświetlanie cieni w grze.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Activa a apresentação de sombras no jogo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ativa a exibição de sombras no jogo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Включает отображение теней в игре.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Aktivuje zobrazovanie tieňov v hre.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Omogoči prikaz senc v igri.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Aktiverar visning av skuggor i spelet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">เปิดใช้งานการแสดงผลเงาในเกม</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Oyunda gölgelerin görüntülenmesine olanak verir.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">启用游戏中阴影的显示。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">允許在遊戲中顯示陰影。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Shadows on Effects">
    <Image>war_thunder_008.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1281" Top="381" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adds dynamic, real-time shadows to special effects like smoke.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">يضيف ظلالًا ديناميكية في الوقت الفعلي إلى تأثيرات خاصة مثل الدخان.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Přidává dynamické stíny ke speciálním efektům, jako je např. kouř, v reálném čase.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Tilføjer dynamiske skygger i realtid til specialeffekter, såsom røg.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Erweitert Spezialeffekte wie z. B. Rauch um dynamische Echtzeitschatten.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσθέτει δυναμικές σκιές πραγματικού χρόνου σε ειδικά εφέ όπως τον καπνό.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adds dynamic, real-time shadows to special effects like smoke.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Añade sombras dinámicas en tiempo real a efectos especiales como humo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Agrega sombras dinámicas y en tiempo real a los efectos especiales, como el humo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Lisää dynaamisia reaaliaikaisia varjoja erikoistehosteisiin, kuten savuun.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Ajoute des ombres dynamiques en temps réel aux effets spéciaux comme la fumée.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מוסיפה צללים דינמיים בזמן אמת לאפקטים מיוחדים כגון עשן.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Dinamikus, valós idejű árnyékokat ad a füsthöz és más speciális effektusokhoz.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Aggiunge ombre dinamiche in tempo reale a effetti speciali come il fumo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">煙などの特殊効果に動的なリアルタイムシャドウを追加します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">연기와 같은 특수 효과에 동적 실시간 그림자를 추가합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Voegt dynamische, realtime schaduwen toe aan speciale effecten zoals rook.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Legger til dynamiske, real-time skygger til spesielle effekter som røyk.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dodaje dynamiczne cienie w czasie rzeczywistym do efektów specjalnych, takich jak dym.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Adiciona sombras dinâmicas e em tempo real ao fumo dos efeitos especiais.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Adiciona sombras dinâmicas em tempo real a efeitos especiais como a fumaça.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Добавляет динамические тени в реальном времени к таким спецэффектам, как дым.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">V reálnom čase pridáva dynamické tiene k špeciálnym efektom, napríklad dymu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Doda dinamične sence posebnim učinkom, kot je dim v realnem času.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Lägger ibl******* till dynamiska skuggor i realtid till specialeffekter såsom rök.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">เพิ่มไดนามิก เงาแบบตามเวลาจริงไปจนถึงเอฟเฟกต์พิเศษ เช่น ควัน</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Duman gibi, gerçek zamanlı, dinamik gölgeler ekler.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">向特殊效果，如烟尘添加实时的动态阴影。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">對像煙之類的特殊效果增加動態、即時陰影。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Small Object Shadows">
    <Image>war_thunder_014.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1424" Top="574" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Allows small objects to cast shadows.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">يسمح الأجسام الصغيرة لنشر الظلال.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Umožňuje malým objektům vrhat stíny.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Gør det muligt for små objekter at kaste skygger.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Aktiviert das Merkmal, dass kleine Gegenstände Schatten werfen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Επιτρέπει σε μικρά αντικείμενα να ρίχνουν σκιές.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Allows small objects to cast shadows.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Permite que objetos pequeños proyecten sombras.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Activa objetos pequeños para proyectar sombras.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ottaa käyttöön pienten esineiden varjot.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Permet aux petits objets de projeter des ombres.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מאפשרת לעצמים קטנים להטיל צללים.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Lehetővé teszi, hogy a kis tárgyaknak is legyen árnyéka.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Consente a piccoli oggetti di proiettare ombre.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">小さいオブジェクトのシャドウの表示を有効にします。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">소형 개체에 그림자가 생기도록 허용합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Staat kleine voorwerpen toe schaduwen te maken.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Tillater små objekter å kaste skygge.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Umożliwia rzucanie cienia przez małe obiekty.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Permite que a apresentação de sombras dos objectos pequenos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Permite que objetos pequenos projetem sombras.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Позволяет небольшим объектам отбрасывать тени.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Umožňuje malým objektom vrhať tieň.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Omogoči majhnim predmetom, da mečejo sence.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Möjliggör skuggeffekter för små objekt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">อนุญาตให้ออบเจกต์ขนาดเล็กทำการทอดเงาได้</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Küçük nesnelerin gölgelerini etkinleştirir.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">允许使用小物体来投射阴影。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">讓小物體投射出陰影。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Soft Particles">
    <Image>war_thunder_011.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="174" Top="762" />
    <TextRect Height="97" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Increases the quality of particle effects, like explosions, smoke plumes ******* bullet impacts.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">زيادة جودة تأثيرات الجزيئات، مثل الانفجارات، ألسنة الدخان وتأثيرات الطلقات.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Zvyšuje kvalitu částicových efektů, jako jsou exploze, oblaka kouře a dopady kulek.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Forøger kvaliteten på partikeleffekter, såsom eksplosioner, røgskyer og kuglehuller.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Erhöht die Qualität von Partikeleffekten wie Explosionen, Rauchwolken und Kugeleinschlägen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Αυξάνει την ποιότητα των εφέ σωματιδίων, όπως εκρήξεις, στήλες καπνού και προσκρούσεις σφαιρών.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Increases the quality of particle effects, like explosions, smoke plumes ******* bullet impacts.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Aumenta la calidad de los efectos de partículas, como las columnas de humo y los impactos de bala.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Aumenta la calidad de los efectos de partículas, como las explosiones, las columnas de humo y los impactos de bala.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Lisää hiukkastehosteiden, kuten räjähdysten, savupatsaiden ja luodinreikien, laatua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Augmente la qualité des effets des particules, comme les explosions, les panaches de fumée et les impacts de balles.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מגבירה את איכות אפקטי חלקיקים כגון התפוצצויות, תמרות עשן ופגיעות קליעים.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Javítja a részecskeeffektusok (például robbanások, füstcsóvák és golyóbecsapódások) minőségét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Aumenta la qualità degli effetti particellari, come esplosioni, pennacchi di fumo e fori di proiettile.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">爆発、煙柱、弾痕などのパーティクル エフェクトの品質を向上させます。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">폭발, 연기 기둥 및 총알 임팩트와 같은 입자 효과의 품질을 향상시킵니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de kwaliteit van partikeleffecten, zoals explosies, rookpluimen en kogelinslagen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Justerer kvaliteten på partikkeleffekter, f.eks. eksplosjoner, røykskyer og kulemerker.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Zwiększa jakość efektów cząsteczkowych, takich jak eksplozje, kłęby dymu i ślady po kulach.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Aumenta a qualidade dos efeitos de partículas, como explosões, colunas de fumo e impactos de bala.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Aumenta a qualidade de efeitos de partículas, como explosões, nuvens de fumaça e impactos de balas.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Повышает качество эффектов с использованием частиц (например, взрывов, столбов дыма и следов от пуль).</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Zvyšuje kvalitu efektov častíc, napríklad výbuchov, oblakov dymu a dier po guľkách.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Poveča kakovost učinkov z delci, kot so eksplozije, oblaki dima in zadetki krogel.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Ökar kvaliteten på partikeleffekter, som explosioner, rökmoln och kulträffar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">เพิ่มคุณภาพของเอฟเฟกต์อนุภาค เช่น การระเบิด กลุ่มควัน และแรงอัดของกระสุน</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Patlamalar, duman kümeleri ve kurşun izleri gibi parçacık efektlerinin kalitesini artırır.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">提高颗粒效果（如爆炸、烟缕和子弹撞击）的质量。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">提高如爆炸、煙柱和子彈衝擊等顆粒效果的品質。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="SSAA">
    <Image>war_thunder_003.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="912" Top="689" />
    <TextRect Height="225" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Super Sampling Anti-Aliasing, is a highly dem*******ing anti-aliasing technique similar to NVIDIA Dynamic Super Resolution, in that it renders the game at a higher resolution before shrinking the result back down to the native Screen Resolution, improving image quality ******* almost entirely eliminating aliasing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">منع الترادف متعدد العينات، عبارة عن تقنية منع الترادف بشكل عال مثل تقنية حل فائق ديناميكي لـ NVIDIA، التي تعرض اللعبة على دقة أعلى قبل انكماش النتيجة لدرجة أقل إلى دقة النافذة الأصلية، مما يؤدي إلى تحسين جودة الصورة وإزالة الترادف تماما.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Super Sampling Anti-Aliasing je velmi náročná technika vyhlazování hran podobná technologii NVIDIA Dynamic Super Resolution, která renderuje hru ve vyšším rozlišení před konverzí výsledku zpět do nativního rozlišení obrazovky, což vede ke zlepšení kvality obrazu a téměř zcela odstraňuje zubaté okraje.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">SSAA (Super Sampling Anti-Aliasing) er en højtkrævende udjævningsteknik, der ligner NVIDIA Dynamic Super Resolution, på den måde at den gengiver spillet ved en højere opløsning, før det skalerer resultatet tilbage ned til den producentspecifikke skærmopløsning, hvilket forbedrer billedkvaliteten og næsten fuldstændig eliminerer aliasing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Supersampling-Antialiasing ist eine hochgradig leistungsintensive Antialiasing-Technik, die NVIDIAs Dynamic Super Resolution-Technologie ähnelt. Dabei wird das Spiel mit einer höheren Auflösung gerendert, bevor das Ergebnis auf die native Bildschirmauflösung heruntergerechnet wird, was die Bildqualität verbessert und Verpixelungen fast vollständig beseitigt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Η εξομάλυνση ορίων υπερδειγματοληψίας είναι μια υψηλά απαιτητική τεχνική εξομάλυνσης ορίων παρόμοια με την δυναμική υπερανάλυση NVIDIA, επειδή φωτοαποδίδει το παιχνίδι σε υψηλότερη ανάλυση πριν συρρικνώσει το αποτέλεσμα ξανά στην εγγενή ανάλυση οθόνης, βελτιώνοντας την ποιότητα εικόνας και εξαλείφοντας σχεδόν εντελώς την εξομάλυνση ορίων.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Super Sampling Anti-Aliasing, is a highly dem*******ing anti-aliasing technique similar to NVIDIA Dynamic Super Resolution, in that it renders the game at a higher resolution before shrinking the result back down to the native Screen Resolution, improving image quality ******* almost entirely eliminating aliasing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">EL antialiasing de supermuestreo (SSAAA) es una técnica antialiasing muy exigente similar a la tecnología Dynamic Super Resolution de NVIDIA, que renderiza el juego a alta resolución antes de reducir de nuevo el resultado a la resolución nativa de pantalla, lo que mejora la calidad de la imagen y prácticamente elimina el aliasing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">El SSAA es una técnica de suavizado de líneas altamente exigente similar a la superresolución dinámica de NVIDIA, porque renderiza el juego a una resolución más alta antes de volver a reducir el resultado a la resolución de pantalla nativa, lo que mejora la calidad de imagen y elimina casi totalmente las líneas.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Super Sampling Anti-Aliasing (Supernäytteenotto-reunanpehmennys) on erittäin vaativa reunanpehmennysmenetelmä, joka on samantapainen kuin NVIDIAn Dynamic Super Resolution, joka tekee pelistä entistä tarkemman ennen kuin se kutistaa tuloksen takaisin alkuperäiseen näyttötarkkuuteen parantaen kuvan laatua suorituskyvyn kustannuksella.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">L'anti-crénelage par super-échantillonnage SSAA est une technique d'anti-crénelage similaire à la technologie DSR de NVIDIA, en ceci qu'elle calcule le jeu à une résolution supérieure avant de réduire le résultat à la résolution native d'affichage, ce qui a pour effet d'améliorer la qualité de l'image et d'éliminer presque entièrement le crénelage.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">החלקת שינון באמצעות סופר-סמפלינג, היא טכנולוגיית החלקת שינון תובענית ביותר, הדומה ל'רזולוציית על דינמית' של NVIDIA, בכך שהיא מעבדת את המשחק ברזולוציה גבוהה יותר ואז מכווצת את התוצאה בחזרה לרזולוציית המסך המקורית, תוך שיפור איכות התמונה והעלמת הקצוות המשוננים כמעט לחלוטין.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">A szuper-mintavételes élsimítás egy nagy teljesítményigényű élsimítási technika, amely annyiban hasonlít az NVIDIA dinamikus szuperfelbontás technológiájához, hogy a játék képeit magasabb felbontáson hozza létre, majd ezeket összezsugorítja a natív ablakfelbontásra.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">L’antialias di supercampionamento è una tecnica di antialias estremamente precisa simile a NVIDIA Dynamic Super Resolution, in quanto esegue il rendering del gioco a una risoluzione superiore prima di tornare alla risoluzione nativa dello schermo, miglior*******o la qualità delle immagini ed elimin*******o quasi completamente l'alias.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">スーパー サンプリング アンチエイリアシングは、NVIDIA ダイナミックスーパー解像度に似た、大量のリソースを使用するアンチエイリアシング技術です。ネイティブの画面解像度へと縮小し戻す前に、より高い解像度でゲームをレンダリングして、画質を向上させ、ほぼ完全にエイリアシングを排除します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">슈퍼 샘플링 앤티엘리어싱은 NVIDIA Dynamic Super Resolution과 유사한 고난이도 앤티엘리어싱 기술으로, 높은 해상도에서 게임을 렌더링한 후에 화면 자체 해상도로 결과물을 압축하여 이미지 품질을 높이고 거의 모든 엘리어싱을 제거합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Super Sampling Anti-Aliasing is een uiterst veeleisende, op NVIDIA's Dynamic Super Resolution gelijkende anti-aliasingtechniek, waarmee de game op een hogere resolutie wordt gerenderd voordat het resultaat wordt teruggebracht naar de eigen schermresolutie, waarbij de beeldkwaliteit wordt verbeterd en aliasing nagenoeg volledig wordt geëlimineerd.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Kantutjevning med supersampling er en svært krevende kantutjevningsteknikk som ligner NVIDIAs Dynamic Super Resolution ved at spillet gjengis med høyere oppløsning før resultatet krympes tilbake til den skjermtilpassede oppløsningen, som forbedrer bildekvaliteten og fjerner kantutjevningen nesten helt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Ustawienie wysokiej jakości wygładzanie SSAA jest bardzo wymagającą techniką wygładzania krawędzi, podobną do technologii dynamicznej super rozdzielczości NVIDIA, która renderuje grę z wyższą rozdzielczością, a następnie zmniejsza wynik do natywnej rozdzielczości ekranu, co zwiększa jakość obrazu, prawie całkowicie eliminując poszarpanie krawędzi.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">O antialiasing de superamostragem, é uma técnica de antialiasing, que requer muitos recursos, semelhante à tecnologia Dynamic Super Resolution da NVIDIA, no sentido em que apresenta o jogo com uma resolução superior antes de reduzir o resultado para a resolução de ecrã nativa, melhor*******o a qualidade da imagem e suprimindo o aliasing praticamente na íntegra.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">O antisserrilhamento de superamostragem é uma técnica de antisserrilhamento altamente pesada, similar à tecnologia de super resolução dinâmica da NVIDIA, que renderiza o jogo em uma resolução superior antes de diminuir o resultado de volta à resolução da tela nativa, melhor*******o a qualidade da imagem e elimin*******o quase inteiramente o serrilhamento.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">SSAA — это ресурсоемкий метод сглаживания, схожий с технологией NVIDIA Dynamic Super Resolution, который также позволяет осуществлять рендеринг игры в повышенном разрешении с последующим его уменьшением до исходного разрешения экрана, что повышает качество изображения и практически полностью устраняет "ступенчатость".</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Vyhladzovanie SSAA (Super Sampling Anti-Aliasing) je vysokonáročná technológia vyhladzovania podobná technológii DSR (Dynamic Super Resolution) od spoločnosti NVIDIA, pri ktorej sa hra vykreslí vo vyššom rozlíšení a potom výsledok znova zmenší na natívne rozlíšenie obrazovky, čím sa zlepšuje kvalita obrazu a takmer úplne sa eliminuje vyhladzovanie.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Super vzorčno glajenje robov je zelo zahtevna tehnika glajenja, podobna tehnologiji dinamične super ločljivosti NVIDIA, ki prikaže igro pri višji ločljivosti, preden rezultat spet skrči nazaj na izvorno ločljivost zaslona, kar izboljša kakovost slike in skoraj v celoti odpravi stopičenje.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Tar bort ojämna kanter från föremål och spelelement. Den bästa inställningen, SSAA, är en mycket kräv*******e kantutjämningsteknik som liknar NVIDIA:s Dynamic Super Resolution på så sätt att den renderar spelet med högre upplösning innan resultatet krymps tillbaka till den inbyggda skärmupplösningen, vilket förbättrar bildkvaliteten och nästan helt eliminerar ojämna kanter.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">การลดรอยหยักแบบ Super Sampling เป็นการลดรอยหยักที่ใช้ทรัพยากรสูงคล้ายกับเทคโนโลยี Dynamic Super Resolution ของ NVIDIA ซึ่งแสดงภาพเกมที่ความละเอียดสูงขึ้นก่อนลดขนาดผลลัพธ์ลงเป็นความละเอียดดั้งเดิมของหน้าจอ ซึ่งช่วยปรับปรุงคุณภาพของภาพและเกือบจะลบรอยหยักได้ทั้งหมด</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Süper Örneklemeli Kenar Yumuşatma, NVIDIA Dynamic Super Resolution teknolojisine benzeyen, son derece yüksek sistem performansı gerektiren bir kenar yumuşatma tekniğidir. Oyunun görüntülerini önce daha yüksek bir çözünürlükte oluşturup sonra elde edilen sonucu doğal ekran çözünürlüğüne küçültür. Böylece görüntü kalitesini artırır ve kenarlardaki tırtıklanmayı neredeyse tamamen ortadan kaldırır.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">超级采样反失真是一款类似 NVIDIA 动态超分辨率技术的高要求反失真技术，可以较高分辨率渲染游戏，然后将结果降至本地屏幕分辨率，提高图像质量，并几乎全部消除失真。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">超級採樣消除鋸齒是一種與 NVIDIA 的「動態超高解析度」技術類似的高要求消除鋸齒技術，在將結果重新縮減回原生螢幕解析度之前，會先以較高解析度呈現遊戲，以改善影像畫質並且幾乎完全消除鋸齒。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="SSAO Quality">
    <Image>war_thunder_002.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1170" Top="734" />
    <TextRect Height="113" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adjusts the quality of the game's Screen Space Ambient Occlusion shadowing ******* shading effects.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">ضبط نوعية مؤثرات التظليل بالشاشة الفضائية المحيطة للعبة.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Nastavuje kvalitu efektů stínování funkce Screen Space Ambient Occlusion.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Justerer kvaliteten på spillets skyggelægning og skyggeeffekter under Omgivende tillukning på skærmområde.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt die Qualität der Schatten- und Shading-Effekte der Funktion „Bildschirmbereich – Umgebungsverdeckung”.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσαρμόζει την ποιότητα των εφέ σκιών και σκίασης της περιβαλλοντικής έμφραξης του χώρου οθόνης του παιχνιδιού.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adjusts the quality of the game's Screen Space Ambient Occlusion shadowing ******* shading effects.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Ajusta la calidad de los efectos de sombrado de la Oclusión ambiental en espacio de pantalla del juego.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Ajusta la calidad del sombreado y de los efectos de sombreado de la oclusión ambiental en espacio de pantalla del juego.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Säätää pelin näyttötilan ympäristön sulkemisen varjo- ja varjostustehosteiden laatua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Règle la qualité des effets d'ombre et d'ombrage de l'occlusion ambiante d'espace d'écran du jeu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מכווננת את האיכות של אפקטי ההצללה וההסתרה של 'הסתרה סביבתית של שטח תצוגה' של המשחק.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Beállítja a játékban a képernyőtéri környezeti kitakarás árnyékolásának minőségét és árnyékolási effektusait.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola la qualità dell'ombreggiatura e degli effetti della sfumatura dell'occlusione ambientale dello spazio sullo schermo (SSAO, Screen Space Ambient Occlusion) del gioco.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">ゲームの [画面スペース アンビエント オクルージョン] のシャドーやシェーディング エフェクトのクオリティを調整します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">게임 화면 공간 앰비언트 오클루전(Screen Space Ambient Occlusion) 그림자와 음영 효과의 품질을 조정합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de kwaliteit van schaduwen en schaduwwerking voor de omgevingsocclusie van de schermruimte van de game.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Justerer kvaliteten på spillets omgivelsesbetingede lys på skjermområdet med tanke på skygger og skyggeleggingseffekter.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dostosowuje jakość cieniowania zamknięcia środowiska przestrzeni ekranu w grze i efektów cieniowania.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Ajusta a qualidade dos efeitos de sombras e sombreamento de oclusão ambiental do espaço de ecrã do jogo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ajusta a qualidade dos efeitos de sombra e o sombreamento da Oclusão de Ambiente do Espaço da Tela do jogo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует качество затенения фонового освещения и эффектов затенения.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Upravuje kvalitu tieňovania a efektov tieňovania pri zatienení okolím v priestore obrazovky v hre.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Prilagodi kakovost senčenja vsestranskega zapiranja zaslona in učinkov senčenja.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Justerar kvaliteten på spelets omgiv*******e inneslutning för bildskärmsutrymme för skuggor och skuggeffekter.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับคุณภาพของเอฟเฟกต์การให้แสงและเงาการบดบังแสงแวดล้อมของพื้นที่บนหน้าจอของเกม</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Oyundaki Ekran Alanı Ortam Kapatma gölge ve gölgelendirme efektlerinin kalitesini ayarlar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">调整游戏的屏幕空间环境光吸收阴影和着色效果的质量。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">調整遊戲中的螢幕空間漫射陰影環場遮擋陰影和網底效果的品質。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Terrain Deformation">
    <Image>war_thunder_002.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1658" Top="741" />
    <TextRect Height="97" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adjusts the fidelity, detail ******* accuracy of terrain deformation caused by the movement of tanks.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">ضبط الدقة والتفاصيل وقيم تشوه التضاريس الناتجة عن حركة الدبابات.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Nastavuje věrnost, detail a přesnost deformace terénu způsobenou pohybem tanků.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Justerer nøjagtigheden, detaljeniveauet og præcisionen af terrændeformation, som forårsages af bevægelsen af tanks.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt die Realitätsnähe, den Detailgrad und die Genauigkeit von Geländeverformungen, die durch Panzerbewegungen verursacht werden.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσαρμόζει την πιστότητα, τη λεπτομέρεια και την ακρίβεια της παραμόρφωσης εδάφους που προκαλείται από την κίνηση των τανκς.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adjusts the fidelity, detail ******* accuracy of terrain deformation caused by the movement of tanks.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Ajusta la fidelidad, detalle y precisión de la deformación del terreno causada por el movimiento de los tanques.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Ajusta la fidelidad, el detalle y la precisión de la deformación del terreno provocada por el movimiento de los tanques.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Säätää säiliöiden liikkeen aiheuttamien maaston vääristymien todenmukaisuutta, yksityiskohtaisuutta ja tarkkuutta.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Règle la fidélité, le niveau de détail et la précision des déformations du terrain provoquées par le mouvement des chars.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מכווננת את מידת הנאמנות למציאות, הפירוט והדיוק של שינוי פני השטח כתוצאה מתנועת טנקים.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Beállítja a tankok mozgása által létrehozott terepdeformáció élethűségét, részletességét és pontosságát.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola la fedeltà, il dettaglio e la precisione della deformazione del terreno provocata dallo spostamento dei carri armati.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">戦車の動きによって生じる地形の変形の忠実度、ディテール、正確さを調整します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">탱크 이동으로 발생하는 지형 변형의 정확성, 디테일 및 정밀성을 조정합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Past de precisie, het detail en de nauwkeurigheid van terreinvervorming veroorzaakt door de bewegende tanks aan.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Tilpasser kvaliteten, detaljer og nøyaktigheten på deformasjoner i terrenget som forårsakes av kjørende tanker.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dostosowuje wierność, szczegółowość i dokładność deformacji terenu spowodowanych ruchem czołgów.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Ajusta a fidelidade, o detalhe e a exactidão da deformação do terrena provocada pelos movimentos dos tanques.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ajusta a fidelidade, os detalhes e a precisão da deformação de terreno causada pelo movimento de tanques.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует достоверность, детализацию и точность деформации рельефа, вызванной передвижением танков.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Upravuje vernosť, detaily a presnosť deformácie terénu spôsobenej pohybom tankov.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Prilagodi zvestobo, podrobnost in natančnost deformacij terena, ki jih je povzročilo gibanje tankov.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Justerar återgivning, detaljnivå och korrekthet för terrängdeformation som orsakas av stridsvagnar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับความสมจริง รายละเอียดและความแม่นยำของการเปลี่ยนรูปร่างภูมิประเทศที่เกิดจากการเคลื่อนที่ของรถถัง</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Arazideki, tanklarının hareketinin yol açtığı deformasyonun görsel gerçekçiliğini, ayrıntı ve netlik düzeyini ayarlar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">调整由坦克动作引起的地形变化的逼真度、细节和精度。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">調整坦克車移動造成的地形變形的逼真度、細節和準確性。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Terrain Displacement Quality">
    <Image>war_thunder_015.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1439" Top="817" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adjusts the quality of displacement mapping applied to terrain surfaces.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">يضبط جودة خريطة النشر المطبقة على سطوح التضاريس.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Nastavuje kvalitu mapování při posunu povrchů terénu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Justerer kvaliteten på afbildning af bevægelse, som anvendes på terrænoverflader.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt die Qualität des auf Geländeoberflächen angewendeten Displacement-Mapping-Effekts.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσαρμόζει την ποιότητα της χαρτογράφησης εκτοπίσματος που εφαρμόζεται σε επιφάνειες εδάφους.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adjusts the quality of displacement mapping applied to terrain surfaces.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Ajusta la calidad de la asignación de desplazamiento aplicada a superficies de terrenos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Ajusta la calidad del mapeado de desplazamiento aplicado a las superficies del terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Säätää maaston pintojen siirtymän kartoituksen laatua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Règle la qualité du mappage de déplacement appliqué aux surfaces du terrain.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מכווננת את איכות מיפוי התזוזה החלה על פני השטח.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Beállítja a terepfelületeken alkalmazott mozgásleképezés minőségét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola la qualità del displacement mapping applicato alle superfici del terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">地形の表面に適用されるディスプレイスメント マッピングの質を制御します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">지형 표면에 적용되는 변위 매핑 품질을 조정합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de kwaliteit van op terreinoppervlakken toegepaste verplaatsingen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Justerer kvaliteten på forskyvningskartlegging på terrengoverflater.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dostosowuje jakość mapowania przesunięcia stosowanego na powierzchniach terenu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Ajusta a qualidade da deslocação do mapeamento aplicado às superfícies de terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ajusta a qualidade do mapeamento de deslocamento aplicada às superfícies do terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует качество карт смещения, накладываемых на поверхности рельефа.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Upravuje kvalitu mapovania posunutím použitého na prvkoch terénu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Prilagodi kakovost dodelitve premikov, ki so uporabljeni na površinah terena.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Justerar kvaliteten för förskjutningskartläggning som används på terrängytor.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับคุณภาพของการแม็ปปิ้งแทนที่ที่ใช้กับพื้นผิวภูมิประเทศ</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Arazi yüzeylerine uygulanan yer değiştirme harital*******ırmasının kalitesini ayarlar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">调整应用于地形表面的置换贴图质量。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">調整套用至地形表面的置換 MIP 貼圖品質。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Terrain Quality">
    <Image>war_thunder_003.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1487" Top="840" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Controls the quality ******* fidelity of the terrain.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">يتحكم في جودة ودقة التضاريس.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Určuje kvalitu a věrnost terénu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Styrer kvaliteten og nøjagtigheden på terrænet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Steuert die Qualität und die Detailgenauigkeit des Geländes.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Ελέγχει την ποιότητα και την πιστότητα του εδάφους.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Controls the quality ******* fidelity of the terrain.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Controla la calidad y la fidelidad del terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Controla la calidad y la fidelidad del terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ohjaa maaston laatua ja todenmukaisuutta.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Contrôle la qualité et la fidélité du terrain.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מפקחת על האיכות והאמינות של פני הקרקע.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Szabályozza a terep minőségét és élethűségét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Controlla la qualità e la fedeltà del terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">地形のクオリティと忠実度を制御します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">지형의 품질 및 정확도를 제어합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de kwaliteit en precisie van het terrein.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Angir kvaliteten på terrenget.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Kontroluje jakość i wierność terenu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Controla a qualidade e a fidelidade do terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Controla a qualidade e fidelidade do terreno.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует качество и четкость ландшафта.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Ovláda kvalitu a vernosť terénu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Nadzoruje kakovost in zvestobo terena.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Styr den kvaliteten och återgivningen för terrängen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ควบคุมคุณภาพและความสมจริงของภูมิประเทศ</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Arazinin kalitesini ve görsel gerçekçiliğini belirler.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">控制地形的质量和逼真度。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">控制地形的品質和逼真度。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Texture Quality">
    <Image>war_thunder_007.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1000" Top="924" />
    <TextRect Height="97" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Controls the quality ******* fidelity of textures applied to all objects ******* surfaces in the game.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">التحكم في جودة ودقة مواد الصور المطبقة على كل الكائنات والأسطح في اللعبة.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Určuje kvalitu a věrnost textur použitých na objektech a površích ve hře.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Styrer kvaliteten og nøjagtigheden på teksturer, som anvendes på alle objekter og overflader i spillet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Steuert die Qualität und Detailgenauigkeit der Texturen aller Objekte und Flächen im Spiel.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Ελέγχει την ποιότητα και την πιστότητα των υφών που εφαρμόζονται σε όλα τα αντικείμενα και επιφάνειες στο παιχνίδι.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Controls the quality ******* fidelity of textures applied to all objects ******* surfaces in the game.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Controla la calidad y la fidelidad de las texturas aplicadas a todos los objetos y superficies en el juego.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Controla la calidad y la fidelidad de las texturas que se aplican a todos los objetos y todas las superficies en el juego.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ohjaa pelin jokaiseen esineeseen ja pintaan käytettyjen pintakuvioiden laatua ja todenmukaisuutta.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Ajuste la qualité et la fidélité des textures appliquées à tous les objets et surfaces.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">הגדרה זו מפקחת על איכות ועל מידת הנאמנות למציאות של המרקמים המוחלים על כל הדמויות והמשטחים במשחק.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Szabályozza az összes objektumra és felületre alkalmazott textúrák minőségét és valósághűségét a játékban.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Controlla la qualità e la fedeltà delle texture applicate a tutti gli oggetti e tutte le superfici nel gioco.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">ゲームのすべてのオブジェクトや表面に適用されるテクスチャのクオリティや忠実性を調整します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">게임의 모든 개체 및 표면에 적용되는 텍스처의 품질 및 정확도를 조절합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de kwaliteit en precisie van patronen toegepast op alle objecten en oppervlakken in de game.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Styrer kvaliteten på og troverdigheten til teksturer brukt på alle objekter og overflater i spillet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Kontroluje jakość i dokładność tekstur wszystkich obiektów i powierzchni w grze.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Controla a qualidade e a fidelidade das texturas aplicadas a todos os objectos e superfícies no jogo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Controla a qualidade e a fidelidade das texturas aplicadas a todos os objetos e superfícies no jogo.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует качество и четкость текстур всех объектов и поверхностей в игре.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Ovláda kvalitu a vernosť textúr všetkých objektov a povrchov v hre.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Nadzoruje kakovost in verodostojnost tekstur, uporabljenih na vseh predmetih in površinah v igri.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Styr kvaliteten och återgivningen på de texturer som används för alla föremål och ytor i spelet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ควบคุมคุณภาพและความสมจริงของลักษณะพื้นผิวที่ใช้กับออบเจกต์และพื้นผิวทั้งหมดในเกม</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Oyundaki bütün nesnelere ve yüzeylere uygulanan dokuların kalitesini ve görsel gerçekçiliğini kontrol eder.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">控制应用于游戏中所有物体和表面的纹理质量和逼真度。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">控制套用至遊戲中所有物件和表面的紋理的品質和逼真度。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Tire/track Marks">
    <Image>war_thunder_002.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="1449" Top="615" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Enables the rendering of vehicle tire tracks, ******* adjusts the quality of the effect.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">تمكين مسارات إطارات المركبة وضبط جودة التأثيرات.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Aktivuje renderování stop od pneumatik vozidel a nastavuje kvalitu tohoto efektu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Aktiverer gengivelsen af hjulspor fra køretøjer, og justerer kvaliteten af effekten.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Aktiviert die Darstellung von Reifenspuren der Fahrzeuge und regelt die Qualität des Effekts.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Ενεργοποιεί τη φωτοαπόδοση των ιχνών ελαστικών οχήματος, και προσαρμόζει την ποιότητα του εφέ.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Enables the rendering of vehicle tyre tracks, ******* adjusts the quality of the effect.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Activa la representación de las huellas de neumáticos de los vehículos y ajusta la calidad del efecto.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Activa el renderizado de las huellas de neumáticos de vehículos y ajusta la calidad del efecto.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ottaa käyttöön ajoneuvon renkaan jälkien piirron ja säätää tehosteen laatua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Active le rendu des traces de pneus des véhicules et permet d'en régler la qualité.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מאפשרת הפקת סימני צמיגים של כלי רכב, ומכווננת את איכות האפקט.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Bekapcsolja a járművek keréknyomainak megjelenítését, és beállítja az effektus minőségét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Abilita il rendering delle tracce degli pneumatici dei veicoli e regola la qualità dell'effetto.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">車のタイヤ痕のレンダリングを有効化し、エフェクトのクオリティを調整します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">자동차 타이어 트랙의 렌더링을 활성화하고 효과 품질을 조절합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Maakt het mogelijk b*******ensporen van voertuigen te renderen en regelt de kwaliteit van het effect.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Aktiverer gjengivelsen av hjulspor og tilpasser kvaliteten på effekten.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Włącza renderowanie śladów opon pojazdów i dostosowuje jakość tego efektu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Activa a apresentação das marcas de pneus dos veículos e ajusta a qualidade do efeito.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Habilita a renderização de marcas de pneus e ajusta a qualidade do efeito.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Включает отображение следов от шин и регулирует качество этого эффекта.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Aktivuje vykresľovanie stôp po pneumatikách vozidiel a upravuje kvalitu tohto efektu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Omogoči prikaz sledi gum vozila in prilagodi kakovost učinka.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Aktiverar rendering av fordonsspår och justerar effektens kvalitet.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">เปิดการทำงานการแสดงภาพรอยเส้นทางจากยางของยานพาหนะ และปรับคุณภาพของเอฟเฟกต์</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Araç tekerlek izlerinin görüntüsünü etkinleştirir ve efektin kalitesini ayarlar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">启用车辆轮胎印渲染，并调整效果质量。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">使遊戲呈現車輛的輪胎軌跡，並且調整效果的品質。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Tree Range">
    <Image>war_thunder_001.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="457" Top="444" />
    <TextRect Height="161" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Controls the distance at which trees, houses ******* other objects are visible, ******* adjusts the game's level of detail setting, which reduces the fidelity of game elements as the player moves further from them.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">التحكم في المسافة التي تكون عندها الأشجار، المنازل والكائنات الأخرى مرئية، وضبط مستوى اللعبة لإعداد التفاصيل، الذي يقلل دقة عناصر اللعبة عند تحرك اللاعب بعيداً عنها.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Určuje vzdálenost, na kterou jsou stromy, domy a jiné objekty viditelné a nastavuje úroveň detailů ve hře, která snižuje věrnost herních prvků, když se hráč pohybuje ve větší vzdálenosti od nich.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Styrer den afst******* hvorved træer, huse og *******re objekter er synlige, og justerer spillets indstilling for detaljeniveau, hvilket reducerer nøjagtigheden af spillets elementer, efterhånden som spilleren bevæger sig længere væk fra dem.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Steuert die Entfernung, in der Bäume, Häuser und sonstige Objekte sichtbar sind, und regelt die Detailgradeinstellung des Spiels, wodurch die Detailgenauigkeit der Spielelemente abnimmt, je weiter sich der Spieler von ihnen entfernt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Ελέγχει την απόσταση από την οποία τα δέντρα, τα σπίτια και άλλα αντικείμενα είναι ορατά και προσαρμόζει τη ρύθμιση του επιπέδου λεπτομερειών του παιχνιδιού, γεγονός που μειώνει την πιστότητα των στοιχείων παιχνιδιού καθώς ο παίκτης απομακρύνεται από αυτά.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Controls the distance at which trees, houses ******* other objects are visible, ******* adjusts the game's level of detail setting, which reduces the fidelity of game elements as the player moves further from them.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Controla la distancia a la que los árboles, las casas y otros objetos son visibles, y ajusta el nivel de detalle del juego, que reduce la fidelidad de los elementos del juego a medida que el jugador se aleja de ellos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Controla la distancia a la que pueden verse los árboles, las casas y otros objetos del juego, y ajusta la configuración de nivel de detalle del juego, lo que reduce la fidelidad de los elementos del juego a medida que el jugador se aleja de ellos.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Ohjaa, miltä etäisyydeltä puut, talot ja muut esineet näkyvät, ja säätää pelin yksityiskohta-asetuksen tasoa, mikä vähentää pelin elementtien todenmukaisuutta pelaajan liikkuessa kauemmas niistä.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Contrôle la distance à laquelle les arbres, maisons et autres objets sont visibles. Règle le niveau de détail, ce qui réduit la fidélité des éléments à mesure que le joueur s'en éloigne.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מפקחת על המרחק שממנו נראים עצים, בתים ועצמים אחרים, ומכווננת את הגדרת רמת הפירוט של המשחק, שמצמצמת את נאמנות רכיבי המשחק כאשר השחקן מתרחק מהם.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Szabályozza azt a távolságot, amelyen belül a fák, házak és más objektumok láthatók, és beállítja a játék részletességét, amely meghatározza a játékelemek élethűségét, amint a játékosok távolodnak tőlük.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Controlla la distanza di visualizzazione di alberi, case e altri oggetti e regola di conseguenza l'impostazione del livello di dettaglio del gioco, riducendo la fedeltà degli elementi man mano che il giocatore si allontana da essi.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">樹木、家屋、その他のオブジェクトの表示距離を制御し、ゲームの詳細度を調整します。これで、プレーヤーが遠くに離れた際のゲーム要素の性を減少させます。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">나무, 집 및 기타 개체의 가시 거리를 조절하고, 플레이어가 이들 개체로부터 멀어질 때 게임 요소의 정확도를 감소시키는 게임의 세부 설정의 수준을 제어합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de afst******* waarop bomen, huizen en *******ere objecten zichtbaar zijn en past het detailniveau van de game aan, waarbij de precisie van game-elementen afneemt naarmate de speler zich ervan af beweegt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Styrer avst*******en for når trær, hus og *******re objekter skal være synlige, justerer spillets detaljnivå slik at naturtroheten til spillelementer reduseres i takt med at spilleren beveger seg bort fra dem.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Kontroluje odległość, z jakiej widoczne są drzewa, domy i inne obiekty oraz dostosowuje poziom ustawienia szczegółowości gry, co powoduje zmniejszanie wierności elementów gry, gdy gracz się od nich oddala.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Controla a distância a que árvores, casas e outros objectos são visíveis, e ajusta o nível de detalhe do jogo, o que reduz a fidelidade dos elementos do jogo, à medida que o jogador se afasta.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Controla a distância na qual as árvores, casas e outros objetos são visíveis, e ajusta a configuração do nível de detalhes do jogo, que reduz a fidelidade dos elementos do jogo qu*******o o jogador se afasta deles.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует дальность видимости деревьев, зданий и других объектов, а также параметр уровня детализации игры, который снижает четкость элементов игры, когда игрок отдаляется от них.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Ovláda vzdialenosť, z ktorej sú viditeľné stromy, domy a iné objekty, a upravuje nastavenie detailov v úrovniach hry. Keď sa hráč vzďaľuje od prvkov hry, znižuje sa tým ich vernosť.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Nadzoruje razdaljo, pri kateri so vidni drevje, hiše in drugi predmeti in prilagodi raven nastavitve podrobnosti v igri, kar zniža zvestobo elementov igre, ko se igralec oddaljuje od njih.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Styr på vilket avstånd träd, hus och *******ra föremål syns, och justerar spelets inställning för detaljnivå, vilket minskar återgivningen av spelelement när spelaren rör sig bort från dem.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ควบคุมระยะที่สามารถมองเห็นต้นไม้ บ้าน และวัตถุอื่นๆ ได้ และปรับระดับการตั้งค่ารายละเอียดของเกม ซึ่งจะลดความละเอียดขององค์ประกอบในเกมขณะที่ผู้เล่นเคลื่อนออกห่างจากระยะนั้น</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Ağaçların, evlerin ve diğer nesnelerin hangi mesafeye kadar görünür kalacağını kontrol eder ve oyundaki ayrıntı düzeyini ayarlar. Böylece oyuncu, nesnelerden uzaklaştıkça, oyundaki öğelerin görsel gerçekçiliği azalır.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">控制树木、房子和其他物体的可见距离，并调整游戏的细节级别设置（可在玩家逐渐远离游戏元素时降低游戏元素的逼真度）。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">控制樹木、房屋和其他物體的可見距離，並且調整遊戲的精細度設定，隨著玩家一邊拉遠距離，一邊降低遊戲元素的逼真度。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="VSync">
    <Image>war_thunder_009.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="379" Top="140" />
    <TextRect Height="113" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Synchronizes the game's refresh rate with your computer monitor to minimize screen tearing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">مزامنة معدل تحديث اللعبة مع شاشة الكمبيوتر الخاصة بك لتقليل تمزق الشاشة.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Synchronizuje obnovovací frekvenci hry s monitorem počítače a minimalizuje tak trhání obrazovky.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Synkroniserer spillets opdateringshastighed med din computerskærm for at minimere skærmforvrængning.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Synchronisiert die Bildwiederholfrequenz mit Ihrem Computermonitor, um Screen Tearing zu minimieren.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Συγχρονίζει το ρυθμό ανανέωσης του παιχνιδιού με την οθόνη υπολογιστή σας ώστε να ελαχιστοποιείται το σχίσιμο οθόνης.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Synchronises the game's refresh rate with your computer monitor to minimise screen tearing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Sincroniza la frecuencia de actualización del juego con la del monitor para reducir al mínimo la distorsión de la pantalla.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Sincroniza la frecuencia de actualización del juego con la del monitor para reducir al mínimo la distorsión de la pantalla.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Synkronisoi pelin virkistystaajuuden tietokonenäytön virkistystaajuuteen screen tearing -efektin (näytön jakautumisen useammaksi kuvaksi) minimoimiseksi.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Synchronise le taux de rafraîchissement du jeu avec celui de votre moniteur pour limiter les effets de tearing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">הגדרה זו מסנכרנת את ערך תדירות הרענון של המשחק עם זה של התקן התצוגה כדי להפחית למינימום את תופעת הקריעה בתמונת התצוגה.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Szinkronizálja a játék frissítési gyakoriságát a számítógép monitorával, így minimalizálja a képszakadást.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Sincronizza la frequenza di aggiornamento del gioco con il monitor del computer per minimizzare l'effetto tearing.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">ゲームのリフレッシュレートをコンピューターのモニターと同期させて、ティアリングを最小限に抑えます。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">화면 찢김 현상을 최소화하기 위해 컴퓨터 모니터의 게임 재생 빈도를 동기화합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Synchroniseert de vernieuwingsfrequentie van de game met uw computermonitor om scheureffecten op het scherm te minimaliseren.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Synkroniserer spillets oppdateringsfrekvens med dataskjermen for å redusere deloppdatering til et minimum.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Synchronizuje częstotliwość odświeżania gry z monitorem komputera, aby zminimalizować rozwarstwianie obrazu.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Sincroniza a taxa de actualização do jogo com o monitor do computador para minimizar as imperfeições.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Sincroniza a taxa de atualização do jogo com o monitor do seu computador para minimizar a distorção da tela.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Синхронизирует частоту обновления игры с монитором используемого компьютера для уменьшения разрывов изображения на экране.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Synchronizuje frekvenciu obnovenia hry s monitorom počítača na minimalizovanie trhania obrazovky.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Sinhronizira hitrost osveževanja igre z vašim zaslonom, da zmanjša trganje zaslona.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Synkroniserar spelets uppdateringsintervall med din datorskärm så att skärmen störs minimalt.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ซิงโครไนซ์อัตราการปรับภาพของเกมกับจอภาพคอมพิวเตอร์ของคุณเพื่อลดรอยขาดของหน้าจอให้เหลือน้อยที่สุด</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Görüntü kopmalarını en aza indirmek için, oyunun yenileme hızını bilgisayar monitörününkiyle senkronize eder.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">将游戏的刷新率和您的计算机显示器同步，以最大程度减少画面撕裂。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">同步化遊戲重新整理頻率和電腦螢幕，以盡可能地減少畫面撕裂。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
  <SettingInfo Name="Water Quality">
    <Image>war_thunder_015.jpg</Image>
    <RegionRect Height="40" Width="40" Left="646" Top="724" />
    <TextRect Height="81" Width="260" />
    <TextInfoList>
      <TextInfo Language="en_US">Adjusts the fidelity ******* detail of water surfaces.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ar_AE">ضبط دقة وتفاصيل أسطح الماء.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="cs_CZ">Nastavuje věrnost a detail vodních povrchů.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="da_DK">Justerer nøjagtigheden og detaljerne på v*******overflader.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="de_DE">Regelt die Detailgenauigkeit von Wasseroberflächen.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="el_GR">Προσαρμόζει την πιστότητα και λεπτομέρεια των υδάτινων επιφανειών.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="en_GB">Adjusts the fidelity ******* detail of water surfaces.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_ES">Ajusta la fidelidad y el detalle de superficies de agua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="es_MX">Ajusta la fidelidad y detalle de las superficies del agua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fi_FI">Säätää veden pinnan todenmukaisuutta ja yksityiskohtien määrää.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="fr_FR">Règle la fidélité et le niveau de détail des surfaces aquatiques.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="he_IL">מכווננת את האמינות והפרטים של משטחי מים.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="hu_HU">Beállítja a vízfelületek valósághűségét és részletességét.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="it_IT">Regola la fedeltà e il dettaglio degli specchi d'acqua.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ja_JP">水面の忠実度とディテールを調整します。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ko_KR">물 표면의 정확도와 디테일을 조정합니다.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nl_NL">Regelt de precisie en het detail van wateroppervlakken.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="nb_NO">Justerer nøyaktighet og detalje på vannoverflater.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pl_PL">Dostosowuje jakość i szczegółowość powierzchni wody.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_PT">Ajusta a fidelidade e o detalhe das superfícies de água.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="pt_BR">Ajusta a fidelidade e o detalhe das superfícies aquáticas.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="ru_RU">Регулирует четкость и детализацию водных поверхностей.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sk_SK">Upravuje vernosť a detaily vodných povrchov.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sl_SI">Prilagodi zvestobo in podrobnosti vodnih površin.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="sv_SE">Justerar återgivning och detaljnivå för vattenytor.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="th_TH">ปรับความแม่นยำและรายละเอียดของผิวน้ำ</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="tr_TR">Su yüzeylerinin görsel gerçekçiliğini ve ayrıntı düzeyini ayarlar.</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHS">调整水面的逼真度和细节。</TextInfo>
      <TextInfo Language="zh_CHT">調整水面的逼真度和細節。</TextInfo>
    </TextInfoList>
  </SettingInfo>
</Application>
