<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<strings>

  <!--Report template-->
  <string id="ReportTitle">[OQcGD][Windows App Certification Kit - Τзśŧ Řëšŭℓŧŝ !!! !!! !!! ]</string>

  <!--Program template-->
  <string id="NotAvailable">[5aEMP][Йôŧ Áνâϊļάьŀê !!!]</string>
  <string id="AppName">[aMt54][Аρр ņâмė: !!] </string>
  <string id="AppVersion">[cz66X][Λφφ νėяśīōи: !!!] </string>
  <string id="AppPublisher">[sob2w][Дρр φΰьľĩśĥёř: !!!] </string>
  <string id="AppArchitecture">[uo72z][Ãφр Áґćђίŧεсŧΰŕε: !!! ] </string>
  <string id="OSDetails">[9qRs2][ÖŚ Vеѓšĩôŉ: !!] </string>
  <string id="KitVersion">[2WkWH][Кϊт Vēŗŝīôή: !!!] </string>
  <string id="Architecture">[UZf1c][ΘŠ Àŕçħϊтęсŧūґē: !!! ] </string>
  <string id="PartialRunWarningWindowsStore">[i8XUQ][Йστ âļľ ŧзѕţŝ ẅēřэ ґūй ďŭřϊñġ νάℓϊďăτĭóη. Ťћĭš mąу ιmφάçţ ỳǿϋя Ŝтöřз ѕûвмįšşìøŉ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!] </string>
  <string id="PartialRunWarningLearnMore">[1MOq4][Łёǻřⁿ mòгέ !!]</string>
  <string id="VersionWarningStore">[tRKlX][Ťнΐš гёφθѓţ ώăš ĝĕиēгąţéð ώιтħ ãл őůţďªτéď νĕřѕĭθŋ θƒ ťĥě Щĩñđōẁş Àφφ €ěятīƒìςāţîǿп Кįт, ǻлď ŷοϋř αрφ мāу ƒâìļ ťнє ŝűьмїśѕїøη рŕбċèŝѕ αѕ á ŗεśúŀŧ. Ŵê ђíġђŀỳ яéċŏmмèήď ŗüήηĩпģ ťне νąłĭďáťíőй üśΐηĝ ţђе ļäţéѕţ ν℮ŗśιǿŋ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="ClickToDownload">[PkFkf][Сĺĩćķ ћеŗē ţō đøωлļθãð ŧħэ ĺāţзѕŧ νèřşιõπ !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="x64OnlyWarning">[NjolA][Ρŀēàşē ěиŝϋѓė тσ ăļѕŏ ŧέšт αйð śùьmїт αй ж86 φǻčĸǻĝє тǿ τнέ ѕтòгέ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!] </string>

  <!--TimeStamp template-->
  <string id="RepGenTime">[krxxW][Гēρŏŕτ ţїmê: !!!] </string>

  <!--OverallResult template-->
  <string id="OverallScore">[J3WqA][Оνĕгάļĺ ѓ℮şůłť: !!!] </string>
  <string id="InterimRepNotice">[OndMl][Ϊñ¢óмρľëτě - Ťĥίş īś аń īпţэŗįм гėρøŗť; φĺèаşэ čőⁿţΐⁿüэ ẁîτћ ŧђэ Ţŏõłќįţ ẃïžαяď ťθ ƒίŋàļíźë ţћэ ѓēρσřт. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="ResultPass">[Q52Ye][ΡÄŠЅЁÐ !]</string>
  <string id="ResultFail">[nIPjo][₣ĂİĿЭÐ !]</string>
  <string id="ResultPwW">[W9f1H][Ρ∆ŠЅЗĎ ŴІŤН ẄÀŘŃÌПĜŠ !!! !]</string>
  <string id="FixWarningCases">[yAQCN][Îτ іš ħΐğħłγ ŗεċōmмзиδ℮ď тнàŧ ŷōμ īńν℮şτĭğāţę дпđ гοστ çāцŝē ẅаŗήïйġş тο ęŉŝūřë тђαť υşèяѕ ôƒ ŷόúř àφφ àřëⁿ’ť ⁿєģāŧїνεļŷ įmρªςŧęδ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>

  <!--OptionalResults template-->
  <string id="OptionalTests">[GbJFU][Ѓёśúļτѕ ƒøґ θφťìσņăŀ тèşŧš !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="OptionalTestsNotice">[ajnwr][Ŧћè ťєŝţś іņ ţнįś śę¢τϊοй ǻřэ įňƒŏřмäťíоήåļ őиļŷ ąйđ ώĭĺŀ ήóт вє џš℮đ ţό éνăłûãτė ўόΰŗ ăрρ ďŭѓīņĝ Мĩ¢ŗσśŏƒт Ѕτôгз όňъθãѓðīŉģ.  Їπνēѕŧïğåτĭⁿğ ƒăïļüгéš ìѕ г℮ċőмmêñðęð ťö ěлşűřė τĥåŧ üşĕŕŝ ẃιłℓ ŋστ ьê їмφãčťєď. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>

  <!--Test template-->
  <string id="ResultSkip">[ntxW6][ŚĶΊΡРĒĐ !]</string>
  <string id="ResultWarn">[Ff0Yi][ẀÅΓŇĪŇĜ !]</string>
  <string id="TestCase">[J6Gw8][Ťèšţ ĉǻŝę: !!] </string>

  <!--TestError template-->
  <string id="SignedFilesExtraMessage">[Bne9q][Άłł ũņšíğπêđ ƒĩĺĕś бƒ ţħε ƒōĺℓǿŵïήġ ℮×тёńśĩőńš: ĚЖËŝ, ĐĹŁŝ, ЅỲŚ, ÐΓV, ÒСХ, ŜСЯ, αňδ €РĻ шíŀŀ вє я℮φθґтëð. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="NoAdditionalInfo">[j8nTz][Иò αďđįτįθŋªł įлƒôѓмäтĩôⁿ ƒŏŕ !!! !!! ] </string>
  <string id="Requirement"> [2pDSB][Ѓëqŭíŗеmέŉτ: !!!] </string>
  <string id="Test"> [8lEuI][Тėŝť: !] </string>
  <string id="TestWarning">[y7Zzp][Ẁдŗņĭήĝ: !] </string>
  <string id="TestInformation">[qE3ty][Ĩйƒøгмãтīǿи: !!!] </string>
  <string id="TestError">[u2UAX][Èґгοŕ ₣όũňð: !!!] </string>
  <string id="Impact">[0ZS9P][Ĩмφáċţ ĭƒ ñőť ƒіхèď: !!! !] </string>
  <string id="ImpactInformation">[8Vq07][Ϊmφάčŧ: !] </string>
  <string id="HowToFix">[XecOU][Нǿώ τō ƒіх: !!] </string>

  <string id="1_1_NoChange">
    [GQfKi][ẄŚŁĶ δîδй'ţ ď℮ŧęćτ ªŋγ ċћдπĝзŝ тб ťђз ѕγşŧέm, ťћīš ċσûłδ вэ đúĕ тθ ä úήşµссèśşƒüŀ öř ΐņċǿmφŀêťë ũñîñŝťăĺℓ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
[GQfKi][    Ρľèªśė ϋпϊйŝтáŀļ убűя ăррĺîćǻтιòŋ âňð гúń тћĭş şтзр бп¢ĕ уòū ǻŕě ðŏп℮. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="1_1_FailedToRemovFiles">[2o0wk][Τнě йöŋ-šћǻяěđ ƒïĺэś дňð ƒòŀđеŕş ŧεѕτ đēţè¢тėđ ţĥē ƒόℓľбŵιйğ êґřοґš: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="1_1_Impact">
    [gJ93K][Д ŭŝĕя mìģђť řēmòνę ǻñ дρр τø ƒя℮έ ûρ δΐşĸ ŝрдćё σř ŧθ ŕэţцѓи τћэ ćσmрũţêř ŧŏ тħ℮ şŧαтé ъêƒøґ℮ ΐņŝтăļľīňĝ τђê ãрр. Ţћè ύňίлşτдłℓ φѓòςèşš мΰśť řэşŧǿґε τнė мдçħїйĕ ŧǿ ĩŧş őříĝϊňάļ śťдŧе ƒöŕ ťђè вēѕť ΰšεŗ ĕхφєгϊзή¢ę. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="1_1_HowToFix">[ucCPA][Ґэмбνĕ āĺł τĥє ƒíℓĕŝ âŋδ Ąðð/Γęмθνê Ргøĝґăм êⁿтřіέś. Śéě ľíŉκ ьеŀóẅ ƒθŗ мοяè їиƒόґмāţîòⁿ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="1_1_HowToFix2">[EDetc][İлšţªŀℓēг Рґõφєŕτΐзš !!! !]</string>

  <string id="1_2_RebootRqd">
    [f7Kyv][Τн℮ αρр ƒōгсέđ ãπ ĭммèđїǻŧē ѓėвǿόт ăƒŧēř ĩŉѕťâĺł. !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="1_2_Impact">[c8prC][₣ôяćΐпģ ŧђê υşèŗ ţó řęŝţāѓť тђęìŕ čõмрūţεя гĩğђт áƒŧêŗ ţĥêў ĭŋšтäŀℓ ŧħέ ãрр čāŋ ¢дųѕē тĥęm ťŏ ℓǿšē δдтά ƒřŏм òτħèř ąφφŝ тħàţ måŷ ь℮ яυийΐņğ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="1_2_HowToFix1">[EIRRa][Ťħ℮ дрр śћöųĺδ дĺłòŵ ţђε ϋśěѓ ŧö řěѕτаѓτ ŧћēĩř ĉômρμтĕя ľάτеř. Śèè łïŉĸ ьεℓőẅ ƒσя mōѓέ ιŉƒояmáτîóŉ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="1_2_HowToFix2">[GzlL8][Śтªŉδăґδ Īπśтαļłεř Ćǿmmâиδ-£ĭⁿε Őφťíöŉѕ !!! !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="1_3_RebootRqd">
    [r0PtG][Τђє άрρ ƒôŗčэđ åň ιмmėδιатé гėвóōť âƒτèѓ µŉįήšŧăĺℓ. !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="1_3_Impact">[hMcU5][₣óгсіŉĝ тћĕ úšєґ ţō ѓěśтдгť τђёіř ςŏmφϋтєґ ѓĭĝћţ äƒťзґ ţĥěý ũйĭⁿšŧǻĺℓ ţђ℮ дφр ςàŉ ςãύśē ŧћέм ţо ļοѕз δáťǻ ƒŕøм őŧĥеř åрφš ŧħáţ máỳ ъέ řцņпιηĝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="1_3_HowToFix1">[0dxuV][Д ŕéъöοт şħöűĺδ ήêνёг ьē τћε òήłу σρťîθņ шħĕŉ ųņΐηşтдŀłìиĝ àŋ āрφŀïĉàťĭοл. Úšéѓş ŝĥǿμļð ћάνз τħё орρøяτμπΐţỳ τö ŗĕŝŧαřţ ļąтėŗ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !] </string>
  <string id="1_3_HowToFix2">[5VeWY][Ѕťãηďãгđ Įņѕτάŀľеŕ Ċóмmаŋď-Ļίйё Ōρţìòйѕ !!! !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="1_4_ValidARP1">
    [oOduG][Ťћ℮ яёģìѕŧґў рöρũļáτīòŋ ŧэśт ďéťéċτеđ тђé ƒòľĺôωīņġ згŗòř: аφρ ðіδņ’τ ċя℮ąτэ тђè řεqüΐŗęď řеĝïşтяу ėŉτяìέś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="1_4_Impact">
    [NL8ue][Дρρş мûşŧ ĉґёаŧέ τħёšē ŗêģīŝŧŕу ēŉťѓΐęŝ ĎіşрŀáŷŃąме, ÌñŝτāℓŀŁøςªţïθŉ, Ρûъĺîѕнêř, ЦŋíⁿśтдľℓЅŧŕίņğ äŋď ΡяσδûčτVэŗŝĭøŋ. Άрρѕ ŧђäτ đбņ’ť ċяєąŧę τħě яёqüîгĕđ ŗеġїşτгÿ êиτѓįεş mдγ ηöт вε ƒόµπð вÿ ěŉŧ℮яряϊѕ℮ ίńνěņţоřỳ ťöσļś. Ŧђìѕ çāπ ċªµşз φґóъĺëмѕ ẁĩτĥ ÖŞ mĭğгатίōпѕ αňđ üρģѓāδёś, àŉð Шìŉďōωś тėŀēмëťŕў ťόōľš mąў лσт ãçĉůŗǻťěℓу ŗэφοřť ΐñƒо ãьöůť τħē ªρφ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="1_4_HowToFix1">
    [BC4F9][Äδď τћз лéçэѕŝǻŗỳ ïŋƒθ το τђě дрφ’ś Щīñďŏẁš Îņšťåłℓėг ρàċĸąğė ŝó ιτ čаŋ сǿŋƒιģџřє Дďđ/Γéмŏνе Ρŕбģřάmš ΐń Ĉоиťřǿĺ Ρăňēŀ сöřѓэçтļў. Ѕєţŧіŋģ ŧĥεѕз φřòрéŗτìėš áŭτõмąτϊćàŀĺў ŵŕϊŧзŝ τнê ċοѓřēѕрбйďïŉġ νǻŀûēš īⁿŧõ ťħè řĕġіšŧяý. Ѕéе ľīñќ ьэľόẅ ƒōŕ моřз íŋƒōŗmâтίõп: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="1_4_HowToFix2">[BbTYx][Ċόπƒіġμгїŋġ Λđδ/Γĕмŏνз Ρгσğŗǻмş !!! !!! ]</string>

  <string id="1_5_NoPass">[QNhtt][Ťĥê ŝîņģĺě μşęř řéĝįšŧяў теŝť ďēτè¢ťêδ ŧнё ƒöłℓòщіńģ єřŕόґѕ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !] </string>
  <string id="1_5_Impact">[hHBGd][Ťĥë аρρłісåţΐŏń ĭş åνäïļãъľè ţó åŀľ úšėřś бƒ ŧĥĕ мåснїηĕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="1_5_HowToFix">[lACzg][Їή â Рёя ūşзя іŉŝťäļŀãťίõη, şђθüĺď ŉŏť ċѓёàţĕ ǿя мòđîƒу мαςнîпé ẁΐðę řėġĭŝтгγ êⁿťѓĩėš (HKLM). !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="2_1_WrongFolders">[1yO5c][Ẃгιŧįпĝ ţõ Щíŋđóωš đίґéςťθŗý, дňď σя ŗσôť đïřėċţθřīéŝ ţêŝт ďєтеćтěδ ŧнέ ƒσľłõшϊпğ зřŗòѓś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="2_1_Impact1">
    [D3jlf][Άррš мύşťп’ŧ ŝтǿřê ďåтª įⁿ śγšтėм ƒòľđзŗś, ŝυ¢ћ ąѕ %ŚŷśťэmĐŕĩνέ% øŕ %ẄїńÐΐŕ%. Şтőřΐиğ αрр āлδ üŝėř δãтä ĭň ă şỳŝтëm ƒōĺđèг čªй çąΰśé αĉсêѕş ªņδ śё¢ûřїţỳ ρґőвĺémś ƒόř тĥĕ ϋŝег. Ùśíйġ ţĥě Ķŉбщņ ₣θľðэґ ΛРĪş эпšúгєѕ тђāţ уóυ äŕĕ àŀẅäÿš ªъℓе ţό ġ℮ţ τő ÿоϋŕ ďǻŧа. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="2_1_HowToFix1">
    [iwiQa][Ŵŕįťє τђэ ƒϊļęś τō тн℮ çοŗŗе¢ť ƒőŀďēгš. Şěé ℓĭπķ ъēłøŵ ƒõя møřе ĭηƒσřmåţïöⁿ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="2_1_HowToFix2">[Bj7lY][Ẁòřĸїńġ щīţћ Κпōẃń ₣бļðēяѕ !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="2_2_WrongFolders">[qpAG3][Ťħе їйşţãℓŀ ţô Ρŕοğгαм ₣ίłēş ťëѕţ ðэťэçŧеδ ťћě ƒøłłσώïήġ еґяõяš: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="2_2_Impact1">
    [YF1ew][∏ăţîνз αрφš ė.ĝ. 32 аŋď 64 ьíţ mϋśт ъέ îŋѕţāľŀэď ťŏ ţђè %Ρѓõğѓаm₣īŀéś% ƒŏℓđёŕ ьγ ðёƒąūłť, πőτę ťћàт 32 ъįτ ãφφš įлśŧаĺĺϊηğ ŏπ ж64 νėѓśїőŋѕ όƒ Ẃĩήđòωś мųŝţ вè şтоřēδ ùйδėŕ %Рябġяām₣іĺęś(х86)%. Şţőѓίŋĝ рŗøĝŗàm ƒїŀèѕ ΐп аņöťħéг ƒøℓðёř сâⁿ ċāµŝē å¢сęŝŝ άпð śεçúѓīťý φгøъłęmş ƒŏя τĥě ϋѕéя. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="2_2_HowToFix1">
    [yrgWP][Ẁяΐтє ţћê ƒīŀëś τò ŧĥē ςöѓѓ℮ςŧ ƒōŀðέгş. Śêє ℓîπќ вĕŀőẁ ƒοř мσґĕ įŋƒθřмдťΐσñ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="2_2_HowToFix2">[NYyVJ][Ŵøѓķîиģ ωïτħ Ќñбŵл ₣òŀδèřŝ !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="2_3_NoPass">[qWJzD][Ťнë Шіпðòŵѕ ŝŧâŕτŭφ ąρρ ŀöâδїŋğ тĕŝт δёţëċтєð тĥё ƒбŀľǿŵĩńğ êѓřσŕŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="2_3_Impact">
    [FNXEZ][Āφрš ťћǻτ ľоàδ âŧ şŧǻяτùφ māý ćăϋśе ŭŋďéŝįяáъŀè ěƒƒεсţś śϋčђ åš, ðìśрℓąỳΐńĝ ùñщαñтéď рǿр-űφŝ, řēðůčĩиġ ьąţťěґŷ ļїƒз, óř čáūśîņğ ţнé ĉбмрųŧĕř ťó ьě¢омę ľэşš ґеšφöйѕīνе. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="2_3_HowToFix1">[4ibc7][₣ōℓŀőώ τћё ъέѕτ ряáçŧĩčēŝ ƒσя тђέ σή/ǿƒƒ τяàńşïŧιόⁿ. Ѕėэ ĺΐŉķ вêĺόш ƒоŗ mόřë íⁿƒσгmăťįσп: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="2_3_HowToFix2">[SUL39][Ẅìηðǿωş Оñ/Φƒƒ Τгàлśĩŧīőлş Şбℓϋţìŏήş Ğύïđз !!! !!! !!! ]</string>

  <string id="3_1_AppInitKey">[xPBZz][Ţђэ ΑрρĬńіť_ĐŁŁŝ ţéŝт đέтêςŧĕδ ŧħз ƒǿŀľøŵĩήģ εгŕòŗѕ: !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="3_1_Impact">
    [aMlEl][Аρφś ŧнáţ įйšţдľļ ÁрφΊňīť ÐĽĻѕ ċåл’т ьз ςĕѓтįƒіęδ. Тĥĕ ĀφρÌήĭт ĐĻĻŝ ǻŕє łόаđ℮đ ьý ¢ǻℓľįήğ Ĺǿăð₤íвřąŕў() δϋѓįиģ тће ÐĽĹ_РЯΩĈЭЅŚ_ÀТŦĀÇΉ рѓôčęŝŝ όƒ Ůšęя32.đĺŀ. Τђēϊґ έάŗłŷ ŀŏдδįпġ φřøνíðёŝ åŋ єаšγ ŵàγ ƒσŕ mаļẃдřé τǿ ґūй ĭŋ ěνеřў ρѓŏçеšŝ. Іт čäή ăℓŝô çàűѕë śýşτěм ďэдđľοċķş, аņď мǻý ðéĉřєâŝє ŝŷśťęm ѓèľîâъіℓìту дŉđ φęѓƒòŕмдñĉе. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="3_1_HowToFix">
    [PpNbq][Ŭśë ąⁿōťĥεŕ тëćћŉïqüè τø αĉнįзνę śīmįĺªѓ ґеѕũłŧş. Šëέ ľïпķ в℮łбώ ƒǿŕ мσґě ΐлƒóѓмáτΐóń: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="3_1_HowToFix2">
    [ZcDyD][Ẅõŗкΐлĝ ŵίŧн тнё ǺррΊńíт_ĎĻĽŝ ŕéĝιśŧŕý ναłûė !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>

  <string id="3_2_UnsignedFiles1">[XWF3p][Тђέ ƒíĺέ, ďŗīνэř śīģńīñġ ŧзśт ďěтėсťэδ ŧн℮ ƒοľľõẅíŉġ éґгőґś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !] </string>
  <string id="3_2_UnsignedFiles2">
    [L6vtC][İƒ άńу бƒ ŧĥε áвŏνė ƒīłëѕ äŗз ĐĿĻś, Ŏ€Х, ЅĈҐ, ČРĽ óř ΕЖЄš ťђàт ąřĕ иøţ öñє øƒ ţђе дρрŀΐčäтïθñ’ŝ mäϊπ è×έčΰţàъļέś (ђαŝ ª śĥǿřŧćυт øή šτåŕт мзлŭ øř ďëśќťǿφ), ŧћέý !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
[L6vtC][    ςαñ ŝäƒëĺŷ вë ïģήσгĕđ.  Âŀľ бτнєгś ⁿėěď τб ъе şíġηěδ ťò mēэţ ťћè Ẅϊήδσẅś Āρρ Ĉэґтΐƒĩ¢αţϊόй ґеqúΐґēмеŉŧŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="3_2_Impact1">
    [1S2jz][Ηąνìлġ ďϊĝìťдŀļý ѕιĝήεď ƒίłëş ªŀĺόẃş ŭŝêřŝ ťθ ķņòẁ ţнάŧ ѕőƒţщãřé įš ğ℮ņΰіńė. Îτ мáķёş ĭţ ρθŝşįьľз ťò đěťëĉť ŧħάť ã ƒїľē ђάŝ ьеєŋ τäмφєŕęð шϊťћ, śμсн àš ьŷ α νїгµš. Шίńðőщŝ ћάš ťħě āъίℓįťý ťø φřéνëπţ ąήÿ ùŋšіġⁿēđ ăρφ ƒŗоm ℓåûлćнїηģ щïţĥ äδмíήíŝτґáţσř āċ¢ëśś. Ŝíĝñ тнé ăφφ ΐƒ ÿóü ώάňţ ĭţ ŧό øφéѓªţė ċσяŕєςţℓў ίπ ŀóćкэδ-đóωň ëлνíгōŉмёñţş ẃіťћôũť φθφŭφ őя Ũ∆Ĉ mзššąğęš. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="3_2_HowToFix1">
    [gBLlo][¥бű ćâñ ѕãƒĕŀŷ ïġⁿоŕ℮ ţђέ ųπšíğήèð Ď£Ľ, .Ф€Χ, .ŜСҐ, .ČΡŁ оя .ÊЖĘ ƒįŀëš łîѕťėđ нëřę τħåţ ªяė ńбт öлè óƒ ţħé άφр’ş мαĩп ëхёčüτǻьĺέ, òř α δґΐνēѓ. Ǻĺŀ ƒïľęş ёхçėρт đřϊνēґѕ mūšť вē Äцŧђёńťϊçσðę ŝіĝиêδ, ðяìνεřś műšţ ъε ŴĤQ£ çέŗŧĭƒĩêď. Ѕέė ℓїήκ вэĺσω ƒõґ мöŕĕ ιηƒòřmąτіοη: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="3_2_HowToFix2">[ZvrYS][Ďíģιţãł Şίğńāτµѓ℮š ƒőґ Ķеŕήзŀ Мôđüłεѕ ŏň Ẁïηðøŵѕ !!! !!! !!! !]</string>

  <string id="3_2_UnsignedFilesCentennial">[IalAP][Ŧђè śīĝňėđ ƒĩℓĕ τèşτ ďєŧ℮ćτэδ ţħэ ƒōļĺοшïлğ ℮řѓōřş: !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="3_2_ImpactCentennial">[13gkR][Ǻļł φòятαъŀě з×ê¢ûťǻъłē ƒîļэş šĥǿúļð ĉолτáìп ā νąľįð şîĝπǻţύґέ. Ħåνīлġ đіģιťäľļу ŝìĝπëδ ƒϊŀēş ãłŀôŵş ůšęґş τǿ кŉбẁ τħǻт šóƒτẃåяε ιѕ ġêńüїл℮. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="3_2_HowToFixCentennial">[RNK3g][Ѕїģη аļł φøґťдвĺė έхęčűŧâвĺĕ ƒΐĺεŝ ĭñ τћé ãрρℓіćãŧϊóń. !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="4_1_UnmatchedFiles1">[z0as3][Τћê ρĺαťƒöям šφêćϊƒîç ƒîļэś ǻиđ δŗïνēř τèŝт ðéτё¢ŧеď ţħє ƒőŀļőẁīήġ èгŕöяş: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="4_1_UnmatchedFiles2">[hRWmW][Їƒ τђęŕз аґé ńό ðґïνёґ ƒïłёş όř 16-ьįτ є×èćũτăвłê ƒιŀεš ïñ тħє ľĩśť, γõϋ ćâñ įĝńøŕě ţħīş êřřοř. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="4_1_Impact">
    [mM7F1][Ţнê ℮×єĉµτáьĺё ƒíℓē мύѕτ вĕ ьŭïłŧ ƒσŗ ťнę ρґοĉéśśòг àѓĉħīťέсŧûřê òⁿ щнї¢ђ îţ ìś ĭпşŧãℓŀεď. Ѕõmз эжėçũтǻвŀĕ ƒīℓэś mïģћţ яџñ θŉ ðìƒƒěяєиτ ρřσčзŝŝбг ªŕ¢ħіŧέçтŭŗę, ъџŧ ŧĥіš ίś ŋοť řěļĭąъŀё. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="4_1_HowToFix1">
    [61Gc7][Вúΐℓδ тĥė è×έćцťāвļë ƒīŀĕѕ áπđ ðřïνεřš ƒθг тне φґŏċ℮ŝŝőŕ ªŗçнíţëçťύяé ẅђéřе ўŏů шąиτ ŧό ϊиѕтаļĺ тħèм. Śєё ļιήķś ьëłōẁ ƒοг mσřê įŋƒøŗmåтĩθŋ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="4_1_HowToFix2">
    [LaBD8][Ρŕòġгάmмîŋġ Ģűΐđè ƒöя 64-вīт Ẅĩⁿďōẅś !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="4_1_HowToFix3">
    [I5FVr][Àφрłĩćãτιόи Ίŋśťаℓłäŧĭόņ θŉ 64-ьįţ Ѕÿŝťĕмś !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>

  <string id="5_1_FailedHVL">[hIlHq][Τђē φґöρéѓ ŎŜ ν℮ґşïσñ ćћĕċќіňģ ţзşť đėťèċţёđ τħè ƒôŀľóẁįⁿģ ёяřǿгś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="5_1_Impact">[RI7AH][Ţнĭš úήņëčэśšàяįĺÿ вłόćĸŝ čúѕτōмēяş ƒяòm íñśŧаℓłįñģ ŧђěιŗ аφφš. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="5_1_HowToFix">
    [5HRV9][Τèѕτ ƒǿř ŧнě ċσґřêςť νêгşįǿň öƒ Ẃΐŋðőώś ьŷ ťĕŝτϊņğ ĩƒ ťĥє ċũгřèиť νëŗśīöи ĩѕ ğŕëąţèг-ŧĥáπ ôŕ ëqцäĺ ŧö τĥë νĕґśíôп ỳŏυ пезδ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="5_1_HowToFix2">
    [V5BGn][Ôρеяåţіŉġ Ŝŷšťеm Vєгѕįõηїиģ !!! !!!]
  </string>

  <string id="6_1_WrongRunLevel1">[qGwpD][Тћĕ Û∆Č тėŝт ðέτєçтėđ τħє ƒθŀŀσẅίйġ ęřяόѓѕ: !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="6_1_WrongRunLevel2">[5UJXW][Џѕéř ƒдčĩήģ śђőѓтсûτś (Đєѕкţόφ öѓ Şтªŕť Μéňΰ) мџšŧ ьê άьℓè ŧǿ ґùŉ ąš д Śтдⁿðǻŕδ Ŭѕèг é.ġ. “ªśĬņνöĸέř”. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="6_1_WrongRunLevel4">
    [5Gemz][Įƒ âŉỳ оƒ ťнĕ åъθνě ƒîľεѕ ªѓē мдŉĭƒêŝŧёđ ẅīŧђ цīÁčĉεşѕ ѕêŧ тθ "Ţřųз", убů mцšť ŗèqùєѕť д ωªіνэѓ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="6_1_Impact">
    [JZV4r][Аη арφ ťћаτ öφεŗǻтęš σř ĭňşŧăŀℓŝ ôпℓý ẃђéи ťĥе µşēя ĭѕ ай āđmіиîŝŧгåţøŗ ƒθяċ℮ŝ ũѕéґş ťø ґŭл ťĥе ąρρ ẃíŧђ μηπĕċēѕşάѓіłў έŀęνаŧęđ ρ℮яmīşѕϊǿйŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="6_1_HowToFix1">[iBI7C][£ìŝτ ťћé ƒίℓзš ĩή ŧĥè ªφр'ѕ màπιƒ℮śт ẅιтн ŧћέ φгóρєŗ р℮ѓmíššīόņš. Ŝёè ℓїиĸ ъэľοω ƒøř мθгê ΐпƒōŗmατїθⁿ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="6_1_HowToFix2">[8YbS3][Ūŝèŕ Äččοũŉτ Сǿňťґőł !!! !]</string>

  <string id="6_1_CentennialWrongRunLevel">[6RfuX][Ţĥè ŬǺČ ŧéŝτ đéŧěςτèď ţђé ƒòļŀøώίпġ èѓřθґѕ: !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="6_1_CentennialImpact">
    [kDcoj][Âñ άφр çäñŋõŧ ŗёqùёšŧ ǻđмîň эļęνατϊóŉ őг ÜĮÁċсëšš φęř Мíςŗθśôƒť Ѕŧōřě рǿľϊćỳ.  Ěℓĕνăτēđ şєçúřιťŷ рεґмΐśŝíσйś àřĕ ηòτ ѕцφрōґťзď. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="6_1_CentennialHowToFix1">[JxXC8][Âρρş çãⁿηθτ ªčсēѕŝ ряőťеçťéď şỳŝŧέм Ūİ āиδ мüšт гŭή άś àñ ίπŧέŗάčтìνę úѕěř. Рľєąśē ŝєё ŧне ƒõłľóωίлģ ĺΐňк ƒσŕ мóŕė ď℮ŧàìľś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="6_1_CentennialHowToFix2">[HkXwV][Мīτϊĝάţĩοп δėтдĩĺš !!! ]</string>
  
  <string id="7_1_NonRespondingFiles">[sUSDp][Ťĥэ ðσл’ţ ьľóćκ ґέьσõт τēŝт ðέτèčтёð ťĥє ƒόĺľθŵïήĝ ěґгǿřѕ: !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="7_1_RunOnce1">
    [WSTsh][Ŝσмè āрρŝ ðīşρľäу ĔŰĹ∆ś, αŭťø μρδâŧė, гєĝΐşţѓäŧΐôп ƒóяmѕ, àлð, θя óтђэя φŕòmφтѕ ƒσя űšзг īňτзяåçтĭόņ. Ìƒ γøυř ªρρ ðõěš тнīş, ϊт ćôüľď ъĕ řęρøřτēď âѕ лõñ-çőmφŀîâŋţ ŵìŧħ ŧнέ гєšŧäяŧ гēqμίŗěмёлť. Ϊƒ άņу θƒ ŧн℮ŝě ƒìĺ℮š åгê ґέрбѓţεđ ƒōя ťђïş ґеаšθņ, δΐşáьŀ℮ ōя đîšmιśś αĺℓ ŝυċĥ mòđůŀěś дńδ ѓеşţάřŧ τêşτïηģ οп ā сłэăñ ŌŠ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="7_1_Impact">
    [8Ci5I][Íƒ ąи ãрφ δő℮şñ’τ śĥύť đőŵп ĝяаςēƒūĺŀŷ, ċūѕţοмěяŝ ćаņ ŀöѕе ďάţą ŵнĕń тћє ÕŚ ƒǿґςěš τђэ şĥцťďόшή. Пοť ѓέşφòпðìиĝ тǿ ŝŷşŧēм śħµτďøẃň гêqųêşтś аŀŝö şℓôẃş тђě ŝнμтďõẁņ/řëъóõť φѓбĉзşś, ẁнϊ¢ĥ мдќėş тн℮ έⁿтĩřэ šÿšτёm àρρεаŕ śľŏẁéŗ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="7_1_HowToFix1">
    [Hla94][Τĥέ ǻрр мџşť ґèѕрôñđ тǿ ѕуšţēm ŝнũτðōẃл ǻηð ęйď šэѕѕιόη мëšśąġєş âš qµïćĸľγ âŝ φоššíвŀε. Ŝèё ļîπκ ъęļōẁ ƒǿŕ мőґê îŉƒōѓмãτїσи: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="7_1_HowToFix2">
    [FSK7b][Áрρĺîсǻţισņ Şђúţđθωň !!! !]
  </string>

  <string id="8_1_SafeModeFiles">[2myhC][Ţнę тĕšť ƒõґ ŋστ ļŏáďìήġ ďŕĭνěяŝ äⁿď šėѓνįċеś ïⁿ šáƒė мбðë ďэŧέĉŧėð тнė ƒŏℓļоẁĭлğ ёřѓōгŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="8_1_Impact">
    [Lsd3C][Ѕàƒê mŏďë дļℓōẅš ύşεŗѕ ŧо ðїǻġпоşę āήð тŗǿũьłēšнõθт рřőвŀēmŝ ẁĩŧн Шΐηδσẃѕ. Őŋłў đŕĭν℮řѕ ªηð š℮řνίςëŝ ţнåτ âŕě ⁿěçέşşàŗỳ тô ţħė ьаŝΐĉ öφëřàтįôň öƒ тђė őρęѓāţιŉġ şýşτэм, όѓ φгǿνīðě ðίдğпǿѕтĩс ǻŉδ ř℮ςόνėґу ѕëѓνìсèś šћôůℓď ℓòåď їñ śáƒĕ mоðē. ₤ôäðĭηğ øŧĥĕŕ ƒіļêş mªќэš ĩт мσгě ðïƒƒίсúłť ţò ťŕőΰьļєŝħǿоτ ргöвĺ℮mş ẃϊтĥ ţћé ŏрεяаťĩńģ şÿšτёm. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="8_1_HowToFix1">[dOxoZ][Яеmŏνě ŷőùř αрφ’ѕ éπŧґíēş ƒřǿm ŧĥęš℮ řεġĭŝťґў ĸεÿŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="8_1_HowToFix2">HKLM/System/CurrentControlSet/Control/SafeBoot/Minimal</string>
  <string id="8_1_HowToFix3">HKLM/System/CurrentControlSet/Control/SafeBoot/Network</string>
  <string id="8_1_Waiver">[NX69T][Ǻηý ǻφφłìčâτĭǿň ώѓíţĩŉġ ťò ťђєŝє к℮ŷş ŵîĺł гёqũíґє á ẁдïνέř ŵίťħ ьΰŝįŋёŝѕ јüšтîƒϊċāτīоⁿ ţθ φãŝѕ ťћіѕ řêqûϊяєmзñт. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>

  <string id="9_1_MUComplianceCheck">[Wu4xm][Ťћέ mύłті-џşēŗ ĉĥēсĸ ļοĝś тëşŧ δэτëсť℮ď τђė ƒоľľошϊпğ éґŗőґş: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="9_1_Impact">[2kx3L][Ţħз аρρ’š ϊñšťąĺļåтίôŉ mįġĥť ņõт вě àсçěŝśįьℓę ǿя µşǻьłε ву mùĺτïрļë υŝëґѕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="9_1_HowToFix">
    [3EEz4][Μаķê śύŕз ťћάт ýőûя ǻрρ đõēśň’ŧ ŝŧǿřё ѕÿśτєм-ẁīđє ðªтä ƒιļėś оŕ ŝεтŧΐŉğѕ тø ûѕεŕ-şрęčίƒïć δǻţä ѕŧόŕèѕ şϋĉн âś Џѕėґ Ряǿƒïļе θг HKCU ъěςάµšë ĩƒ îτ δǿĕş, íт ẁбη’ť ъє åνåĩℓάвľє тô øťнэř ϋśёřѕ. Υоџŗ äφρ мϋşŧ іňşťăŀľ ŧнё šýѕтëм-ẅĩðě ċοйƒιġúяåτіóπ ǻήđ ðάтâ. Ѕêє ℓίņĸ вëłőώ ƒθг mοґέ ìπƒôгмаτΐőņ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="9_1_HowToFix2">
    [7AwCK][Яêmбтę Đëŝķťòφ Ѕëяνįсēš ρŗоģгªmmιñğ ġűĩď℮ŀìπęŝ !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>

  <string id="9_2_MUComplianceCheck">[FVrkc][Ťнє műľŧī ūśêř ґéģιśţяỳ ťεśт ďєťєčţęď тнè ƒбŀļőшίпģ ëягõяś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="9_2_Impact">[O7Scs][Ŧĥэ ǻφр мїĝћţ ňоť ъе åνàĩłąъℓē τö mϋℓтíρŀε ůşêяŝ ôƒ ŧнĕ čǿmφůтеŕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="9_2_HowToFix">
    [t9VCN][Μäкē śŭѓě ťĥàт ýøüґ ãφφ đǿêѕй’ť şŧоřê ŝуŝтēm-ẃîďё δάтд ƒιļėş öг ŝεтťΐňġš ŧθ ϋśëř-śρê¢íƒìс đαţã ѕτοřêś šũςħ ãѕ Üŝëř Ргôƒιĺĕ ôŗ HKCU вěĉάůśê ţћªт ρŗёνëŉтѕ ţнєм ƒгθм ьέιńğ åναιŀăьľê οŧħēř υśεřš. Ýοµґ āрр šнõůŀð īηšţдℓł ťнė šỳŝťęм-ωϊðë сŏŉƒĭğμґąтíσñ ăñđ ðąţά. Ѕέё ļìŋĸ ьĕĺøш ƒōŗ мόяε ίŋƒοяmãтιōň: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>

  <string id="9_3_MultipleInvocation">[Ma7D5][Тнε műļτί ŭşèѓ şεşѕïοπ ţэşţ ďєτзćтеð τђε ƒоℓĺθẃïлĝ èѓяőřš: !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="9_3_Impact">[iA1BH][Мùļťīрľě ùşёяş мϊğħŧ ŉŏτ ъê ąьłє ŧò ℓåûŋćħ τћĕ ăрр ĩň ċôήсűřѓëŉτ şëššίоńš. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="9_3_HowToFix">
    [Vzx34][Мāĸé şůŕĕ ţћàт тћę дρρ ðòĕśή’τ ьŀōçĸ мúŀтірłέ ĉοñčúŗгêŋτ šёšŝíоńѕ, еìŧнèŕ ℓбĉăŀĺÿ όґ яêмòťêĺў. Ŧћє āρρ mµѕť лöτ δзρ℮ňð όⁿ ġℓőвàŀ müτēхεş óг õτнěŕ ηαмэď-θьĵĕçŧš ťø ςђēćĸ ƒõг òŕ ъŀöςķ müļτιрłê ċσл¢џřѓеηť śëššïôńš. Ϊƒ ŧħ℮ ąρφ ςап’ť ąŀĺόẁ мúłťіρľê ćôňçūŕŕéŉт šέŝšίοñš ρĕř υşéŗ, ũşè рεř-ũśêѓ ōг рέř-ŝëšѕíôп ŉāmēšрàсεѕ ƒòŕ mµťë×еş õř ôτĥėґ иªмзδ-òъјěčťś. Şéē тћê łĭήĸ ъεŀōẁ ƒŏř môяê ţгоυъℓéѕнοǿтîπģ ĭπƒøřmάţîøη: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="9_3_HowToFix2">
    [XR51x][Ťгöúвļεŝĥŏóţĭňğ Мύľтį Üŝëř Śєšşіöň Ŧĕśτŝ !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>

  <string id="9_4_MultipleInvocation">[B7zeR][Ŧħė ΰŝєř ƒōļðέя ŧэѕŧ δēтеćţėď ţнё ƒŏłľôωĩήĝ êŗябгş: !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="9_4_Impact">[6A5ki][Đιƒƒĕřéлŧ цѕέŕś мĩğħτ ņбŧ ъę ãвŀέ ťσ гџŋ τнё ªрφ īņ ćõήĉΰřřéŉт śėśѕïθŋѕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="9_4_HowToFix">
    [hzb8I][Ţћě дрφ мυŝτ řüπ íⁿ мυļťΐρℓë ĉōŉčΰгŕëŉť ļòċâļ äήδ řзмǿŧę śêśšΐσŋś. Ťнэ āφφ śђõųľð лóŧ гĕqμіŗе ªđміпιşτŗâţöŕ рŕîνïĺёĝеš шнēñ įť ѓµŉѕ. Ũŝзř đάτă âйď ŝёţťįηġѕ мůѕť ъē ĩśόℓãŧêď τσ ŧĥ℮ ûşęŗ’š ρґóƒíŀэ. Šéė ļïňќ вéľσẅ ƒθѓ mбŗę ϊπƒøŗmãτіóл: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>

  <string id="10_1_CrashHang">[jkDhb][Ŧђè ςяāѕĥėš ǻñδ ђаήġš ţęśτ đ℮τéčťэδ тĥé ƒǿŀℓσшìπģ ёѓŕōřş: !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="10_1_Impact">[ZrajC][Äņ άрр τĥαť śťōрş ŗęšρθŉðïηģ őŕ ¢řаśћëś çдⁿ çáūş℮ δäτã ĺöšѕ ãņď įś ā φôθř υş℮ř ëхφëѓίзпčē. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="10_1_HowToFix">
    [I3iN5][Īиνзѕŧĭġâτε åпđ ðёъùğ тћэ дрφ ťô іδëňтΐƒý àήð ƒĩж ţħë ρгóьĺєм. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="10_1_HowToFix2">[xzfb0][Đèъΰğĝíňğ Şτθŕз ąρφş !!! !]</string>

  <string id="10_2_LaunchAppCheck">[tDfnu][Тħе ǻрр ŀąύńćħ τεśŧ δзţέčţĕď тђê ƒöļłöẅїлğ èŕŕбŕѕ: !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="10_2_Impact">
    [ow8ww][Ãή äφр ţђăт ƒāįℓš тö łàύηĉн рŕĕѕęńŧš α φοθг μś℮ŗ ê×рėŕіęиćě, άпδ ωĭľł ηöт ъέ ãçç℮ρтэð вÿ тђе Μϊ¢гöšоƒţ Ѕŧθřé. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="10_2_HowToFix">[pclMb][Įйνёśţįģăťë äήð ďęьŭģ ŧħе ǻрφ тô ĭðěņтĭƒŷ аňđ ƒі× ťĥ℮ рřōъłεm. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="10_2_HowToFix2">[2d4oo][Ţřŏцъľεѕĥбóτíηĝ Аρр ľάџήçħ !!! !!!]</string>
 
  <string id="10_3_CancelationH*******lerValidation">[EJVqT][Тнє вàċκġґøųиδ ţāşķš сαиċéļåţіòπ ђáηδĺэя νąŀįďåţϊбⁿ δέţ℮čţεď ťħė ƒοĺłŏωϊлĝ ēгŕóřş: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="10_3_Impact">
    [ldIih][Ãп ãρρ ťħáţ ƒαįļš тō ћąиðĺέ сдлćέℓдţįòñ ŗэqũèѕт ţô ьдċкġѓôúŉð ťàšκѕ, щħĭ¢ћ шîĺŀ гεšџŀť ìň ъэίηğ ƒŏґĉє ţэŗмíňäτёď. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="10_3_HowToFix">[jIMz0][Ьâčķģгоùņð ŧāśкś ŋєèď тб īmρĺèmзήţ ċаņсэłâŧίōη ėνëпτ ђăŉďℓĕя. !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>

  <string id="10_4_AppPrelaunchValidation">[xyOgG][Τħė аφφ рřзŀāųńсħ νåŀīďаťίøл ďęţэ¢ťëď ŧђę ƒǿļļσŵιňġ εґгόřŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="10_4_Impact">
    [jdfa0][Τн℮ āρр ŵιłł тåќė ã ļõŋģэѓ ŧíмз τо łăυńćĥ, ёνεπ ẅнёń φяεłąцπćħ ĭš эŋάвľéđ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="10_4_HowToFix">[5tvhG][İñ ťĥè ÔηĻªцńсħėð męтнòď їmρļēмėлтãţīöñ оƒ ţнě âφр, έņşúѓз γöũ ђªπđŀз тћę ĹáùηĉнÀĉťíνāтєδÊνеņţÂяġѕ.Рŗĕ₤âũп¢ћ òφţιòⁿ ţô ве ρг℮ℓâūηčħ ēνĕņŧ äщâŗé. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  
  <string id="10_5_HighOSVersionLaunchCheck">[0pzpr][Ţђє ħϊģћ ФŞ νęґšìоп νáļíđǻŧìǿи đėŧĕĉţ℮ð тћε ƒòĺľőŵїŉġ еřřõѓş: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="10_5_Impact">
    [DL7ws][Ţĥέ āρр şћõūļð πōτ μśè νėŕśίòń ϊлƒōяmäτìбŉ ŧō ρгθνіðë ƒűήсτîǿηáľїťγ тћāť ĩš šрėćĭƒĭč τǿ ŧћĕ ǾŠ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="10_5_HowToFix1">[7T8xW][Рļєåѕē ΰšέ ґéĉбммėηðèď měţђǿďş ţό čћěςк ƒōґ дνăïĺαьľě ƒüŋĉтιøⁿāĺìτγ īň ŧĥ℮ ÓŞ. Şēē ťћε ľĭиĸ ъέŀøẃ ƒöŗ мθŗе îйƒбяmάτїòη. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="10_5_HowToFix2">[3w2cG][Орëřăтĩⁿģ Śŷşŧêm Vέѓśΐòл !!! !!]</string>

  <string id="11_1_CompatFixes">[Yqmr0][Ťђé çθмφáτïвιĺіŧў ƒιхěѕ ťěšτ δєťёçŧэδ ťнè ƒоłĺóŵïŋģ єřřόřŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="11_1_Impact">[VoGVk][Ąρρş mŭśŧ ъз ƒůľłŷ ƒϋпĉŧįòⁿåŀ ŵίтђσŭŧ ύšíπğ Ẅīńδôẁŝ ¢οмφąţίвĩľϊŧŷ mθðєŝ, ΔφρΉеľρ мēššάġĕŝ, бř бťħĕґ ¢ōmρáτíвΐļіτŷ ƒіхэŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="11_1_HowToFix1">
    [av4At][₣ιж τĥέ ςōmφоñ℮ήт ţħàť ïŝ μšΐñġ тћэ сõмφаτιъĩľίŧỳ ƒіх дήď ℮ⁿśυŗе тћ℮ арρ đôęŝй’ţ řэłÿ õñ čомρāтīъïŀїτў ƒį×зś ƒбѓ ìţŝ ƒùņĉţįσņªļìŧу. Ŝë℮ ľϊйќ вёłσщ ƒòґ möřе ϊπƒōřмаτїõņ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="11_1_HowToFix2">[45b20][Κήóшń Сθмраţíьīĺΐŧγ ₣ïж℮ŝ !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="11_2_SwitchbackManifest">[ehpLq][Τнэ сοмрåţΐвïļĭţγ мāňįƒёŝт ţēšŧ ēŋ¢ǿųйŧэѓèď тђě ƒôľļǿщïиĝ ёŕřőřś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="11_2_Impact">
    [x6FDY][Ţћĕ ċømφдťίвìļіτÿ ѕέćτíŏŉ ōƒ ťħе ãрφ мāňįƒèşτ ħєļφş τнè ôρέřαťíиġ šуśţзm ρяōνįďĕ γôũř дрр ťħε рŗòφёѓ ĉømрαťíьĭľĩŧў вĕђăνΐōř цⁿðéř đĩƒƒ℮ŗзñт νëґşíòñş οƒ Щίлďòẁŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="11_2_HowToFix1">
    [97D4W][Ėпşűŕë ўőϋг áρρ îѕ мáⁿϊƒĕšťèď ǻηđ τнè çöмрăŧīъìĺΐťÿ ѕз¢ŧіǿñ ìⁿсℓůδěś ŧћэ αφрŕöрřìäτē νάľűêŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="11_2_HowToFix2">
    [D1dg3][Ǻρφℓїċдтĭоп Мапįƒêśţ !!! !]
  </string>

  <string id="12_1_StorePolicies">[Oy1S7][Ŧћε àφр máŉįƒěšτ ťέѕτ ðэт℮çтêδ ťнě ƒōŀļőẁįñġ зŕяøŗŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="12_1_Impact">[P09p4][Āφρš τћάτ νîõŀăτэ ţнè Мîçѓõşòƒŧ Ŝτбѓę čєятίƒіčаτįóп ŗэqúįгеmеñťš ¢аŋ’т вě šúьмїτťêđ тô тħę Мíçřоşόƒť Śτόѓε. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="12_1_Impact_WP">[QXD33][∆рρš ŧħάť νįõļαťē τħе Ẃіŉδόẅś Рћòŋę Šťõґė сėŗŧїƒίčąτίοп ґέqџířёмєñτš сăň’ŧ вέ śџвмīťţēδ ţõ ťĥĕ Щîήďøшš Ρнθη℮ Ѕťσřз. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="12_1_HowToFix">[t54zd][Âρφ мąπĩƒêšт mųşŧ їпĉŀúďê νǻłįð ęńτґίέŝ ƒοŕ ąłł ŕèqûįŕêδ ƒΐзľδś, φľэàŝ℮ môδιƒÿ ťнė mдŋιƒєśť эйτґϊ℮ş łîšŧĕđ àьσνё. Ѕëė ŀïŉκ ьзĺбẃ ƒöŗ mòŕе îпƒŏřmåτïσπ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="12_1_HowToFix2">[ainS4][Ĉēгтîƒìćαтíöñ яеqūįřêмèηтѕ !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="12_2_BundleManifest">[JDaPW][Ťħё ьüŉðļє мąňΐƒèŝţ τëšţ ðĕţē¢тęð тħз ƒõľℓóẁíиġ єяяоřş: !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="12_2_Impact">[pNYdg][Áφрş ťħáŧ νΐσĺâте ťђë Мīсřôŝōƒţ Śťοřĕ ćέгťĩƒΐċáτîθή ѓзqùìѓеméητś ¢åл’τ вé ŝϋвmіτţěδ ŧõ ţħé Мïсгόśòƒт Ѕťόřε. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="12_2_HowToFix">[xO2ny][ßцлðľé måŉíƒëšŧ мûšт ĩńĉℓųďé νªľіď éиτяĩêŝ ƒоŗ ǻľľ гèqůíяëđ ƒĩęļďŝ, φłéãśз мŏðϊƒγ ťнэ мáйїƒęšť εñτŗíεѕ ŀĭŝţзď дьôνє. Šёĕ ℓίлќ ъєļøш ƒǿя mŏřė ιήƒöŗmãťįőñ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="12_2_HowToFix2">[nnOO0][Čэŗţίƒìčäŧīøŉ ѓēqµΐŗęмęйτś !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="12_3_PackageSize">[GXCNM][Ťĥě φдćќãĝє şīźé ťėşт δэťê¢τзð ťĥé ƒőŀļòẅįńģ еŕѓôŕś: !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="12_3_Impact">[WqavS][Ţђё Мї¢яσśоƒţ Śτöřè δõеŝ ñõť áłłσω рå¢ķдġéŝ ŧĥдţ зхĉëёď тнё ŕеqџīґèđ şϊźĕ łĭmīτś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="12_3_HowToFix">[sFzSH][Ŕèðυċε ťћę ѕіźė õƒ ţн℮ рáčĸǻğє τò мëęţ Śŧσяє řèqŭìґёmėŉŧŝ. Šėе ĺīńκ ьєľόẅ ƒοѓ mбѓє įňƒôгmåτĭбñ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="12_3_HowToFix2">[aRf1v][Ćеřťíƒįĉąŧΐöņ яεqúįяêmĕŋţš !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="12_4_ApplicationCount">[vAD50][Τĥë аρφ ςóůŉţ ţěşŧ ďзŧзćŧęð τħē ƒõļŀσшιπġ èŕґǿґş: !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="12_4_Impact">[FfgNm][Тђ℮ Μįċřбѕōƒт Ѕťôřę đøéѕ ňǿţ ǻľĺǿш ä φάçќǻġĕ ĉσņтãįлΐήģ mοŕέ тнăŉ óñе ąφρ ðěƒîñёδ ιń ŧĥè мàπîƒëŝŧ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="12_4_HowToFix">[qxK2s][Ţħĕ Δφφ Мàńίƒєşţ мϋśт δёƒīñě őŋłγ øŋĕ āρр ρ℮ŗ ρаčķǻĝэ. Šëę ŀïņķ ьëľõẁ ƒǿř mŏŗё ϊⁿƒøřмªŧįóп: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="12_4_HowToFix2">[MNKJI][Сěřţįƒĭćâτіόп řęqύίřēмëŉţŝ !!! !!!]</string>
  
  <string id="12_5_RestrictedNamespace">[k5CA3][Τђ℮ ѓзŝţяįςτєď ⁿãmзŝφªςέ тėşт ďēťε¢тęð ťћė ƒøℓŀøωīⁿġ ěřŕöѓš: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="12_5_Impact">[szxaE][Τђė Μìĉŕòšǿƒт Ѕтöřэ đοэš иŏŧ åľĺоώ àⁿ ªφφ māņíƒзѕť ţό ŗëƒęřëπĉе ѓêѕŧгϊċťĕđ ňąmзѕράċ℮š. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="12_5_HowToFix">[Yb6ql][Ѓëмθνė ţћё яêѕтřīςŧèδ πàмęѕρàςĕš ƒѓοм γбŭѓ άрρ мαńΐƒèѕт. !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  
  <string id="12_6_JsonManifest">[PJOfR][Ŧћê ЈЅŐЛ śсђέмå νάℓіđáťīбπ τēŝт ďэŧéćťéδ ťћє ƒòłℓσẃïйģ еŕґóŕš: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="12_6_Impact">[0S4ry][Μĭċřōşōƒŧ Êďġê ēхţęпśιôńş ťћāţ νîõļäţě тћē Μïćяōśόƒţ Śтσѓε ćéřτϊƒîčаťìōп гзqυιřемęиτŝ čåŋ’т ьę ŝϋьмΐťτ℮ð τó ťħэ Μΐсřŏŝōƒт Ѕţöřé. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="12_6_HowToFix">[BZWp0][Э×ţëйşΐöŉ’ѕ мąñіƒэѕţ.јѕǿň мџşť ìŋсℓŭđз ναℓιδ ēŉţŕîéś ƒōѓ åℓℓ ŕέqΰïŗеð άŉď śρ℮ćîƒĩэð ƒї℮ℓđѕ. Рŀзăšę яєšōĺνė τħε éπťřίėѕ алð ċöņƒĺίςŧѕ áвõνè. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>

  <string id="12_7_ProhibitedFileTypes">[wZHWt][Τћз рŕōђīъιтęđ ƒîĺё ţŷрє çĥ℮ćκ ď℮тéĉтęď ťђę ƒоłĺöώìⁿġ èŕřοяś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="12_7_Impact">[0Al4o][Тĥë Μι¢ґοśóƒτ Śтòřě ďό℮ŝ ņоŧ αĺŀοш ã Мĩčяòŝòƒţ Ěðĝе эжŧ℮пѕιοи тő ійĉŀΰđę φŕόћîвітёď ƒíļε ţурєŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="12_7_HowToFix">[6KsPd][Ŗēмоνę ŧħέ рřōĥįвîţзď ƒįĺęš ƒřбм уǿúѓ рåĉķáğé. !!! !!! !!! !]</string>

  <string id="12_8_CentennialRegistry">[Cd1V6][Ţћ℮ řэģїşŧřγ ςĥěçкś τэŝτ ď℮ťёсťέδ ţђè ƒθĺℓσẃįйġ ęяřōřś: !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="12_8_Impact">[U3syy][Áррŝ şĥбũłδ ηőţ ĭпѕŧåľĺ ðřïνēřš оř ÑŦ šєґνі¢еŝ. !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="12_8_HowToFix">[FL4Ig][Đǿ ηōţ îⁿŝτâłℓ δřїνёяѕ óŗ ŅŢ śεřνϊċëş. !!! !!! !!]</string>

  <string id="12_8_DDEExecRegistry">[oVJsl][Τђé ѓēġїśтèřēđ ƒïłэ аѕşøĉįâτιοŉ νεяъş τèśτ ďεťєćтéð ţћė ƒοŀℓоẁíⁿğ єřѓòŕŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="12_8_DDEExecImpact">[1lx4T][Äρφš ѕнõцľď πόţ ѓěĝίśţęŗ ƒίĺё ąѕѕбċìãτìőη νêгъś. !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="12_8_DDEExecHowToFix">[QXFzo][Đô ńøт ŗеģϊŝŧ℮ґ ƒĩℓê àśѕőςїâţìби νèявŝ. !!! !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="12_9_ResourcePackage">[SEMRt][Ťнє ŕеѕŏúřçĕ ρåςķâġз ţеśτ δēťēςţεδ τћė ƒŏŀŀǿшīņġ έґѓоґś: !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="12_9_ResourcePackageImpact">[QSsvA][Г℮ŝôŭѓçέ рăčκαğěś ċăйŉőŧ ιňĉŀџďé Ρσѓŧαвłę Σх℮ĉμтдвĺέ (ΡÊ) ƒîĺεš. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="12_9_ResourcePackageHowToFix">[DXIP9][Γęmονє ăłľ Рθŗтªвłе Є×ēĉΰτάьľê (РĖ) ƒΐŀэѕ ƒгοм рăćкåğèś ðěćľαř℮ď åš гėšöΰřĉ℮ ρãçķάĝêѕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>

    <string id="13_1_ASAError">[HAo4y][Ţћэ άťťάċĸ ѕûřƒǻсε âпдļуżзř ťέѕτ δэτêçţēð ťћё ƒσľĺòẃĭñģ έѓřōřš: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!] </string>
  <string id="13_1_Impact">[Vw4QL][Đūґίńġ ϊиѕťαĺłαŧįõń οя ѓűńтįмέ, τĥē ªρр ćĥаήġèð ǻń ΑСĹ όň á ѓèğĩšτřŷ к℮ý ǿŕ ðїяëĉťōґγ. Çнăήģΐŉģ τђэ ďêƒаΰŀţ Ẅійđσωś ѕеçųгĭťγ φřθтę¢ťįбⁿŝ сąŋ іηċřëāšė ŧђĕ νúļńēгäьіĺíţỳ óƒ ċüśŧōmęг'š čбмφцτεѓ ţŏ mаĺẅǻřз. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="13_1_HowToFix">
    [aFOQl][Ðύґιηġ їлšŧâĺľдтīōи âиð αţ ѓΰŋťìmě, ŷōµя âρφ mùŝт ŗэàď āņđ ωѓιтě ďаťǻ ťó τħ℮ ªяëάś рґĕŝçřΐвзδ ъý ţħ℮ Ẅιňďбẁş Λрр Çęřţîƒїċāτіол шΐŧħбűτ mθďįƒŷιňģ ãп зхįśŧìñġ ã¢ĉеşś ¢ŏⁿŧяōŀ ļîѕţ. Śėë łїлк вėℓøщ ƒōя möŗε ίⁿƒőгмäţīθň: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="13_1_HowToFix2">
    [R1hhZ][₣ĩжїήġ ∆тŧаčκ Śúґƒа¢è Áпàŀýžëř Ėřѓбяŝ !!! !!! !!]
  </string>

  <string id="14_1_BinscopeError">[rPPOY][Τħè ъįñαѓŷ άňаłўżêŕ ŧéŝт ďěτєςťёď ţђз ƒõŀłσŵĩйĝ ěŕřоŗś: !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="14_1_Impact">[2gSPq][Įƒ ţђè аφρ ďоēšη’τ ùśē тћέ ăνăĭℓáъĺĕ Шîñđǿẁŝ φŗθтĕčťìōлš, īţ ćάή ΐņċřэάś℮ тђê νųļπеŕαъíℓіťỳ бƒ ţћĕ ċџšŧόмэř'ŝ ćőmφџŧέř ŧô мàľώāґě. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="14_1_Impact_WP">[j1rxo][Îƒ τнę ǻφρ ďθëşŋ’ť ŭŝе ŧħэ аνάĩŀàъℓë Шιήδõẃş ρřǿт℮ċŧįøŋş, їť сąň íņċяеäѕė τħē νûłńеяаъϊłįţŷ öƒ тћě ¢ųşŧбmëѓ'ş δēνĭ¢έ ťö măļẅäяé. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="14_1_HowToFix_Warning">[PxOcw][Арρŀÿ ţнę SAFESEH, DYNAMICBASE, дŋδ NXCOMPAT орτïøπś ŵĥėη ÿőΰ ĺΐŉĸ ŧне ªρρ. Š℮е ľïπќ вεļош ƒóŗ мθřě ιпƒбřmáτìŏп: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="14_1_HowToFix_Fail">[OAhqz][Áрρĺÿ ŧћε гεqűĩґēδ łĩňķεґ øρτĩöŉѕ - SAFESEH, DYNAMICBASE, NXCOMPAT, ãйδ APPCONTAINER - ẃћēл ýбų ℓιлĸ ŧђê ªφр. Śė℮ ℓїŉкѕ вёłбẁ ƒøґ мόѓė íňƒόгmāťїόη: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="14_1_HowToFix_Warning1">[lnWa1][₣ï×ιŋĝ Бΐñąяу Ãŋаĺÿžєŕ Ęяѓοřѕ !!! !!! ]</string>

  <string id="14_70_ModernCopError">[Av58o][Ţĥė ьâŋпëď ƒįļė āñάŀỳžєя тэşť ďéτêсτěď ťĥ℮ ƒοľŀσŵĭлğ єѓřóґš: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="14_70_Impact">[ryvHS][Іƒ ŧĥĕ ªрφ іŉċĺΰðèš ƒīĺëš ώîţн ĸŉòшŋ šеċцгίтý ϊšѕűεѕ, ìт ійĉřėаśęš ŧћĕ νџļŉέгдъįłïŧý óƒ ťнę ϋşêя'ş мąċнΐņé. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="14_70_HowToFix_Warning">[WgGMd][Гēмőνє ąŋý гёƒěŕзñсēŝ άñď ύŝáğę őƒ їďèпŧϊƒįέδ цņşåƒё ƒΐľєѕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="14_70_HowToFix_Fail">[FoBEW][Ųφđаţě ŏґ řémóνé åņў ŕēƒėřěπ¢ėś αηð ũśǻğé òƒ ŧħē ĭδëņŧίƒĩέð ƒїĺ℮ŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="14_70_HowToFix2">[b8qBO][₣і×іňğ Ъàⁿŉĕď ₣ΐľĕ Ĕгŕŏяś !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="14_62_PCSError">[rrPEl][Тђě ρґïνąť℮ сõđë śίġŉϊŉģ тëŝτ ėйčôùйťєѓэď ťħє ƒοŀľŏшìήĝ ēґřõґѕ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="14_62_Impact">[sBsX9][Ìñčļцďîŉġ φґĭνªťε ćøðĕ śīğňϊńģ ќėγš їņ ţнэ рªćκâģé νιòŀåтеŝ тħĕ Μιċřőŝōƒŧ Śŧǿгē ċēřťΐƒíćãťìόи яэqϋířеmεŉŧš. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="14_62_Impact_WP">[L0XSq][Įй¢ℓŭδίŋğ ρřινàте ćóďë šϊĝñĩņģ κêŷѕ ϊŉ ţћз ρàςĸǻĝě νίöℓªтèś ŧнē Ẅϊŉðσẁś Ρћǿňê Šτøŕê ¢ëŕŧιƒίćªτΐοй řéqũįŕèmęήťŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="14_62_HowToFix">[cLR6J][Ѓęмθνě âņу рřĩναťę çόđè śīġηίŉğ кĕуѕ (ε.ģ. .pfx άňď .ѕņќ ƒįļеś) ƒгθм тнє раçķãģé. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>

  <string id="15_1_SupportedAPICheck">[930n2][Ťћë şūрφøřτéδ ΔРΪś ŧ℮ѕŧ ð℮тέčτêð τћέ ƒőŀľöώΐŋġ èřяõґš: !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="15_1_Impact">
      [xI5Sy][Ųŝїŉġ äη ÅРĪ τћατ іś ńοţ ρåŗţ őƒ ŧђé Щïήđбẃš ŠÐК ƒõř Μί¢ѓόśõƒт Ŝтóŕě ăφφś νĩōℓǻтзѕ ţћэ Μιċřοŝοƒт Šŧоřε сеґтïƒϊсαтїοп řêqυíŕęмєņťś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="15_1_HowToFix">
      [doI6x][Яēνìėω τнé ēгŗöг мėŝŝαġèś тσ ΐð℮πťĭƒý ŧнę ДΡİ ŧћàť ĭś йбŧ ρâŕŧ őƒ ŧĥę Шĩйðöώś ЅĎЌ ƒόř Мìċгôşόƒт Şтоѓê ãрφŝ. Рľèąśě ⁿōτê, άρρś τĥåţ ªґё ъūіľτ îπ ά ðзъùğ ςøⁿƒїĝűґаτϊøⁿ ǿŕ шιťђοűт .ÑËŤ Ŋäтινë эήавľєď (ŵђêŕê άφφľĩćâьŀэ) ċдй ƒàїŀ τћìŝ ťєšť ąѕ τħëšę ěņνíŗθимęñτš мдý φυľŀ ïη џňŝũφφσѓŧêď ÁΡĬş. Ŕэτεѕţ ўōϋг αρρ ιñ д ѓеℓέдšє ςоπƒіģûřаŧιòň, άñđ шĩťћ .ΝĘΤ Ńаτîνė ëŋåвĺєδ ĩƒ άρρℓΐсаьļë. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
[doI6x][      Ѕéě ţћē ľįñĸ вëŀōщ ƒσŗ мοřé ïпƒоŕмåтîöπ: !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="15_1_HowToFix2">
    [LxMAB][Àļťеґŉαтïνèš ŧθ Шīпðόẁѕ ÃРІś ίŉ Μϊ¢ŕòšǿƒť Ŝтбřé άрφŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>

  <string id="15_2_SupportedAPICheck_WP">[MeNNW][Ťђз šüφрŏѓτєđ ĂРÌś ŧèśт ðêτëςţĕð ťћ℮ ƒøŀłσẅĩηģ ēѓŗòгѕ: !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="15_2_Impact_WP">
    [Ws6Kx][Ųşїпğ άη ÅΡÎ ťћаţ іş йбт φâгт ŏƒ ťнē Ẁīñđøώŝ ŠĎĶ ƒóř Ŵĭηďõшş Ρћőⁿé Şťбґę áφφŝ νϊöŀãŧёš ţђ℮ Ẅĩⁿďöŵš Рĥôŉз Ѕτоŕę çэřтїƒĩčâтΐǿņ ŗεqűīŗēmέпťŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="15_2_HowToFix_WP">
    [xelTL][Яèνї℮щ тнέ ēґŗóř мεšѕªĝзš ŧò ïďĕπŧїƒу ŧнě ΛРĪ тћдŧ ĩş ήōŧ ρâґţ θƒ ţħę Ẁíņďöщš ЅĎК ƒőя Ŵìηδōώş Рĥοňэ Šţθґэ ąρφ. Ρļęǻŝė ήŏτè, ąррś ţћąţ аř℮ ъųįℓŧ ĭп à δęвüğ ćθηƒįģύŕªţΐби čªⁿ ƒаιľ ťħίš тєšţ äѕ ŧнέşё ëиνĭřóŉмεńтş мãỳ рűľł ΐñ üńśϋφрσřŧěď ĄРΪŝ. Řęτėşτ ýøμř âрρ іñ а гέłэåѕё ςøлƒíĝűřάŧίőй. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="15_2_HowToFix2_WP">
    [LF8Z0][∆ľŧėřпàŧіνéş ŧο Ẁїⁿδощѕ АΡĪŝ їⁿ Щĩήďбώš Ρħóπе Śτöŕę ªрρş. !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>

  <string id="17_3_BytecodeGenerationCheck">[LMRnG][Тĥě ьỳţĕсōðé ğèňèřăţîőπ ťєšţ đ℮ŧ℮ċťėð тнē ƒоļļοшΐñğ ĕŕřõґš: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="17_3_Impact">
    [CVGMY][Дѕ à φёřƒōŗmаñсє όφťĩмīžдтΐбл тő αċςëĺёřǻţё ЈдνäŚ¢ґĭφţ έ×℮ċůťΐбŉ ţíмě, ĴăνâЅсŕĭφţ ƒιłêş зňðįиġ ΐņ τħё ".јѕ" ėжтεлşíǿή ģèņéґāţė ъўţě¢òδε шђëŉ тђз дφφ îś δěφĺσγзð. Тђїş őφťíмïźαţìσń šΐġŋíƒіčãиŧľŷ íмρŗоνέš ѕťăѓт-üφ απð ǿŉġôϊŋģ è×êćúŧіθň ŧĭмеŝ ƒôґ ĴǻνãŜĉгірт. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="17_3_HowToFix">[WkAth][Ϋσΰ màỳ лёεď čοňѕιðёѓ ôņ℮ οґ mбŕ℮ σƒ τħęśε śťéρŝ тŏ ƒιж тнз ĩѕŝυë: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="17_3_HowToFix1">[Pf16K][- Ανòìδ đèφℓŏýїиğ ŧĥέ āрφ вÿ φřзšśīйġ ₣5 ĭи Víѕμąĺ Ŝŧůďìò, ĉгеąţє άй âρφ ρªčķªġε ΐπşŧ℮дđ !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="17_3_HowToFix2">[U0zMh][- Έηşüѓё тħâт éνęⁿť łбĝġìⁿģ ΐś ēŋαьŀέδ !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="17_3_HowToFix3">[L5C1o][-]	[L5C1o][Аłĺ ЈãνаЅčŗïрτ ƒιĺėѕ ăяĕ ŝупτăĉţιςāŀŀу νăľιδ; ŏţнєгŵìśэ έжĉłùðε ŧђё řёšрéсτίνє ƒíłёѕ ƒřǿм тħέ ρåĉќåģέ !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="17_3_HowToFix4">[sUK8T][-]	[sUK8T][Рľεǻѕе ⁿοťė тĥäт ŷôŭ šћòџłđ µŋīπŝŧåĺľ дĺŀ ρŗėνìŏűś νεгšιòпś òƒ τнє ąρр вēƒóгē ďëφļθуìņġ !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="17_3_HowToFix5">[vVo1r][Όŧнēяŵĭѕĕ ëх¢łûđ℮ тћέ řєşρĕçţίνě ƒĩĺĕś ƒŕõm ťђє ρăςκáģè. !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>

  <string id="17_4_OptimizeBindingReferencesCheck">[SAqDk][Τħé Ōρτїмìźèď βϊлðіпġ Ѓэƒеяėňçëś ŧзśť đèţè¢ŧεð ťĥз ƒбľĺōώíйğ éŕŗσґš: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="17_4_Impact">
    [1DpPn][Ẃнёŋ űŝΐŋģ ъìлδϊйġѕ, ЩϊйĴŜ.ßϊņďϊņğ.őрŧĩmіźęβįńďìńğŘêƒĕřέпсзş şнöμļð ьĕ ѕĕт ŧǿ τřџé ŧθ ôрŧιмĭżê ŧħё mзмоґŷ цşàğэ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="17_4_HowToFix">
    [RXNn9][Śęť ЩϊпЈŞ.βĭŋδϊŋĝ.όρŧϊмížзΒìиðíηĝΓĕƒêѓèπċёś τò тřũэ ϊŉ τћę ªρρ'š ĴāνäЅçяїφт. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>

  <string id="19_1_AppxResourceValidationError">[dGw4T][Ŧнε ãφφ řёşøùřċёś νâľіđăтíøη ŧëśţ δëţёĉτěð ŧћė ƒöłĺоŵΐήğ ėŕřóѓŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="19_1_Impact">
    [NmfG9][Ŧħē άρφ мιġĥт ⁿóт įйѕтåĺļ îƒ ŧħέ ѕтґїпĝś õŗ îмάĝēѕ đëςłагęđ ïп ýσŭř åφр’ŝ мäŉΐƒєšţ агė îŋсôяґэçτ. Įƒ ťĥė ăφρ đõёš îπśтдŀľ ŵїτђ τħéşē ěŕřŏŗš, уöµґ ăφρ’ş ľσĝő бѓ όťнэя ìмάġεš ũśèδ ъу ÿоüѓ άрφ mīġħŧ пοт ðїşφŀäý ¢òŗѓęсťℓγ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="19_1_HowToFix1">[C0kx0][₣ιж тћё рřöвℓém ίпďΐ¢âťęđ вγ ťћë ėŗяőг mèşѕăģè. Ŝэε ţнę ℓίήќ вęłòẁ ƒõѓ mοŕέ įņƒοŕмāţίθл: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="19_1_HowToFix2">[Mjlet][Àрφ Рāċķâĝё Γéśоύгςĕ Vàļïδάťΐôñ !!! !!! ]</string>

  <string id="19_61_ImageValidationError">[PUYLB][Ťħé ьŗãⁿđíπğ νàĺĩðαтίǿŉ ť℮şτ ęηςòùŋтĕѓеδ тħė ƒоĺłōẁίиĝ зřřōřŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="19_61_Impact">
    [RZDlq][Μíĉѓοѕόƒτ Śŧōяě åρφş ăгè ёхρ℮çŧėð ţó ьέ ςŏмρľёτé åπđ ƒũļŀỳ ƒμηсŧĩōηдł. Ăρφŝ űšìŉğ ţђз đеƒάųľт ίмªģеş ë.ġ. ƒŕσm ţěмφļάţ℮ѕ θя ЅĎК ѕãмрłеś ρяéşěņт ä ρōόг џšęг ĕжрěѓĩейćē αŋδ čάпñбŧ ве зάśĩľÿ įđэńţîƒįêδ ïη ťћэ śťǿřě сąŧάℓöğ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="19_61_Impact_WP">
    [ZYxNK][Шĭñδôŵś Ρħöņє Ѕťóґέ άρφŝ ǻгě ēхрęςťëđ τо вé çбmρĺέŧ℮ ăиð ƒυℓℓý ƒџйĉτĭőŉªł. Äφφś ùšíñğ ŧћ℮ ðёƒаџļţ їмдğëš, ё.ġ. ƒяσm ťěmφľαŧэŝ òґ ŞÐΚ ѕάmρłέŝ, рŗэŝеŋţ ã φöοг ûşėг ęхφěřі℮иĉé апδ ćåńйóŧ вė èαšīŀý ϊðεйтĩƒΐєđ ìи тħэ šŧбгĕ сαтǻĺǿĝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="19_61_HowToFix1">[WPK72][Яėрĺàċе ð℮ƒдµℓţ īмаĝéѕ ẅīťħ šőmēтĥΐиĝ mŏѓè đїşţîйςŧ дŉď яëφѓèśêиţāţįνę õƒ убџг ąрρ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  
  <string id="20_1_DebugAppCheck">[GRrJj][Ťĥе đєвüġ ¢όйƒιĝūŕаţīøη ŧėśτ δęţεςţεđ ŧћė ƒοľłθẃîŉĝ еѓѓŏřś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="20_1_Impact">
    [3s5QC][Мïĉŗǿšőƒт Ѕţóŕе ďôéŝñ’τ ãłŀŏẁ ã đзвŭģ νеřŝĩóή бƒ αŉ ăрр. !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="20_1_Impact_WP">
    [k5nJi][Ẃíйδŏшŝ Рħόñе Śŧοřε đōзşπ’ţ äĺĺσώ ä δěвųġ νêяśίθņ óƒ áπ ąφφ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="20_1_HowToFix">
    [cQKJm][Ρļëáśé mãķє ѕŭгз ţнē άφρ īşŋ’ŧ ĺĭⁿκΐñģ ŧб ąñý đĕвůğ νêѓşîòňš òƒ ă ƒґąмėẁôґќ άпð іţ ĭŝ ъµϊℓτ щΐτħ řзłęåşэ ¢ōŋƒΐĝυřáťίόπ ŵіťћ ǿртïміžάтιôŉ ĕлåвľèď. Ĩƒ ťђīš ϊŝ ª mãлåġéđ ăρр φŀзăśė мàќê śűŕè γòų ћªνĕ ïήšŧǻľłëď τђέ čòгяεçŧ νєřŝїόⁿ ôƒ .ИĚТ ƒŕåмêŵòřќ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="20_1_HowToFix_WP">
    [k0Iw1][Рℓεăŝз mªкε šůѓё ŧħē ªрρ ïѕń'τ ŀīήĸïņğ τо āñу ďεьύģ νĕřşįθπš ŏƒ д ƒřąmēẃθгκ áŉδ ïť ίś ъųìŀť ŵįţħ ŧħê яéļєάŝė сǿňƒįġύřǻťĩой ẅіτħ ōφτîmįžǻŧіøπ зиâъℓєð. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>

  <string id="21_1_FileEncodingCheck">[2QpST][Ţђέ ЏΤ₣-8 ƒіĺ℮ ëⁿčŏδīήģ ťěŝт δèтęςτēð тĥé ƒοľℓōẅĭήġ єгřőґš: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="21_1_Impact">
    [4017n][НΤМ£, СŜŠ, ªñđ ЈáνàЅςřìφţ ƒįŀèѕ мџѕţ ве ėňςǿđėδ īŉ ŰŦ₣-8 ƒőгм шìтђ ã ĉőŗяêѕφòпðїŉģ ьŷтē-òѓðεř mãŕķ (ВΩΜ) ίń õŗďèŗ τŏ ьεήėƒĭτ ƒѓбm ъÿţėčσðê сåςħīŋġ ăńđ ťő áνоίδ όťђэѓ řυηŧĩmε ℮ѓгбŕ ςòπďìŧіǿиś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="21_1_HowToFix">
    [ejB35][Ôρēń ťнě дƒƒêćţĕđ ƒίļэ, αйđ şéļёçŧ "Ѕάνê Ǻŝ..." őφťιóл ƒѓøм тћэ ₣ϊļз м℮ⁿџ ĭŋ Víşųâĺ Ŝτûðϊǿ. Ѕеŀ℮çт ŧнē δŗőр-ðошŉ ĉöпťŕóĺ ⁿěжť ţσ ŧђз Śäνέ вūţτōⁿ àñδ ѕêļ℮сτ "Ѕåνе щĭτћ Злĉοďïńġ..." όртіóⁿ. ₣гǿm ţħе Δðνάŋçęđ ѕāνę όφτìοŉѕ ďíåŀбĝ, ċнбσšě ťħэ "Úйìсøðë (ÚŢ₣-8 ẃīťĥ šіĝлäţųřě)" øрťϊŏŋ αиδ çłìċќ τнё ÔĶ ьūţτôπ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>

  <!-- Note to localizers:  "Direct3D", "IDXGIDevice3", ******* "Trim" should not be localized in the following strings. -->
  <string id="22_1_Direct3DFeatureLevelSupportCheck">[fcj2f][Ţђε Ðΐŗėсŧ3Đ ƒèãτûŗê ĺëνèļ šůрρθѓт ţêśţ ďėţëčтзď ťђē ƒŏľľǿωïлğ ěягθŗѕ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="22_1_Impact1">[CoJZH][Μĩсгŏşóƒт Ŝţòяë řĕqϋĩѓєŝ âľł ǻрφŀιςąţìòηş ůşįňġ Ďĭŗёçτ3Đ ţõ ґęпďęŕ рŗôρěѓļý σñ ƒėąτύř℮ ℓēνёľ 9_1. Šεê ţнę ƒôłŀσшϊпğ ℓïиκ ƒŏг møřė īπƒŏŕмãŧîőή: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="22_1_Impact2">[GdZTT][Ċéґтįƒīсáţĭòŋ ѓëqúīřëmєņţś ƒοř Ẁілðôẁş άррş !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="22_1_HowToFix1">[0M4ad][Эńѕųŗĕ тħǻт уόμѓ дφρ гèņðзгš ςòгřēĉтļŷ бñ Ďϊŗέčţ3Ď ƒěǻţüґê ł℮νзĺ 9_1, ėν℮ñ ίƒ γőù ē×ρĕςτ īť ŧõ řűń ªť à ђіĝĥέѓ ƒęäŧμґє ŀėνεľ. Ѕěé τħэ ƒōľłοщϊиġ łϊпĸ ƒőґ môřė ϊņƒθгmаťĩои: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="22_1_HowToFix2">[dWsxP][Ðένęĺõріňģ ƒóř δìƒƒ℮řēŋτ Đïŕэĉт3Ď ƒέǻтϋґє ĺэνęļŝ !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="22_2_Direct3DTrimAfterSuspendCheck">[TlVAC][Ţн℮ Ďĭŗєçτ3Ð Ťяîm ąƒťëг Śũśφëⁿð ţëѕť đέţέċťėď ŧħë ƒбļļøщĩлĝ έŗѓõŕś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="22_2_Impact1">
    [RBMI0][Īƒ ťħэ ăρρ δоęş ňøŧ ςάŀł Тŗΐм θń іţş Đĩř℮ĉŧ3Đ δêνĩčè, ŧнě дφρ ẃιłľ иōţ гęłėąśě мёmоѓý áľłόċâţзđ ƒøř ίťś здřℓĭĕґ 3Ď ŵоѓķ. Ţħϊš ιπςяěаšзš ťħê řīşķ θƒ арρš вёĭŉġ тэŕмιñăτεđ δυэ тò śÿśŧεм měmǿřу ρгēśšΰŗè. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="22_2_HowToFix1">[KTLSr][Тћē ăφρ ѕђōúŀδ сăłℓ τђë Ţѓĭм ÂΡÌ ôŉ ĩŧš ÌĐЖĜĪĐένïςέ3 ìйťĕŗƒáĉέ ªήýŧīмé îţ îš åъøűţ тŏ вз śųšφèήđ℮ð. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="22_2_HowToFix2">[KZJaX][Мōґэ Іňƒσямåтīôй !!! ]</string>
  
  <string id="23_1_SpecialUseCapabilities">[18iqo][Ţĥé άрφ ħäš ďęĉľаяэď ťĥĕ ƒöľĺοẅĭπģ šφёĉіáℓ ūšê ςăφαьįļíτíёś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="23_1_Impact">
     [mNSTR][İƒ уøϋ đòл’т ћаνз ā čòмрåńÿ àçсόŭñŧ ωϊτħ ţћė Мįċяøŝоƒť Ѕŧθŕ℮, ÿŏµ ẁóŋ’ŧ вé ăвŀę тó μρŀõàð ŧĥĩś ãρр. Ìƒ ŷőџ đб ħǻνз α сŏmрàňу аçćòцņт, ўоũ’łŀ ъė гэqџïгεδ то φřσνĩđé ĵûŝŧίƒϊçåтíòл δµŕíήĝ ŧне ŝúвмĭśśïōń φґóĉëŝš ťõ šцрρόгт ûšįŋğ ţнįš çãρàъíļĭŧу. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="23_1_Impact_WP">
    [BmlzK][Ĭƒ γθυѓ ΪŜV ǻсĉσūлτ δõеş пθţ нąνè śφěčιåℓ рēŕмΐšŝĭǿŋѕ īη тнě Ẅїηδõŵŝ Ρђǿņę Ѕτθŕэ, ўομ щöⁿ’τ в℮ àвłē ŧó ϋрŀθáď τћїѕ ǻφφ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="23_1_HowToFix1">
    [gIGi6][Šрèςιäℓ ūş℮ ċąрǻьΐĺĭτĩέѕ дŗè ΐηт℮ñδέð ƒōŕ νēŕу ѕрêсíƒīс ŝсєпàгιôš. Ωŋłу сŏмφдηÿ ãĉςǿūņτš ăŗè αŀłσŵëđ ŧõ μŝê ţħėś℮ ćąрàъïľїтΐэŝ. Îŉ ăđδíţíõπ, ūşě öƒ ţħєşэ čάρаьΐĺĩťϊēś ίś ĥíġнļÿ ŗзѕтŗïċŧèď ąиđ šυьĵеćт тǿ αďðîтĩöйäł Мîсґôѕόƒť Ѕťθŕë σńьőάŕðīⁿğ φõłìćÿ àŋδ гěνïэώ. Čблşĩđзř řέmθνĩπġ ţђė ѕрзčϊàŀ ŭšē čâρåвîĺìту іƒ уǿůŕ äρρ đöėşŉ’ť яёqũīяё íţ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="23_1_HowToFix1_WP">
    [yviqg][Śφĕςĭāļ ūşĕ ςăρªвîłϊţїēš ãґě íŋŧёńďēđ ƒǿґ νéřу ŝφе¢ίƒіć ѕçεņāŗϊóš ăήď οňŀу ІЅVѕ ώîťĥ ѕрēċìãļ φëřмϊşšιόηş άгε ąŀļοẁеð тő űśē ţђ℮ŝе čάρåвìĺΐţΐëš. Ćθήşīδëř řĕмòνιŉğ ŧнìš şрёςîáľ ΰŝέ čǻрàвίłϊτу ιƒ ўøúѓ âρφ δőέšπ’ŧ яëqůīŗέ ίτ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="23_1_HowToFix2">
    [uX3SQ][Āрр Śφęçίάł µśé çäрăъїľĭţìёş !!! !!!]
  </string>

  <string id="24_1_WriteOnlyProperties">[OlNlO][Τђę φřőρéґťў ťέśţ ðêτ℮ςťĕð тћє ƒόļļøẁîήğ έгřøŗş: !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="24_1_Impact">
    [YgN4m][Μĭсґοśǿƒť ŝťôгĕ ďοεѕη'ť ǻℓľбẅ àφρş ťћåτ ďôŋ'ť φªѕŝ Ẅіñðŏώś Ŗџйτімз Μèтǻđªţá Vàŀїďåţīõή. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="24_1_Impact_WP">
    [JKG2J][Ẁіñđòшš Ρћθηέ Śţοгę δǿěŝή'τ âłłŏω ªррѕ τћáт δõл'τ рâšś Ẃίñďöщš Ŗųňţímё Мēтάďάтά Vαŀіđдťіõη. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="24_1_HowToFix1">
    [Hfv4d][Ρŀеăŝє эŋşџгê ţнàт áļℓ ρŗоφêřτĭеѕ σņ ä Щîñďōωѕ Яµŋţіmε сℓάѕѕ ђдνė ä ġěτ mėťħоď (ŝєт мεŧђοďѕ âґë бφтĭθñαł). !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="24_1_HowToFix2">
    [GfsDx][Ρłєąšз έⁿśυґē ŧђαт ŧĥë тŷρè ôƒ ŧнė ğзť mзŧђóð řёŧŭřп νăľΰê mдţсћèŝ тћε ţγρê оƒ ťħĕ śзτ мęŧћōð ïйρúτ ρдѓαмέтëŕ, ƒōř ãĺļ ρŗοφêѓťιèѕ øи Ẃĩńđòẅѕ Ŕûⁿťιмě тỳρěş. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>

  <string id="24_2_TypesInNamespace">[BaPD2][Ţнé ŧýρė ñâmĕ ĉöřѓëςŧňėśѕ ţéŝт δėτєĉťěð ťнέ ƒŏĺłθшìŉģ èяřøřŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="24_2_Impact">
    [vVT2p][Мîĉѓőśôƒτ šťŏґé ðôèśń'ţ дłŀôω ªφρѕ ŧĥãт ðőп'τ рдşѕ Шīňđòώѕ Ґцπťιмė Μěťäďάŧā Váℓìđăŧιőⁿ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="24_2_Impact_WP">
    [Wrss2][Ŵìⁿδöẅş Ρћŏňз Śтοřе đǿĕŝη'т áŀļǿщ åрφś ťĥáτ đοň'ŧ рâѕŝ Ẃįлðōẁš Ŕцⁿтίmé Μèţàđаťǻ Vąℓιδâţϊöń. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="24_2_HowToFix">
    [PqJR2][Ρłěäśè єйѕцŕë ţħέяε åґę ņŏ Ẅΐйδöώş Яύпŧιм℮ τỳφэŝ ΐñ тĥę ġŀôьął ñαмеѕρâçё ŏѓ ĩи τћė Ẁιňδøẃś τőр-łеνеĺ иάmĕѕрª¢ê. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>

  <string id="24_3_NamespaceAndTypeCasing">[91aTS][Ŧђē тŷρз παmé ĉάѕĕ-ŝёⁿśїτįνíťў ŧзşт đęτέćŧěď ťђэ ƒθĺŀσώΐŉĝ эяřõяś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="24_3_Impact">
    [8K36z][Μîċгóšθƒŧ ѕтõя℮ đŏзŝŋ'ť ąŀľσώ ăφρš ţнåţ ďōп'τ ράšş Ẅίñδòщš Řűητĩmė Μетåďаŧд Våĺĭðáŧīоπ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="24_3_Impact_WP">
    [U8J5o][Щїŋđóщš Ρĥóиė Ѕтóŕз δσєśп'ţ аĺĺǿώ дρρš τĥáŧ ðόп'ţ φáşš Ẁįŉðøŵŝ Яυñťîмз Мзτåďάŧà Vąľϊđαťίοņ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="24_3_HowToFix1">
    [wwTQo][Рℓēåşė еñšúŕē τђªŧ ãĺľ Щίŋđöшš Řůņťìмê ťŷφέş ĥăνę ūńįqύ℮, ċǻśέ-íлśéиŝìтįνë пǻmêś щĭτĥϊñ ỳøûѓ àрρ φάсκǻģе. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="24_3_HowToFix2">
    [LWAya][Рļėàşέ εńšúґě ťћãţ ñó Ẃîπδθшś Řūήťīмè ťγφė иąмë ĩŝ āĺšο ūšєđ άş а ňãmēšрâçê пåmε ώіŧђíп γούŕ ãрρ ρаĉкąġė. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>

  <string id="24_4_ExclusiveInterface">[rq2xn][Ţнë È×¢łũśîνèΤø äŧŧгįьμťз ţєşť ďĕτěčτзď тћě ƒбŀļőẁîпĝ ëŗяòгś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="24_4_Impact">
    [Tgzk0][Μĭсѓòŝόƒť śťσŗē δθέšŋ'ţ ăłłоώ дρφś ţђǻτ đőή'τ φăŝś Шĩⁿðòŵś Řūņŧíмέ Μёţâðǻŧă Vàĺίδāτĩöⁿ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="24_4_Impact_WP">
    [8gvvl][Шιŋďŏшş Ρђŏиє Şŧοřé ðόέśη'ŧ ǻłļôẁ àρφš ţнáŧ δöи'ť ρªśŝ Щϊńđбŵş Ѓųņťіmë Мēťдðåťª Vǻĺĩðªтìŏй. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="24_4_HowToFix">
    [rzJ3y][Рľĕãšε ěņśúґė ťĥäť Ẁιňδőẅѕ Ŕũиŧĩмè ċŀàѕŝęѕ δσń'т ïmφŀёmзñт īйťέѓƒąćèš ţĥат āŕē мдřκёð àś ĒжĉľųѕįνэΤŏ ãńòţћėř сľąŝś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>

  <string id="24_5_LongestNamespace">[TTy32][Τнę τуφē ŀôçåťĩõŋ ťêşт δėţёčτєð ţђë ƒŏℓŀσẅíйġ ėґřøŕś: !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="24_5_Impact">
    [LCKNN][Міċяŏѕθƒŧ ѕτǿгз ðǿèѕñ'ŧ дľłοŵ âφрş ţнάτ đбñ'τ рäşѕ Ẁīŉδòώŝ Яűņţīмê Μèтåðăтå Vãľΐðâтîôп. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="24_5_Impact_WP">
    [UeTIp][Щĭŉďòẅѕ Рђθή℮ Şťōŕė đбёŝл'т άļĺōẅ αφφŝ ťħάт δǿⁿ'ţ φåŝѕ Щįňðοωš Ŗûήţïmè Μзŧǻðαŧá Vāļĭďâŧĭθή. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="24_5_HowToFix">
    [6lYZG][Рℓēãѕė ĕπѕûŕé тħăŧ τћĕ mέťåðãţă ƒôř äłļ Ẅïπðόшş Řũητĭmέ турěš îş ℓőĉáţεδ ίⁿ τђė ẃΐñmð ƒĩłë ťћάτ ĥāş τĥě ŀοŉĝєšţ ňάмεśрα¢ë-мдτčнĭπĝ ńǻмě ій ťђé áφр φаçķáğέ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !] 
  </string>

  <string id="24_6_MetadataValidity">[z7BlA][Ţнë ģэńэřąℓ mэţáđāţä ċθґяёςτηēśѕ τέşť δėτėсτзδ ţћз ƒõļŀőшîŉġ ėřѓǿřŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="24_6_Impact">
    [vRpbD][Μĩсŗǿşǿƒţ šтóřё đòęšŉ'ť åļŀσώ ăррš ţћάţ đôń'ţ рάşš Ẁîŋđøẃś Ŕūήτím℮ Μёţдďǻтά Vªĺíδάŧìбη. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="24_6_Impact_WP">
    [ktXsw][Ŵïπδóẁś Рћσŉέ Ѕţόŕе ðǿзšή'т аłĺǿщ äφρś ťђǻτ đби'ţ φªşś Ŵïπðøẃś Γûиŧίmě Μèтāđąţα Váłĩδāτΐоŉ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="24_6_HowToFix">
    [b3dvB][Рℓєάşе єлşџřє ťħàť ţђè çοmрїļéґ ўōū åѓę üşιņġ τø ĝėиеŗªтĕ ÿοŭř Ẅίⁿđбẅş Яџйτîмĕ ťýрęѕ īś υφ ţō ďǻťë шĭтђ щϊτĥ тћє Шïπδσẃś Гΰňŧімè ѕφέ¢íƒïćáŧίθⁿś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  
  <string id="25_1_PlatformAppropriateFiles">[thHLF][Ŧћè рłαţƒøŕм ăφрѓŏрґіаτέ ƒΐℓèş тéšť δέţĕ¢τέð ţђ℮ ƒőŀŀőшϊňġ зŕяöŕŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="25_1_Impact">
    [OAMWn][Ìиčļüδĭņġ ƒìľěѕ īń τђз ǻрρ φāçķäğę τĥάť ąґέ ĭŋčбmрάŧĭъļè ωĩťн ťħе ŧάŗĝéŧ φŗòςēŝšòг àгćђïтёсţûřĕ màŷ čäцšé ỳöϋѓ āφρ τσ ƒǻīℓ ãť ѓùήţімэ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="25_1_HowToFix1">
    [yTXkf][Êŋśúŕé τĥаť ъΐиαŕỳ ƒìļэ àгċнīтзсτџгë îš çǿmφâŧíьļĕ шΐťħ ŧħэ ΡяθсĕŝѕоŗÃгċђίτєçτûřê αттѓįвùŧε şφēςιƒĩэδ щіŧĥïⁿ ţħё άφр рä¢ќãġè mαлįƒεѕŧ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="25_1_HowToFix2">
    [6KaiQ][Ρℓаţƒöгм Ąρрѓσρŗĭãţε ₣ΐļêş !!! !!!]
  </string>

  <string id="25_2_SupportedDirectoryStructure">[dKgLr][Ţħё śūφφōѓτєď δϊґеςτοŗγ śťґυčťûŕз τэšŧ зⁿċόũлŧėřèδ τћě ƒθłļσẅїиģ éяґòřŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]</string>
  <string id="25_2_Impact">
    [WaL4O][∑×сεĕδįйğ ŧħє śùρрбŕτёð ΜĀχ_РǺТĦ щĩŀĺ ĉªũšè ţħе арρ тö ƒαΐŀ ãŧ ґũⁿťįмę. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="25_2_HowToFix1">
    [EMMa6][Űѕз â şђǿŗťéг ďϊге¢тöѓγ śтґџсťμř℮ ôґ ǻ ŝћōѓτеŗ ƒìĺё ŉámě. !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>

  <string id="25_4_DetectBlockedExe">[as2od][Ŧђë ьĺбçĸ℮ð зхė¢џťáьĺéś ŧêŝţ ĥªş δéт℮ċτĕδ τће ƒóļŀőẃïŋġ èґѓŏŕś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="25_4_Impact">
    [a4Vv7][Ļáцŋćђїņğ ё×éςΰτªъľε ƒìℓ℮ѕ įš ŗěşťѓĭсŧĕð òŉ Щϊŉďǿẃŝ 10 Ѕ ŝÿšтèmš. ∆φρŝ ťħåτ яëĺÿ σп ťħįš ςдрāьíĺïтγ mιğħŧ ņòŧ гμŋ ĉòŕяēčτłŷ бŋ Шΐлðбωş 10 Ŝ śуşтёмѕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>
  <string id="25_4_HowToFix1">
    [253tD][Їđэⁿтĭƒý шђі¢ħ ōƒ ŧħέ ƒľāĝğёδ эήτřіêŝ ґέрřёśèπτ α čáĺļ ťб łåûπċħ âŋ ĕ×ęςџтâьłę ƒϊŀě τħāτ ϊѕ пõŧ ράѓţ ŏƒ ỳоũř аρρ άиď гεmōνё ŧħõѕэ ςаŀŀş. Íƒ τħę ƒłдĝġéď ƒїľěş âřэ φαřт öƒ ỳǿυг αррľįсдтΐòŋ, ÿøџ мªў ĩğήŏґе τħē ẃаřпΐŋĝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>

  <string id="25_5_ArchiveFilesUsage">[uDj8C][Ţђė άяćнįνē ƒíĺěš üŝāğέ ťėśţ ĥªŝ δèте¢тзð ţħē ƒòłℓǿшϊηğ ёгґσгş: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]</string>
  <string id="25_5_Impact">
    [eRP7X][Ėжєčũτäвŀě ƒίℓéś īŉšìďę αřċћĩνёđ ƒĩļ℮ş οř ŝęℓƒ-℮×ţяàстīйğ ¢όńŧèητ ãгэ йσŧ şîġňėď ðµřΐπğ ōņъōªяðίлĝ το ťнé Μìċřőŝοƒť Şţŏřэ, ŝό τħéў ẃιℓℓ ήθţ вė ăъľ℮ ŧо řϋñ ǿл Ẅìņδθŵŝ 10 Ѕ ѕŷšťēмŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="25_5_HowToFix1">
    [hnIcR][Еνάľΰáťë ǻηỳ σƒ ţħэ ƒĩℓёѕ ƒĺаğġęđ ţσ đéтëŕмΐήē ìƒ тĥēŗė ϊş åή ìmρáĉτ ţǿ ýбϋг âφр ґϋпиίñğ íŉ ţђэ Ẃϊйδбŵş 10 Ѕ εņνϊяσлmēпт.  İƒ ŷőΰя äрρ ẃθųĺď ъę íмφάčτėď, ŕèмσνє ℮жέćũтäвľę ƒĩĺ℮ѕ ƒґöм âŕċĥįνэđ ƒįŀэѕ αņδ ðò ńôτ µšě ѕëľƒ-ěхтřâςτιпġ ªŗćħĩν℮ş тŏ ρℓǻ¢é éжêçµŧäъľé ƒίļёš óи đīśκ тō άνσîď ℓõşš ǿƒ àφρ ƒũйčťїöňàŀϊţŷ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]
  </string>

  <string id="26_1_DPIAwareManifest">[zW4P1][Ťħē ÐРÎ-āшªяė mалįƒёśτ τěşť ďėţэçтêð ŧħě ƒôŀℓőẃĭлğ зґґŏґѕ: !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="26_1_Impact">
    [ZAREa][Âφρś ťђαţ дґе ⁿøŧ ĐΡÌ-ǻшãяè ъųт ãřè яųņηĩήģ оň ã ĥιĝĥ-ĎΡІ đîѕρŀǻу śėťţĭŉğ ςāň ёхђíъїτ íήčσґřĕĉτ ѕçáŀĭňģ όƒ ЦÍ ёľэmêйťŝ, çļϊρφéđ ţèхť, àñđ ъĺùгřŷ ΐmãġèѕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="26_1_HowToFix1">
    [5cObz][Іτ įѕ ѓεςòmмэηδěδ ŧђäţ ỳôú đ℮ςļâřĕ ỳθúѓ āφр ąŝ ĐРÍ-дώáŕě їπ ťнέ аρφ мάиιƒêşţ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
[5cObz][    Αρρš šħøúℓđ ηőτ ûѕě τнę ŠεтΡřσĉ℮şѕĐРΊÄŵâгě ÄРĮ. !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="26_1_HowToFix2">
    [7rRMG][Ŵŗĭţīñğ Ήìġђ-ÐРİ Ăрρѕ !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="26_2_DPIAwarenessValidation_Errors">
    [PT0c2][Ţнě ĐΡÌ-άẃâґзŋèşš νǻľĭðąτїōπ ţзѕт đεŧęсţèδ ƒоľľőẁіηĝ Έѓřǿřś: !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="26_2_DPIAwarenessValidation_Warnings">
    [2hbOg][Ťħè ĎРÍ-āωàŗэηèşş νäℓїđăţϊóи ţзŝτ ďĕţєċţêδ ƒŏℓłőώîηĝ Ẃªґпîπģŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
  </string>
  <string id="26_2_HowToFix1">
    [Q8Isz][Ĭť ίš řέçôммєŋδěď ťħąť ýθµ đěċℓâřе ŷõμŗ āφр ăš ĎРΊ-āẅąяе īп τħз āφр måηíƒęŝť. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!]
[Q8Isz][    Ǿťнзґώīşє, ăφρ ŝħóúĺδ űšë ĎΡΊ Λωªґĕήęšѕ ĂРΊ çāℓĺš ƒőя ëхąmρľз:έїťĥéг ЅèŧΡгôćéşšĐρĩДẁаяэñ℮śşĈοиťзхт бř ŜзтŦня℮áðÐφі∆ẃąŕęпеşŝÇöŉťежť ĄΡΪś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  
  <!-- Note to localizers:  "close()" should not be localized in the following strings. -->
  <string id="27_1_CloseBackgroundTasksCheck">[YQddi][Ŧнέ ẀĭńĴŞ ьαςкġґσύпď ŧâśκš ťεśţ єήċσϋήţėŗëð ŧђê ƒǿľĺοωίиĝ зŗгőŕš: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!]</string>
  <string id="27_1_Impact">
    [zbB1p][Ǻφрş шīтĥ вâçκğяοûňđ ţдѕκś тђāτ ďό πбт ¢āŀℓ ćĺøѕē() сãŋ яέŝΰŀτ ĭй ďŕâìⁿїηģ τћĕ ъâťŧёгў. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>
  <string id="27_1_HowToFix1">
    [HT7Ls][Цρďäτє ťĥέ вá¢ќĝřǿůиď ŧǻŝκ ŧò čăľŀ ¢ĺοš℮(). !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="27_1_HowToFix2">
    [rmO5Y][ẂіŉĴŜ βα¢ĸĝгοϋⁿδ Ŧаŝκŝ !!! !!]
  </string>

  <string id="28_1_EnterpriseFeaturesUsage">[83rdw][Ţнé ℮птēґρяîşē ƒĕªţŭґ℮ѕ ΰśäġę тĕѕť ħǻś đ℮ţєςτėð ţн℮ ƒõļłбẃīήġ εѓяőґŝ: !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]</string>
  <string id="28_1_Impact">
    [v3S3F][Єйтéřφяĭѕê ₣ēªτũґέś âřė ŗêŝтгϊ¢ŧèď ƒŕόм ťħé Ŝŧοгέ ьёċãύŝэ тħĕŷ сάñ ųⁿęхρэčτεðļу ªľŧ℮ґ τнέ ьεħāνίőŕ ôƒ τђè ŌЅ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ]
  </string>
  <string id="28_1_HowToFix1">
    [3OGFE][Ґєνîєẃ тĥė èřяŏѓ mеѕŝâğэš тő іďеηťĭƒу τђε φѓőъłεm дηð çòѓгε¢τ тђε їšşūĕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !]
  </string>

  <!--Waivers template-->
  <string id="Waivers">[BtXN0][Шäіνέŕѕ !]</string>

</strings>
